{
  "sections": [
    {
      "wordsets": [
        {
          "title": "2.1",
          "definitions": {
            "PEER": {
              "word": "PEER",
              "phonetic": "(pEr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to look carefully, stare </p><p>To PEER at something is to look at it long and carefully in order to see it clearly. </p><p>“He PEERED through his glasses at the dim object.” </p><p>“The children PEERED out at us from behind the fence.” </p><p>“Jim PEERED at the street sign in the snowstorm.</p><p>” Usage: PEER is usually used with at.</p>"
            },
            "SIGNIFY": {
              "word": "SIGNIFY",
              "phonetic": "(sig'-nÔøΩfl)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to mean, show, be a sign of </p><p>You can see the word <i class=“def-ital\">sign</i> in SIGNIFY (although the words are pronounced differently). To SIGNIFY something is to be a sign of it, to show it. See <i class=“def-ital\">-fy</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“The ship’s anchor on Rhode Island’s flag SIGNIFIES the importance of the sea in the state’s history. </p><p>“He SIGNIFIED that he was still there by raising his hand.</p><p>” Often the sense of SIGNIFY is to mean. “The seal at the bottom of the page SIGNIFIES that this is an official document.”</p>"
            },
            "TASK": {
              "word": "TASK",
              "phonetic": "(task)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a job, duty, chore, assignment A TASK is a job or duty, usually one that is difficult. It is often work that is assigned or given to someone.</p><p> “She took on the hard TASK of cleaning the garage.” </p><p>“Bob was given the TASK of washing the attic windows.” </p><p>“Your TASK for today is to finish Chapter Three and write a summary of it.” </p><p>“We divided the TASKS according to age.”</p>"
            },
            "AVALANCHE": {
              "word": "AVALANCHE",
              "phonetic": "(av'-ÔøΩlanch)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a snow or rock slide/n An AVALANCHE is a huge mass of snow, earth, or rock which comes crashing down the side of a mountain.</p><p> “The Alpine village was completely covered by the AVALANCHE.\"</p><p> “They say any loud noise, like a gunshot, can cause an AVALANCHE.\"</p><p> From this basic meaning, AVALANCHE has come to be used about any sudden great rush or outpouring.</p><p> “The young actor received an AVALANCHE of mail after his first movie.”</p>"
            },
            "THRESHOLD": {
              "word": "THRESHOLD",
              "phonetic": "(thresh'-hOld",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">thresh’-Old) n.: an entrance, doorstep </p><p> A THRESHOLD is a board or stone at the bottom of a doorway or entrance into a building or room. THRESHOLD is usually used simply to mean an -<i class=“def-ital\">entrance</i> to a room. </p><p>“He stood on the THRESHOLD waiting to be admitted.” </p><p>“The bridegroom is supposed to carry the bride across the THRESHOLD of their new home.” </p><p>Because you cross the THRESHOLD in order to enter, the word has also come to be used about the entrance to or beginning of almost  anything. </p><p>“He is at the THRESHOLD of a great career in politics.” “This is the THRESHOLD of a new Golden Age in human affairs.”</p>"
            },
            "TRANSFORM": {
              "word": "TRANSFORM",
              "phonetic": "(trans-form')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to change /nYou can see the word <i class=“def-ital\">form</i> in TRANSFORM. To TRANSFORM something is to change its shape or form. See <i class=“def-ital\">trans-</i> under Prefixes. </p><p>“Solar cells TRANSFORM sunlight into electricity.” </p><p>“Her appearance was totally TRANSFORMED when she changed from blue jeans to an evening gown.” </p><p>“The ugly duckling was TRANSFORMED into a beautiful swan.” </p><p>When something is TRANSFORMED it undergoes a TRANSFORMATION. </p><p>“His TRANSFORMATION from bus driver to movie star happened in less than six months.\"</p><p> In the Pretest, <i class=“def-ital\">move</i> is the most commonly chosen wrong answer for TRANSFORM, perhaps because TRANSFORM sounds like <i class=“def-ital\">transfer</i>, which means to <i class=“def-ital\">move</i>. Other forms of the word: TRANSFORMATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "REPLY": {
              "word": "REPLY",
              "phonetic": "(ri-pll')",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an answer, response </p><p>A REPLY is an <i class=“def-ital\">answer</i>. </p><p>“His REPLY to the question was hard to understand.\"</p><p>“What did you say in REPLY to that?” </p><p>You don’t have to REPLY in words. </p><p>“Their REPLY to our request was to laugh at us.” </p><p>REPLY is also a verb. </p><p>“I REPLIED that I didn’t know anything about it.” </p><p>“Please REPLY to his letter as soon as you can.”</p>"
            },
            "TUTOR": {
              "word": "TUTOR",
              "phonetic": "(tU'-tÔøΩr",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">tyU’-tÔøΩr) v.: to teach, train </p><p>TUTOR means to <i class=“def-ital\">teach</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">train</i>, usually where one teacher teaches one pupil. To TUTOR someone is to give him private, personal lessons, usually in one subject. </p><p>“My father is getting someone to TUTOR me in math.” </p><p>TUTOR is also a noun meaning a <i class=“def-ital\">teacher- or <i class=“def-ital\">trainer</i>. </p><p>“Mr. Jones is looking for a job as a TUTOR of English.” </p><p>“Jane never went to school; she was taught at home by a TUTOR.”</p>"
            },
            "PULVERIZE": {
              "word": "PULVERIZE",
              "phonetic": "(puhl'-vÔøΩr-lz)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to crush, grind into dust </p><p>PULVERIZE comes from the Latin word for <i class=“def-ital\">dust</i>. To PULVERIZE something is to crush it so completely that it is turned into powder or dust. </p><p>“The miller PULVERIZED the wheat between the grindstones.” </p><p>In general use the word means to destroy completely. </p><p>“The invading army was PULVERIZED by our superior forces.” </p><p>“The boxer PULVERIZED his weaker opponent.”</p>"
            },
            "ACCURATE": {
              "word": "ACCURATE",
              "phonetic": "(ak'-yÔøΩrit)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">correct, exact </p><p>The <i class=“def-ital\">cur</i> part of ACCURATE comes from a Latin word for <i class=“def-ital\">care</i>. Something that is ACCURATE is <i class=“def-ital\">correct</i>, without errors, especially as a result of taking care. </p><p>“Her income tax report is ACCURATE to the penny.” </p><p>“He made an ACCURATE guess about how fast they were traveling.” </p><p>Someone who is ACCURATE does not make mistakes. </p><p>“He is usually ACCURATE in his predictions about who will win the election.” </p><p>The noun form is ACCURACY. “His ACCURACY in hitting the bullseye on the dartboard was unbelievable.” </p><p>“We look for ACCURACY rather than speed in this kind of work.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ACCURACY, n.</p>"
            },
            "ASSIST": {
              "word": "ASSIST",
              "phonetic": "(ÔøΩsist')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to help, aid </p><p>ASSIST comes from Latin words meaning to <i class=“def-ital\">stand by</i>. To ASSIST someone is to help him by giving him support or doing something for him. </p><p>“Several nurses ASSISTED the doctor during the operation.” </p><p>“I wanted to ASSIST my brother, but he said he could do it by himself.” </p><p>“His deputy ASSISTED him in writing the report.” </p><p>ASSISTANCE is the act of helping. </p><p>“The baby didn’t need anyone’s ASSISTANCE in walking across the room.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ASSISTANCE, n. ASSISTANT, n.</p>"
            },
            "CONCLUDE": {
              "word": "CONCLUDE",
              "phonetic": "(kÔøΩn-klUd')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to end; to decide </p><p>The verb CONCLUDE has two meanings. The first is to <i class=“def-ital\">end</i>. </p><p>“He CONCLUDED the meeting by asking everyone to leave.” </p><p>“The teacher always CONCLUDES the class by asking if there are any further questions.” </p><p>CONCLUDE also means “to reach a final judgment,” <i class=“def-ital\">to decide</i>. </p><p>“After a great deal of thought, we CONCLUDED that it was best for her to go to a private school.” </p><p>“The detective CONCLUDED that Mr. Perkins was not to blame for the robbery.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: CONCLUSION, n. </p><p>CONCLUSIVE, adj.</p>"
            },
            "DROUGHT": {
              "word": "DROUGHT",
              "phonetic": "(drowt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a dry period </p><p>A DROUGHT is a long period of dry weather. </p><p>“All the grass turned brown and the crops failed during the DROUGHT.” </p><p>“The DROUGHT finally ended when a thunderstorm soaked the region.” </p><p>DROUGHT is sometimes used to mean any kind of long shortage or lack of something. </p><p>“The team finally ended its season-long scoring DROUGHT by getting four goals in a game.” </p><p>The most commonly chosen incorrect answer is <i class=“def-ital\">flood</i>, which is an opposite of DROUGHT.</p>"
            },
            "EDIBLE": {
              "word": "EDIBLE",
              "phonetic": "(ed'-ÔøΩbÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">fit to be eaten, suitable for food, not poisonous </p><p>Something that is EDIBLE is able to be eaten. (See <i class=“def-ital\">-able</i> under Suffixes.) The word does not mean that something tastes good or is good for you to eat, only that it is fit to be eaten. </p><p>“The food was so bad it was barely EDIBLE.” </p><p>“This fruit will not be EDIBLE until it ripens.” </p><p>The plural noun EDIBLES is a fancy word for food. EDIBLES are things which are fit to be eaten. </p><p>Other forms of the word: EDIBLES, n.</p>"
            },
            "PRIVILEGE": {
              "word": "PRIVILEGE",
              "phonetic": "(priv'-ÔøΩlij",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">priv’-lij) n.: a special right, special benefit </p><p>A PRIVILEGE is a special right which is given to some but not to others. </p><p>“He was given the PRIVILEGE of watching television until eleven o’clock on weekends.” </p><p>“We have the PRIVILEGE of parking our car on this street.” </p><p>“Should doctors have special PRIVILEGES the rest of us don’t have?” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Sworn duty</i> is often chosen as the meaning of PRIVILEGE. This phrase is actually just about an opposite of PRIVILEGE. A <i class=“def-ital\">duty</i> is something you have to do; a PRIVILEGE is something you are allowed to do. </p><p>Other forms of the word: PRIVILEGED, adj.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "1",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "PEER at them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "look closely",
                    "laugh",
                    "take aim",
                    "shout",
                    "jump"
                  ],
                  "word": "PEER",
                  "correct": "look closely"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "What does this SIGNIFY?",
                  "answers": [
                    "need",
                    "improve",
                    "stop",
                    "mean",
                    "use"
                  ],
                  "word": "SIGNIFY",
                  "correct": "mean"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Important TASK.",
                  "answers": [
                    "order",
                    "thought",
                    "question",
                    "job",
                    "trip"
                  ],
                  "word": "TASK",
                  "correct": "job"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Saw the AVALANCHE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "blizzard",
                    "army",
                    "spear",
                    "earthquake",
                    "snow slide"
                  ],
                  "word": "AVALANCHE",
                  "correct": "snow slide"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "At the THRESHOLD.",
                  "answers": [
                    "top",
                    "entrance",
                    "stairs",
                    "prison",
                    "barn"
                  ],
                  "word": "THRESHOLD",
                  "correct": "entrance"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To TRANSFORM it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "change",
                    "move",
                    "lose",
                    "keep",
                    "break"
                  ],
                  "word": "TRANSFORM",
                  "correct": "change"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Usual REPLY.",
                  "answers": [
                    "amount",
                    "idea",
                    "question",
                    "answer",
                    "talk"
                  ],
                  "word": "REPLY",
                  "correct": "answer"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We will TUTOR him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "forget",
                    "teach",
                    "encourage",
                    "amuse",
                    "drive"
                  ],
                  "word": "TUTOR",
                  "correct": "teach"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PULVERIZE them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "open",
                    "strengthen",
                    "squeeze",
                    "cut",
                    "crush"
                  ],
                  "word": "PULVERIZE",
                  "correct": "crush"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Your report is ACCURATE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "correct",
                    "revealing",
                    "helpful",
                    "wrong",
                    "clever"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACCURATE",
                  "correct": "correct"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Please ASSIST him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "join",
                    "obey",
                    "stop",
                    "help",
                    "ask"
                  ],
                  "word": "ASSIST",
                  "correct": "help"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CONCLUDED at ten o'clock.",
                  "answers": [
                    "changed",
                    "opened",
                    "ended",
                    "met",
                    "agreed"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONCLUDE",
                  "correct": "ended"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Predicted the DROUGHT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "defeat",
                    "dry period",
                    "flood",
                    "windstorm",
                    "heat wave"
                  ],
                  "word": "DROUGHT",
                  "correct": "dry period"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "This was EDIBLE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "sweet",
                    "silly",
                    "good tasting",
                    "burned",
                    "fit to eat"
                  ],
                  "word": "EDIBLE",
                  "correct": "fit to eat"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It was his PRIVILEGE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "secrecy",
                    "turn",
                    "sworn duty",
                    "special right",
                    "present"
                  ],
                  "word": "PRIVILEGE",
                  "correct": "special right"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Can you PEER at something that is far away?",
                  "word": "PEER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does + SIGNIFY the word plus?",
                  "word": "SIGNIFY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is eating cake a TASK for most people?",
                  "word": "TASK",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it safe to be in front of an AVALANCHE?",
                  "word": "AVALANCHE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "If you are on the THRESHOLD of something, have you just completed it?",
                  "word": "THRESHOLD",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a caterpillar undergo a TRANSFORMATION when it becomes a butterfly?",
                  "word": "TRANSFORM",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually expect a REPLY when they ask a question?",
                  "word": "REPLY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Should a person who can't speak Spanish become a TUTOR of it?",
                  "word": "TUTOR",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a rock be PULVERIZED?",
                  "word": "PULVERIZE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "If a clock is ten minutes fast, does it give you the ACCURATE time?",
                  "word": "ACCURATE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do most adults need ASSISTANCE in putting on their clothes?",
                  "word": "ASSIST",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does dinner usually CONCLUDE with dessert?",
                  "word": "CONCLUDE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually enjoy DROUGHTS?",
                  "word": "DROUGHT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "When food turns rotten, does it become EDIBLE?",
                  "word": "EDIBLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do some people have more PRIVILEGES than others?",
                  "word": "PRIVILEGE",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "The old man PEERED at Jim for several minutes before recognizing him.",
                  "word": "PEER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He nodded his head to SIGNIFY that he was ready.",
                  "word": "SIGNIFY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Sandra had the difficult TASK of getting the house ready for the party.",
                  "word": "TASK",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The announcement of the job opening produced an AVALANCHE of applications for it.",
                  "word": "AVALANCHE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "George couldn't make up his mind to go in; he just stood on the THRESHOLD and looked around.",
                  "word": "THRESHOLD",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His company TRANSFORMED him from the Chicago office to the New York office.",
                  "word": "TRANSFORM",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He REPLIED to her greeting with a nod.",
                  "word": "REPLY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "When you are failing a course, it might be wise to get a TUTOR.",
                  "word": "TUTOR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The cement factory uses a rock-crushing machine to PULVERIZE stones.",
                  "word": "PULVERIZE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Jim practiced for hours to increase his ACCURACY in shooting the basketball.",
                  "word": "ACCURATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She ASSISTED that we all come to the party.",
                  "word": "ASSIST",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He CONCLUDED to them that he was going away.",
                  "word": "CONCLUDE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The severe DROUGHT left two feet of snow on the ground.",
                  "word": "DROUGHT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EDIBLE mushrooms are not poisonous.",
                  "word": "EDIBLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "As punishment, he was given the PRIVILEGE of taking out the garbage for a month.",
                  "word": "PRIVILEGE",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "PEER",
                  "answers": [
                    "notice",
                    "glance",
                    "hear"
                  ],
                  "word": "PEER",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SIGNIFY",
                  "answers": [
                    "show",
                    "mean",
                    "stay"
                  ],
                  "word": "SIGNIFY",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TASK",
                  "answers": [
                    "cry",
                    "work",
                    "struggle"
                  ],
                  "word": "TASK",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "AVALANCHE",
                  "answers": [
                    "snow",
                    "time",
                    "rush"
                  ],
                  "word": "AVALANCHE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "THRESHOLD",
                  "answers": [
                    "doorway",
                    "beginning",
                    "exit"
                  ],
                  "word": "THRESHOLD",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TRANSFORM",
                  "answers": [
                    "copy",
                    "change",
                    "vary"
                  ],
                  "word": "TRANSFORM",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "REPLY",
                  "answers": [
                    "read",
                    "respond",
                    "answer"
                  ],
                  "word": "REPLY",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TUTOR",
                  "answers": [
                    "remember",
                    "train",
                    "teach"
                  ],
                  "word": "TUTOR",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PULVERIZE",
                  "answers": [
                    "grind",
                    "twist",
                    "destroy"
                  ],
                  "word": "PULVERIZE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ACCURATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "right",
                    "full",
                    "definite"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACCURATE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ASSIST",
                  "answers": [
                    "support",
                    "use",
                    "aid"
                  ],
                  "word": "ASSIST",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CONCLUDE",
                  "answers": [
                    "remember",
                    "decide",
                    "finish"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONCLUDE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DROUGHT",
                  "answers": [
                    "dampness",
                    "heat",
                    "dryness"
                  ],
                  "word": "DROUGHT",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EDIBLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "eatable",
                    "nonpoisonous",
                    "harmful"
                  ],
                  "word": "EDIBLE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PRIVILEGE",
                  "answers": [
                    "desire",
                    "right",
                    "benefit"
                  ],
                  "word": "PRIVILEGE",
                  "correct": "0"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.2",
          "definitions": {
            "SEIZE": {
              "word": "SEIZE",
              "phonetic": "(sEz)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to grab, take, grasp, snatch </p><p>SEIZE means “to take suddenly and by force,” to <i class=“def-ital\">grab</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">snatch</i>. </p><p>“The child SEIZED the piece of candy and ran off with it.” </p><p>SEIZE is often used about grabbing a chance or opportunity. </p><p>“I will SEIZE every chance I get to practice skating.” </p><p>The noun from SEIZE is SEIZURE. </p><p>“He said that the police’s SEIZURE of his car was illegal.” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Find</i> is the most commonly chosen wrong answer in the Pretest. <i class=“def-ital\">Finding</i> something is not the same as SEIZING it, however. </p><p>Other forms of the word: SEIZURE, n.</p>"
            },
            "GAINFUL": {
              "word": "GAINFUL",
              "phonetic": "(gAn'-fal)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">producing a gain, profitable </p><p>A GAIN is an increase or a profit. </p><p>“The stock market made a GAIN of five points yester- day.” </p><p>Something which is GAINFUL produces a GAIN. (See <i class=“def-ital\">-ful</i> under Suffixes.) GAINFUL is used about jobs, businesses, and similar activities which earn money for the person doing them. </p><p>“After years of doing only volunteer work, she decided to seek GAINFJJL employment.” </p><p>“He was good at what he did, but it wasn’t a very GAINFUL trade.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: GAIN, n., v.</p>"
            },
            "INDUSTRIOUS": {
              "word": "INDUSTRIOUS",
              "phonetic": "(in-duhs'-trE-ÔøΩs)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">hardworking, diligent, busy  </p><p>One meaning of the word INDUSTRY is “steady attention to business,” <i class=“def-ital\">hard work</i>. </p><p>“His success was due to years of steady INDUSTRY.” </p><p>INDUSTRIOUS means “full of INDUSTRY,” <i class=“def-ital\">hardworking</i>, and is used about people. See <i class=“def-ital\">-ous</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“He was a very INDUSTRIOUS student; he always seemed to be doing his homework.” </p><p>“You will have to be more INDUSTRIOUS in doing your job if you want to get a raise.” </p><p>The most commonly chosen wrong answer is <i class=“def-ital\">brilliant</i>. This is perhaps due to a confusion between INDUSTRIOUS and <i class=“def-ital\">illustrious</i>. <i class=“def-ital\">Illustrious</i> means <i class=“def-ital\">famous, distinguished</i>. </p><p>“You should be INDUSTRIOUS if you ever hope to become <i class=“def-ital\">illustrious</i>.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: INDUSTRY, n.</p>"
            },
            "MANIAC": {
              "word": "MANIAC",
              "phonetic": "(mA'-nE-ak)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a madman, lunatic </p><p>MANIA is a violent form of insanity or madness. A MAN- IAC is a raving madman. </p><p>“That MANIAC is chopping down all the trees in the parks.” </p><p>Often MANIA is used in a weaker sense to mean “extreme enthusiasm,” a <i class=“def-ital\">craze</i>. </p><p>“There was a sudden MANIA for collecting match- book covers.” </p><p>MANIAC is also sometimes used in this weaker sense. </p><p>“He was a MANIAC for playing pinball. You couldn’t drag him away from the machine.</p><p>” Other forms of the word: MANIA, n.</p>"
            },
            "OMIT": {
              "word": "OMIT",
              "phonetic": "(O-mit')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to leave out, leave undone </p><p>To OMIT something is to leave it out, to fail to include it or do it. </p><p>“She OMITTED my name from the list.” </p><p>“I OMITTED doing my homework last night.” </p><p>“Please OMIT the first two pages and start with the third.” </p><p>An OMISSION is an act of leaving out. </p><p>“We were all upset by the OMISSION of his name from the list.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: OMISSION, n.</p>"
            },
            "MYSTIFY": {
              "word": "MYSTIFY",
              "phonetic": "(mis'-t:>-fl)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to puzzle, make mysterious, confuse, baffle </p><p>MYSTIFY is the verb form of MYSTERY. See <i class=“def-ital\">-fy</i> under Suffixes. To MYSTIFY means to <i class=“def-ital\">make mysterious</i>; if you are MYSTIFIED, you are completely puzzled. </p><p>“Does the difference between a prefix and a suffix MYSTIFY you?” </p><p>“The magician MYSTIFIES us with his tricks.” </p><p>“The police were MYSTIFIED by the unusual case. They didn’t know how to go about solving it.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: MYSTERIOUS, adj. </p><p>MYSTERY, n. </p><p>MYSTIFICATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "ORIGINAL": {
              "word": "ORIGINAL",
              "phonetic": "(:>-rij'-:>-nÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">first, earliest, new </p><p>The ORIGIN of something is its starting point, its beginning. </p><p>“What is the ORIGIN of the custom of giving gifts at Christmas?\"</p><p>ORIGINAL means “having to do with a beginning.” See -al under Suffixes. Sometimes ORIGINAL gives the idea of first or earliest. </p><p>“She had the ORIGINAL idea, then everyone else copied her.” </p><p>Sometimes the word gives the idea of new or fresh. </p><p>“There were many ORIGINAL costumes at the party. No one had ever seen anything like them before.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ORIGIN, n.</p><p>ORIGINALITY, n.</p><p>ORIGINATE, v.</p>"
            },
            "PREY": {
              "word": "PREY",
              "phonetic": "(prA)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a victim </p><p>Animals which are or can be killed and eaten by other animals are called PREY. </p><p>“The worm is the usual PREY of the robin.</p><p>” People can also be PREY when they are the victim of a criminal, a disease, or the like. </p><p>“The pickpocket carefully chose his PREY in the crowd.</p><p>” To “fall PREY to” something is to become a victim of it. “Everyone in the family fell PREY to the illness.</p><p>” PREY is also used as a verb. </p><p>“The wolf PREYS upon the herds of sheep.”</p>"
            },
            "REBOUND": {
              "word": "REBOUND",
              "phonetic": "(ri-bownd'",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">rE-bownd’) v.: to bounce back, spring back </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">re-</i> under Prefixes. To <i class=“def-ital\">bound</i> is to bounce or leap. To REBOUND is to bounce back, like a ball when it is thrown against something. </p><p>“The golf ball REBOUNDED from the tree and hit him on the head.</p><p>” REBOUND is also used about someone or something that “bounces back” from a disappointment or setback. </p><p>“The movie industry is starting to REBOUND after several years of losing money.” </p><p>“Stan REBOUNDED from his illness to become more active than ever.</p>"
            },
            "SCAMPER": {
              "word": "SCAMPER",
              "phonetic": "(skam'-pÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to run quickly, scurry, move hastily </p><p>SCAMPER means “to run quickly or playfully,” to <i class=“def-ital\">scurry about</i>. </p><p>“The children SCAMPERED about the lawn as they played tag.” </p><p>“The mice SCAMPERED toward the hole when I turned on the light.” </p><p>The most commonly chosen wrong answer is <i class=“def-ital\">jump up</i>. SCAMPER is used just about running, not jumping.</p>"
            },
            "SNARL": {
              "word": "SNARL",
              "phonetic": "(snahrl)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to growl, bare the teeth, speak harshly </p><p>SNARL means to <i class=“def-ital\">growl</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">bare one’s teeth</i> like a dog. SNARLING indicates anger or hostility. </p><p>“The dog SNARLED at the cat to keep her away from the food.” </p><p>“The watchdog SNARLED in warning, so we went no further.” </p><p>When people SNARL, they don’t usually bare their teeth, but they do speak with a growling sound, to express their anger or irritation. </p><p>“The man SNARLED at the children in his usual un- pleasant manner.” </p><p>SNARL is also a noun. </p><p>“The bad-tempered lady replied to his suggestion with a SNARL.”</p>"
            },
            "OBSTACLE": {
              "word": "OBSTACLE",
              "phonetic": "(ob'-stÔøΩkÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a barrier, hindrance, obstruction </p><p>An OBSTACLE is something that stands in the way of something else, something which stops progress or makes it difficult. </p><p>“They kept putting OBSTACLES in my way as I tried to walk up to the front of the room.” </p><p>An OBSTACLE does not have to be a physical object. </p><p>“Our game with Jefferson High is the only OBSTACLE left between us and the championship.” </p><p>“There are many OBSTACLES facing a person who tries to solve the problem of hunger in the world.”</p>"
            },
            "SWAY": {
              "word": "SWAY",
              "phonetic": "(swA)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to swing, move to and fro; to influence </p><p>SWAY means “to swing back and forth” the way trees do when the wind blows them. </p><p>“The flowers were SWAYING in the gentle breeze.” </p><p>“She was probably dizzy, because she SWAYED when she stood up.” </p><p>SWAY also has the meaning of <i class=“def-ital\">control</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">influence</i>. If you can SWAY something, then you can control its movement. </p><p>“The reporter tried to SWAY public opinion by writing misleading articles about the candidate.” </p><p>“Sam was SWAYED by their appeals, and finally agreed to help them.”</p>"
            },
            "WITHER": {
              "word": "WITHER",
              "phonetic": "(wi'-TH:;,r)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to dry up, waste away </p><p>When something WITHERS it dries up, it becomes stale and lifeless. |n“Without water, the plants WITHERED.” </p><p>“His hope of success WITHERED as he grew older.</p><p>” To WITHER something is to make it dry up or become lifeless. </p><p>“Old age WITHERED her once great beauty.” </p><p>WITHERING is an adjective which means “able to devastate, destroy, or stun.” </p><p>“The WITHERING fire from the machine guns halted the soldiers’ advance.</p><p>” A “WITHERING glance” is a look which is intended to stun a person or make him unable to act. </p><p>“Susan’s WITHERING glance stopped Bob in his tracks.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: WITHERING, adj.</p>"
            },
            "IGNITE": {
              "word": "IGNITE",
              "phonetic": "(ig-nlt')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to set on fire, cause to burn; to catch fire, begin to burn </p><p>To IGNITE something is to set fire to it. </p><p>“The burning cigarette IGNITED the straw.” </p><p>“He IGNITED the blaze with just one match.</p><p>” When something IGNITES, it begins to burn. </p><p>“When we threw on a few matches, the fire IGNITED.” </p><p>IGNITE is also used in a broader sense to mean to <i class=“def-ital\">excite, inflame</i>. </p><p>“Carol’s speech IGNITED the crowd’s enthusiasm.”</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "2",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "SEIZE it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "want",
                    "keep",
                    "grab",
                    "find",
                    "need"
                  ],
                  "word": "SEIZE",
                  "correct": "grab"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GAINFUL employment.",
                  "answers": [
                    "harsh",
                    "profitable",
                    "useless",
                    "possible",
                    "pleasant"
                  ],
                  "word": "GAINFUL",
                  "correct": "profitable"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INDUSTRIOUS men.",
                  "answers": [
                    "lazy",
                    "low-paid",
                    "brilliant",
                    "dirty",
                    "hardworking"
                  ],
                  "word": "INDUSTRIOUS",
                  "correct": "hardworking"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Afraid of the MANIAC.",
                  "answers": [
                    "computer",
                    "murderer",
                    "madman",
                    "disease",
                    "policeman"
                  ],
                  "word": "MANIAC",
                  "correct": "madman"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "OMIT the last section.",
                  "answers": [
                    "leave out",
                    "rewrite",
                    "reduce",
                    "send",
                    "put in"
                  ],
                  "word": "OMIT",
                  "correct": "leave out"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They MYSTIFY me.",
                  "answers": [
                    "show",
                    "chase",
                    "shame",
                    "puzzle",
                    "hurt"
                  ],
                  "word": "MYSTIFY",
                  "correct": "puzzle"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The ORIGINAL inhabitants.",
                  "answers": [
                    "evil",
                    "first",
                    "pure",
                    "early",
                    "newest"
                  ],
                  "word": "ORIGINAL",
                  "correct": "first"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Found his PREY.",
                  "answers": [
                    "victim",
                    "pet",
                    "companion",
                    "weapon",
                    "opponent"
                  ],
                  "word": "PREY",
                  "correct": "victim"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To REBOUND quickly.",
                  "answers": [
                    "fall off",
                    "jump",
                    "spring back",
                    "stop",
                    "tie up"
                  ],
                  "word": "REBOUND",
                  "correct": "spring back"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The children SCAMPER.",
                  "answers": [
                    "hide",
                    "run quickly",
                    "laugh loudly",
                    "sit still",
                    "jump up"
                  ],
                  "word": "SCAMPER",
                  "correct": "run quickly"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Heard him SNARL.",
                  "answers": [
                    "choke",
                    "whine",
                    "laugh",
                    "shout",
                    "growl"
                  ],
                  "word": "SNARL",
                  "correct": "growl"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Certain OBSTACLES.",
                  "answers": [
                    "crimes",
                    "threats",
                    "aids",
                    "barriers",
                    "mistakes"
                  ],
                  "word": "OBSTACLE",
                  "correct": "barriers"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SWAY in the breeze.",
                  "answers": [
                    "stand",
                    "dance",
                    "swing",
                    "fly",
                    "wander"
                  ],
                  "word": "SWAY",
                  "correct": "swing"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It may WITHER.",
                  "answers": [
                    "dry up",
                    "darken",
                    "cave in",
                    "continue",
                    "grow"
                  ],
                  "word": "WITHER",
                  "correct": "dry up"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The log IGNITED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "changed color",
                    "dried out",
                    "fell apart",
                    "caught fire",
                    "became wet"
                  ],
                  "word": "IGNITE",
                  "correct": "caught fire"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it polite to SEIZE something from someone else?",
                  "word": "SEIZE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a paying job a form of GAINFUL employment?",
                  "word": "GAINFUL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do teachers usually like INDUSTRIOUS pupils?",
                  "word": "INDUSTRIOUS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a MANIAC a normal person?",
                  "word": "MANIAC",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually OMIT pages when reading a book?",
                  "word": "OMIT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Should a teacher MYSTIFY his students?",
                  "word": "MYSTIFY",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "If something is ORIGINAL, has it ever been done before?",
                  "word": "ORIGINAL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do tigers hunt PREY?",
                  "word": "PREY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a stone REBOUND when it is dropped into the water?",
                  "word": "REBOUND",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would some adults be able to SCAMPER?",
                  "word": "SCAMPER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a dog's SNARL a sign of anger?",
                  "word": "SNARL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it sometimes possible to get past an OBSTACLE?",
                  "word": "OBSTACLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do dancers sometimes SWAY?",
                  "word": "SWAY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does rain make plants WITHER?",
                  "word": "WITHER",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a match IGNITE a forest fire?",
                  "word": "IGNITE",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "He SEIZED us to agree with him on the subject.",
                  "word": "SEIZE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Al didn't do any GAINFUL work until he was in his early thirties.",
                  "word": "GAINFUL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His first job when he arrived in this country was in an INDUSTRIOUS steel mill.",
                  "word": "INDUSTRIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He drove like a MANIAC; we were all frightened to be in the car with him.",
                  "word": "MANIAC",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We were shocked by the OMISSION of these great athletes from the all-star team.",
                  "word": "OMIT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I am MYSTIFIED by your unusual behavior.",
                  "word": "MYSTIFY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "This was. the most ORIGINAL idea for a party that I've heard in a long time.",
                  "word": "ORIGINAL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "After losing ten games in a row, the team fell PREY to doubts about its ability.",
                  "word": "PREY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The ball REBOUNDED from the wall and came straight back to him.",
                  "word": "REBOUND",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The kitten SCAMPERED around the room chasing the ball of yarn.",
                  "word": "SCAMPER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "When Helen opened the present, she SNARLED with delight.",
                  "word": "SNARL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Lack of a college degree was a major OBSTACLE between Cynthia and success.",
                  "word": "OBSTACLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Jack's opinions were SWAYED by everything he read or heard.",
                  "word": "SWAY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The long illness had WITHERED him: he was only fifty years old but he looked eighty.",
                  "word": "WITHER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We managed to IGNITE the fire by pouring water on it.",
                  "word": "IGNITE",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "SEIZE",
                  "answers": [
                    "want",
                    "steal",
                    "take"
                  ],
                  "word": "SEIZE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GAINFUL",
                  "answers": [
                    "delightful",
                    "profitable",
                    "beneficial"
                  ],
                  "word": "GAINFUL",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INDUSTRIOUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "busy",
                    "active",
                    "strong"
                  ],
                  "word": "INDUSTRIOUS",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MANIAC",
                  "answers": [
                    "madman",
                    "doctor",
                    "criminal"
                  ],
                  "word": "MANIAC",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "OMIT",
                  "answers": [
                    "miss",
                    "skip",
                    "choose"
                  ],
                  "word": "OMIT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MYSTIFY",
                  "answers": [
                    "confuse",
                    "puzzle",
                    "insult"
                  ],
                  "word": "MYSTIFY",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ORIGINAL",
                  "answers": [
                    "nice",
                    "fresh",
                    "new"
                  ],
                  "word": "ORIGINAL",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PREY",
                  "answers": [
                    "victim",
                    "food",
                    "play"
                  ],
                  "word": "PREY",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "REBOUND",
                  "answers": [
                    "stop",
                    "bounce",
                    "return"
                  ],
                  "word": "REBOUND",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SCAMPER",
                  "answers": [
                    "limp",
                    "chase",
                    "run"
                  ],
                  "word": "SCAMPER",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SNARL",
                  "answers": [
                    "choke",
                    "snap",
                    "growl"
                  ],
                  "word": "SNARL",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "OBSTACLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "ruin",
                    "bother",
                    "obstruction"
                  ],
                  "word": "OBSTACLE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SWAY",
                  "answers": [
                    "influence",
                    "fall",
                    "swing"
                  ],
                  "word": "SWAY",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "WITHER",
                  "answers": [
                    "divide",
                    "shrink",
                    "crumble"
                  ],
                  "word": "WITHER",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "IGNITE",
                  "answers": [
                    "drive",
                    "burn",
                    "excite"
                  ],
                  "word": "IGNITE",
                  "correct": "0"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.3",
          "definitions": {
            "COMMOTION": {
              "word": "COMMOTION",
              "phonetic": "(kÔøΩmO'-shÔøΩn)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a disturbance; confusion, noise, excitement </p><p>A COMMOTION is a disturbance. You can see the word</i> motion</i> in COMMOTION. COMMOTION usually suggests a great deal of movement and, often, noise and excitement. </p><p>“I don’t know how you could sleep through all that COMMOTION.” </p><p>“The sudden appearance of the long-lost son during the reading of the will caused quite a COMMOTION.” </p><p>“The rubbish collectors made an awful COMMOTION as they banged the barrels around.” </p><p>“Despite the COMMOTION we were still able to carry on a conversation.”</p>"
            },
            "AIL": {
              "word": "AIL",
              "phonetic": "(Al)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to trouble, be the matter with; to have some- thing the matter, be ill </p><p>When something AILS a person it troubles him, it causes him pain or discomfort. The word is used when we don’t know exactly what the matter is. </p><p>“He went to the doctor to find out what was AILING him.” </p><p>“Nothing AILED her that a long vacation couldn’t cure.” </p><p>When a person is AILING, something is the matter with him. </p><p>“She was always AILING. Ever day she had some kind of ache or pain.” </p><p>An AILMENT is an illness or a disorder. </p><p>“Bob had several AILMENTS, but none of them was serious enough for him to go into the hospital.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: AILMENT, n.</p>"
            },
            "BATTER": {
              "word": "BATTER",
              "phonetic": "(bat'-ÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to beat, hit repeatedly/n BATTER means “to hit over and over again,” <i class=“def-ital\">to beat</i>. If a thing is BATTERED, it is usually beaten out of shape. If a person is BATTERED, he is usually deeply bruised or injured. </p><p>“During the storm, heavy waves BATTERED the houses on the shore and many were destroyed.” </p><p>“We used a heavy piece of wood to BATTER down the door.” </p><p>“The fighter was badly BATTERED during the boxing match.”</p>"
            },
            "COMMAND": {
              "word": "COMMAND",
              "phonetic": "(kÔøΩmand')",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an order </p><p>A COMMAND is an <i class=“def-ital\">order</i>. </p><p>“The leader gave the COMMAND to begin marching.” </p><p>“He put his COMMANDS in writing so there would be no question about what they were supposed to do.” </p><p>“They refused to obey the foolish COMMAND to step over the edge of the cliff.</p><p>” COMMAND is also a verb. </p><p>“She COMMANDED them to leave the house or she would call the police.” </p><p>“The king COMMANDED the council to meet and approve his decisions.” <i class=“def-ital\">Request</i> is the most popular wrong answer in the Pretest. When you make a <i class=“def-ital\">request</i> you ask a person to do something. When you give a COMMAND you order him to do something.</p>"
            },
            "DANGLE": {
              "word": "DANGLE",
              "phonetic": "(dang'-gÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to swing, hang loosely </p><p>When something DANGLES it hangs loosely, so that it can swing back and forth. </p><p>“The wind chimes on the tree limb DANGLED in the breeze.” </p><p>“The baby tried to grab his mother’s necklace which was DANGLING in front of him.” </p><p>To DANGLE something is to swing it loosely. “He DANGLED the watch in front of our eyes.” </p><p>You can also DANGLE things like promises or jobs. </p><p>“Visions of great wealth were DANGLED before him in order to interest him in investing in their project.” </p><p>“The manager DANGLED the prospect of a better job for her within six months or so.”</p>"
            },
            "DECEIVE": {
              "word": "DECEIVE",
              "phonetic": "(di-sEv')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to trick, mislead </p><p> To DECEIVE someone is to make him believe something that is false. </p><p>“Ellen DECEIVED me by making me think she really liked me.” </p><p>“Jane was DECEIVED into believing that the money would be used to feed the poor.” </p><p>“Don’t DECEIVE yourself. You can’t really climb that mountain.” </p><p>DECEIT is <i class=“def-ital\">trickery</i>, the quality or act of DECEIVNG. </p><p>“She accused Don of DECEIT in hiding the truth from her.” </p><p>“There was an element of DECEIT in the way the commercial presented the facts.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: DECEIT, n. </p><p>DECEITFUL, adj.</p>"
            },
            "ASTOUND": {
              "word": "ASTOUND",
              "phonetic": "(ÔøΩstownd')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to amaze, overcome with surprise </p><p>To ASTOUND means to <i class=“def-ital\">amaze</i>, to <i class=“def-ital\">astonish</i>. Someone who is ASTOUNDED is much more than surprised; he is so astonished that he can barely think. </p><p>“The news of his victory ASTOUNDED all of us.” “She was ASTOUNDED to discover that one of her ancestors had been a duchess.” </p><p>“He was ASTOUNDED when he found out he had won the lottery.” </p><p>Other forms: ASTOUNDING, adj.</p>"
            },
            "DISPUTE": {
              "word": "DISPUTE",
              "phonetic": "(dis-pyUt')",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an argument, quarrel, verbal conflict  /nA DISPUTE is an argument or quarrel. </p><p>“There was a long DISPUTE among them about who was the best.” </p><p>“Several minor DISPUTES between the countries finally led to full-scale war.” </p><p>“There can be no DISPUTE about it. We have to leave now.” </p><p>DISPUTE is also a verb. It can mean to <i class=“def-ital\">argue</i>. </p><p>“He DISPUTED with the other boys over how much to spend.” </p><p>Or it can mean “to call into question,” to <i class=“def-ital\">argue against</i>. </p><p>“The players all DISPUTED the referee’s call.” </p><p>“Jim DISPUTED everything his brother had said.”</p>"
            },
            "EAVESDROP": {
              "word": "EAVESDROP",
              "phonetic": "(Evz'-drop)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to listen secretly to a private conversation </p><p>An eave is the part of the roof which overhangs the side of a building. The <i class=“def-ital\">eavesdrop</i> is the water which falls from an eave, or the ground under the eave on which the water falls. To EAVESDROP originally meant to stand on this eavesdrop in order to listen to a conversation inside the building. From this the word has come to mean any kind of attempt to listen secretly to what people are saying in private. The word emphasizes sneakiness and secrecy. To EAVESDROP on someone else’s conversation is not a polite thing to do. An EAVESDROPPER is a person who listens secretly to conversation he is not supposed to hear. </p><p>“She stood outside the kitchen door to EAVESDROP on her parents’ conversation.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: EAVESDROPPER, n.</p>"
            },
            "EMBLEM": {
              "word": "EMBLEM",
              "phonetic": "(em'-blÔøΩm)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a symbol, sign, image </p><p>An EMBLEM is a picture, design, or figure that stands for something else. It could represent an idea, a school, a company, or the like. </p><p>“Our school’s EMBLEM is a screaming eagle.” </p><p>“The dove is an EMBLEM of peace. Many people pick <i class=“def-ital\">motto</i> as the meaning of EMBLEM. A <i class=“def-ital\">motto</i> is a short phrase that is associated with a country or a group of people; an EMBLEM doesn’t use words. </p><p>“Our motto is ‘Ever to excel.’ Our EMBLEM is a tiger cat ready to jump.\"</p><p> Other forms of the word: EMBLEMATIC, adj.</p>"
            },
            "CLOAK": {
              "word": "CLOAK",
              "phonetic": "(klOk)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a cape </p><p>A CLOAK is a long cape or sleeveless robe. </p><p>“She likes to wear her red CLOAK with the fur trim.” </p><p>“He held the dog under his CLOAK to keep it warm.” </p><p>CLOAK is also a verb meaning to <i class=“def-ital\">cover</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">hide</i>. </p><p>“He CLOAKED his hatred under a mask of smiles.” </p><p>“The house was CLOAKED in darkness; we couldn’t see it until we were almost there.” </p><p>“The mountain top is always CLOAKED in mist.” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Dress</i> is the most commonly chosen incorrect answer. Both a <i class=“def-ital\">dress</i> and a CLOAK are articles of clothing, but they are not the same thing.</p>"
            },
            "ESTIMATE": {
              "word": "ESTIMATE",
              "phonetic": "(es'-tÔøΩmAt)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to judge, rate, evaluate </p><p>To ESTIMATE is to make a judgment about something without having complete information. </p><p>“The teacher ESTIMATED that half of her students would pass the test.” </p><p>“We tried to ESTIMATE how long it would take us to finish the job.” </p><p>“No one could ESTIMATE the height of the mountain.” </p><p>An ESTIMATE is this kind of a judgment. As a noun, the word is pronounced es’-t:rmit. </p><p>“He didn’t know exactly how many people were coming to the party. He had to make an ESTIMATE.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ESTIMATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "FRAGMENT": {
              "word": "FRAGMENT",
              "phonetic": "(frag'-m:)nt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a part, piece A FRAGMENT is a separate or incomplete part of something, especially a part that is broken off. “We recovered several FRAGMENTS of the broken glass, but some are still missing.” </p><p>“He could only remember FRAGMENTS of the song; he had forgotten most of it.” </p><p>“They overheard FRAGMENTS of the conversation going on in the next room.“nFRAGMENTARY is an adjective which means “made up of FRAGMENTS,” <i class=“def-ital\">incomplete</i>. </p><p>“We have received only FRAGMENTARY reports of what happened there.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: FRAGMENTARY, adj.</p>"
            },
            "HYMN": {
              "word": "HYMN",
              "phonetic": "(Him)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a song of praise, usually to God </p><p>A HYMN is a song praising God. It is usually sung in a church service of some kind. </p><p>“They sang his favorite HYMN in church that Sunday.” </p><p>HYMN is also sometimes used for any song of praise. </p><p>“He wrote a solemn HYMN in honor of his nation’s independence.”</p>"
            },
            "DONATION": {
              "word": "DONATION",
              "phonetic": "(dO-nA'-sh:)n)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a gift, present, contribution  </p><p>A DONATION is a gift or contribution, usually given to a charity of some kind. </p><p>“Every year we give a DONATION to the Heart Fund.” “After the disaster, the people whose homes had been destroyed needed DONATIONS of food and clothing.” </p><p>“He asked everyone for a small DONATION to buy a going-away present for George.” </p><p>When you make a DONATION, you DONATE. </p><p>“She refused to DONATE anything to the party.” </p><p>“We will accept whatever you choose to DONATE.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: DONATE, v.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "3",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Another COMMOTION.",
                  "answers": [
                    "vacation",
                    "problem",
                    "disturbance",
                    "mixture",
                    "meeting"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMMOTION",
                  "correct": "disturbance"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "What AILS you?",
                  "answers": [
                    "stops",
                    "frightens",
                    "cures",
                    "convinces",
                    "troubles"
                  ],
                  "word": "AIL",
                  "correct": "troubles"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Started to BATTER it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "beat",
                    "hate",
                    "shut",
                    "praise",
                    "build"
                  ],
                  "word": "BATTER",
                  "correct": "beat"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His first COMMAND.",
                  "answers": [
                    "question",
                    "warning",
                    "order",
                    "idea",
                    "request"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMMAND",
                  "correct": "order"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He DANGLED the keys.",
                  "answers": [
                    "lost",
                    "dropped",
                    "hid",
                    "swung",
                    "mixed up"
                  ],
                  "word": "DANGLE",
                  "correct": "swung"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To DECEIVE us.",
                  "answers": [
                    "rob",
                    "trick",
                    "laugh at",
                    "warn",
                    "fire"
                  ],
                  "word": "DECEIVE",
                  "correct": "trick"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ASTOUNDED by the news.",
                  "answers": [
                    "excited",
                    "fooled",
                    "driven",
                    "annoyed",
                    "amazed"
                  ],
                  "word": "ASTOUND",
                  "correct": "amazed"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Another DISPUTE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "threat",
                    "agreement",
                    "injustice",
                    "criticism",
                    "argument"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISPUTE",
                  "correct": "argument"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Tried to EAVESDROP.",
                  "answers": [
                    "run away",
                    "listen secretly",
                    "sneak in",
                    "understand",
                    "speak clearly"
                  ],
                  "word": "EAVESDROP",
                  "correct": "listen secretly"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "A new EMBLEM.",
                  "answers": [
                    "map",
                    "motto",
                    "song",
                    "symbol",
                    "mistake"
                  ],
                  "word": "EMBLEM",
                  "correct": "symbol"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Her CLOAK.",
                  "answers": [
                    "dress",
                    "watch",
                    "cape",
                    "shoes",
                    "hood"
                  ],
                  "word": "CLOAK",
                  "correct": "cape"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Had to ESTIMATE it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "share",
                    "forget",
                    "praise",
                    "judge",
                    "sell"
                  ],
                  "word": "ESTIMATE",
                  "correct": "judge"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Another FRAGMENT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "part",
                    "glass",
                    "book",
                    "idea",
                    "problem"
                  ],
                  "word": "FRAGMENT",
                  "correct": "part"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Wrote the HYMN.",
                  "answers": [
                    "organ music",
                    "prayer",
                    "drinking song",
                    "holy song",
                    "poem"
                  ],
                  "word": "HYMN",
                  "correct": "holy song"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Many small DONATIONS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "regions",
                    "services",
                    "gifts",
                    "checks",
                    "requests"
                  ],
                  "word": "DONATION",
                  "correct": "gifts"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a dogfight be a COMMOTION?",
                  "word": "COMMOTION",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people with a lot of AILMENTS feel good?",
                  "word": "AIL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a car be BATTERED?",
                  "word": "BATIER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do children usually give COMMANDS to their parents?",
                  "word": "COMMAND",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do mountains DANGLE?",
                  "word": "DANGLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can the appearance of something DECEIVE people?",
                  "word": "DECEIVE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a person be ASTOUNDED if the sun rose in the morning?",
                  "word": "ASTOUND",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a DISPUTE lead to a fistfight?",
                  "word": "DISPUTE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does an EAVESDROPPER try to avoid being noticed?",
                  "word": "EAVESDROP",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is \"In God We Trust\" the EMBLEM of the United States?",
                  "word": "EMBLEM",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a CLOAK cover a person's shoulders?",
                  "word": "CLOAK",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can you ESTIMATE the price of something without knowing everything",
                  "word": "ESTIMATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "about it?",
                  "word": "FRAGMENT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are light bulbs sold in FRAGMENTS?",
                  "word": "HYMN",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a HYMN usually be sung in church?",
                  "word": "DONATION",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "If you earn money, does your boss DONATE your pay to you?"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Tom COMMOTIONED to us to join him.",
                  "word": "COMMOTION",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I don't know what's AILING Bill; he's been moping around the house for over a week.",
                  "word": "AIL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The boxer BATTERED his opponent until the fight had to be stopped.",
                  "word": "BATIER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The policeman COMMANDED the driver to show his license.",
                  "word": "COMMAND",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The boss DANGLED the prospect of a big raise in front of Jim to get him to stay with the company.",
                  "word": "DANGLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I don't DECEIVE that you are coming at all.",
                  "word": "DECEIVE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Bill was ASTOUNDED when he found the treasure buried in his backyard.",
                  "word": "ASTOUND",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Dick didn't care which side of the DISPUTE he was on; he just loved to argue.",
                  "word": "DISPUTE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They were talking so loud there was no need to EAVESDROP on their conversation.",
                  "word": "EAVESDROP",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "A maple leaf is Canada's EMBLEM: it appears on many of their coins.",
                  "word": "EMBLEM",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The houses along the beach were CLOAKED in a thick fog.",
                  "word": "CLOAK",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His ESTIMATE of the number of marbles in the jar proved to be correct.",
                  "word": "ESTIMATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Nick's FRAGMENTARY knowledge of Spanish enabled him to speak it perfectly.",
                  "word": "FRAGMENT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He sang a beautiful HYMN which inspired them all.",
                  "word": "HYMN",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He asked us for a large DONATION to his favorite charity.",
                  "word": "DONATION",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "COMMOTION",
                  "answers": [
                    "noise",
                    "confusion",
                    "danger"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMMOTION",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "AIL",
                  "answers": [
                    "be ill",
                    "hurt",
                    "fear"
                  ],
                  "word": "AIL",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "BATTER",
                  "answers": [
                    "beat",
                    "dent",
                    "stop"
                  ],
                  "word": "BATIER",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "COMMAND",
                  "answers": [
                    "demand",
                    "order",
                    "ask"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMMAND",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DANGLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "drop",
                    "swing",
                    "hang"
                  ],
                  "word": "DANGLE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DECEIVE",
                  "answers": [
                    "fool",
                    "amuse",
                    "cheat"
                  ],
                  "word": "DECEIVE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ASTOUND",
                  "answers": [
                    "surprise",
                    "worry",
                    "astonish"
                  ],
                  "word": "ASTOUND",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISPUTE",
                  "answers": [
                    "decide",
                    "quarrel",
                    "oppose"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISPUTE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EAVESDROP",
                  "answers": [
                    "attack",
                    "listen",
                    "spy"
                  ],
                  "word": "EAVESDROP",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EMBLEM",
                  "answers": [
                    "design",
                    "picture",
                    "school"
                  ],
                  "word": "EMBLEM",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CLOAK",
                  "answers": [
                    "gown",
                    "cape",
                    "robe"
                  ],
                  "word": "CLOAK",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ESTIMATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "know",
                    "guess",
                    "judge"
                  ],
                  "word": "ESTIMATE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FRAGMENT",
                  "answers": [
                    "hole",
                    "section",
                    "piece"
                  ],
                  "word": "FRAGMENT",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HYMN",
                  "answers": [
                    "church",
                    "band",
                    "song"
                  ],
                  "word": "HYMN",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DONATION",
                  "answers": [
                    "gift",
                    "present",
                    "debt"
                  ],
                  "word": "DONATION",
                  "correct": "2"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ],
      "reviewTest": {
        "wordList": [
          {
            "word": "ACCURATE",
            "answer": "accurate"
          },
          {
            "word": "DANGLE",
            "answer": "dangled"
          },
          {
            "word": "ESTIMATE",
            "answer": "estimate"
          },
          {
            "word": "PEER",
            "answer": "peered"
          },
          {
            "word": "SEIZE",
            "answer": "seized"
          },
          {
            "word": "ASTOUND",
            "answer": "astounded"
          },
          {
            "word": "DISPUTE",
            "answer": "disputes"
          },
          {
            "word": "FRAGMENT",
            "answer": "fragments"
          },
          {
            "word": "PREY",
            "answer": "prey"
          },
          {
            "word": "SWAY",
            "answer": "sway"
          },
          {
            "word": "COMMAND",
            "answer": "command"
          },
          {
            "word": "DROUGHT",
            "answer": "drought"
          },
          {
            "word": "MYSTIFY",
            "answer": "mystify"
          },
          {
            "word": "PULVERIZE",
            "answer": "pulverized"
          },
          {
            "word": "THRESHOLD",
            "answer": "threshold"
          },
          {
            "word": "COMMOTION",
            "answer": "command"
          },
          {
            "word": "EMBLEM",
            "answer": "emblem"
          },
          {
            "word": "ORIGINAL",
            "answer": "original"
          },
          {
            "word": "SCAMPER",
            "answer": "scamper"
          },
          {
            "word": "TRANSFORM",
            "answer": "transformed"
          },
          {
            "word": "CONCLUDE",
            "answer": "concluded"
          },
          {
            "word": "AIL",
            "answer": "ailing"
          },
          {
            "word": "DECEIVE",
            "answer": "deceive"
          },
          {
            "word": "HYMN",
            "answer": "hymn"
          },
          {
            "word": "OMIT",
            "answer": "omit"
          },
          {
            "word": "SNARL",
            "answer": "snarl"
          },
          {
            "word": "ASSIST",
            "answer": "assist"
          },
          {
            "word": "DONATION",
            "answer": "donations"
          },
          {
            "word": "IGNITE",
            "answer": "ignited"
          },
          {
            "word": "PRIVILEGE",
            "answer": "privilege"
          },
          {
            "word": "TASK",
            "answer": "task"
          },
          {
            "word": "AVALANCHE",
            "answer": "avalanche"
          },
          {
            "word": "EAVESDROP",
            "answer": "eavesdrop"
          },
          {
            "word": "INDUSTRIOUS",
            "answer": "industrious"
          },
          {
            "word": "REBOUND",
            "answer": "rebounded"
          },
          {
            "word": "TUTOR",
            "answer": "tutor"
          },
          {
            "word": "BATTER",
            "answer": "battered"
          },
          {
            "word": "EDIBLE",
            "answer": "edible"
          },
          {
            "word": "MANIAC",
            "answer": "maniac"
          },
          {
            "word": "REPLY",
            "answer": "reply"
          },
          {
            "word": "WITHER",
            "answer": "wither"
          },
          {
            "word": "CLOAK",
            "answer": "cloak"
          },
          {
            "word": "GAINFUL",
            "answer": "gainful"
          },
          {
            "word": "OBSTACLE",
            "answer": "obstacles"
          },
          {
            "word": "SIGNIFY",
            "answer": "signify"
          }
        ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "part1": "The announcement that there would be no school next week caused quite a(n)",
            "part2": "among the students.",
            "correct": "commotion",
            "word": "COMMOTION"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Jim",
            "part2": "the opportunity to ask the teacher several important questions.",
            "correct": "seized",
            "word": "SEIZE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The cat hunted down its",
            "part2": "a bird looking for worms on the wet ground.",
            "correct": "prey",
            "word": "PREY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The desert is in a state of permanent",
            "part2": "; it hasn't rained there for centuries.",
            "correct": "drought",
            "word": "DROUGHT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "With irrigation, they",
            "part2": "the dry area into productive farmland.",
            "correct": "transformed",
            "word": "TRANSFORM"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Art gave",
            "part2": "responses to every question on the test and got an A.",
            "correct": "accurate",
            "word": "ACCURATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "She was on the",
            "part2": "of becoming a great artist when she went blind.",
            "correct": "threshold",
            "word": "THRESHOLD"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The palm tree started to",
            "part2": "in the gentle breeze.",
            "correct": "sway",
            "word": "SWAY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The",
            "part2": "problem was bad enough, but all the problems we've had since then have been even worse.",
            "correct": "original",
            "word": "ORIGINAL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "His strange theories",
            "part2": "us. We can't understand them at all.",
            "correct": "mystify",
            "word": "MYSTIFY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The teacher yelled at them to stop, but they paid no attention to her",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "command",
            "word": "COMMOTION"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The news of their defeat",
            "part2": "me. I never thought they could lose.",
            "correct": "astounded",
            "word": "ASTOUND"
          },
          {
            "part1": "A glittering diamond",
            "part2": "on the end of the chain.",
            "correct": "dangled",
            "word": "DANGLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We like to knock the icicles off the roof with a stick and watch them shatter into",
            "part2": "on the ground below.",
            "correct": "fragments",
            "word": "FRAGMENT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They",
            "part2": "through the smoke at the burning building.",
            "correct": "peered",
            "word": "PEER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The tank ran over the wooden box and completely",
            "part2": "it.",
            "correct": "pulverized",
            "word": "PULVERIZE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "From the way she kept looking at her watch I",
            "part2": "that she thought it was time to go.",
            "correct": "concluded",
            "word": "CONCLUDE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "She is a very disagreeable woman, always involved in bitter",
            "part2": "with her neighbors.",
            "correct": "disputes",
            "word": "DISPUTE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The children",
            "part2": "quickly after the man selling ice cream cones.",
            "correct": "scamper",
            "word": "SCAMPER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The motto of the United States is \"In God We Trust.\" The country's",
            "part2": "is the bald eagle.",
            "correct": "emblem",
            "word": "EMBLEM"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We had no idea how much the necklace was worth, so we took it to a jeweler and had him",
            "part2": "its value. ",
            "correct": "estimate",
            "word": "ESTIMATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Many small",
            "part2": "to our fund are as important as one large gift.",
            "correct": "donations",
            "word": "DONATION"
          },
          {
            "part1": "She waved to them to",
            "part2": "that she was all right.",
            "correct": "signify",
            "word": "SIGNIFY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "No one would",
            "part2": "us, so we had to do the job all by ourselves.",
            "correct": "assist",
            "word": "ASSIST"
          },
          {
            "part1": "When I ask you something, I would like a(n)",
            "part2": ", even if you just nod your head.",
            "correct": "reply",
            "word": "REPLY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The leaves on the plant began to",
            "part2": "after several weeks without water.",
            "correct": "wither",
            "word": "WITHER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We were frightened by the announcement that a dangerous",
            "part2": "had escaped from the mental hospital.",
            "correct": "maniac",
            "word": "MANIAC"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Most teenagers have difficulty in finding",
            "part2": "employment, so they can't make any money.",
            "correct": "gainful",
            "word": "GAINFUL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We heard the wolves",
            "part2": "as they fought over the dead lamb.",
            "correct": "snarl",
            "word": "SNARL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "All the people in the church stood up to sing the",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "hymn",
            "word": "HYMN"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The branches of the tree",
            "part2": "the sides of our house in the high winds.",
            "correct": "battered",
            "word": "BATTER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "She wore a long",
            "part2": "that kept her warm but left her arms free to move.",
            "correct": "cloak",
            "word": "CLOAK"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Although Gail was",
            "part2": "about doing her English lessons, she couldn't seem to bring her grade up to anything more than a B.",
            "correct": "industrious",
            "word": "INDUSTRIOUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The intense heat",
            "part2": "the cans of paint.",
            "correct": "ignited",
            "word": "IGNITE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "You must be sure to answer all the questions. Do not",
            "part2": "any.",
            "correct": "omit",
            "word": "OMIT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Betty",
            "part2": "quickly from the disappointment of not winning the contest and was soon her usual happy self again.",
            "correct": "rebounded",
            "word": "REBOUND"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Ed has been",
            "part2": "for months, but he refuses to go to the doctor to find out what's wrong.",
            "correct": "ailing",
            "word": "AIL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We wouldn't",
            "part2": "you. We're telling you the truth about this.",
            "correct": "deceive",
            "word": "DECEIVE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The",
            "part2": "of mowing that huge lawn was too much for Ed, so he had to get someone to help.",
            "correct": "task",
            "word": "TASK"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The skiers just missed being caught in the",
            "part2": "that came crashing down the side of the mountain.",
            "correct": "avalanche",
            "word": "AVALANCHE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Alice is doing fine in most of her classes but she needs someone to",
            "part2": "her in French.",
            "correct": "tutor",
            "word": "TUTOR"
          },
          {
            "part1": "He tried to",
            "part2": "on their conversation by placing a microphone under the table.",
            "correct": "eavesdrop",
            "word": "EAVESDROP"
          },
          {
            "part1": "In order to survive in the wilderness it is necessary to know which plants are",
            "part2": "and which are poisonous.",
            "correct": "edible",
            "word": "EDIBLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It was a",
            "part2": "to speak with the great man for a few moments.",
            "correct": "privilege",
            "word": "PRIVILEGE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "There were trash cans, broken tables, and other",
            "part2": "in our way as we tried to walk through the basement.",
            "correct": "obstacles",
            "word": "OBSTACLE"
          }
        ],
        "type": "fitb"
      }
    },
    {
      "wordsets": [
        {
          "title": "2.4",
          "definitions": {
            "STAMPEDE": {
              "word": "STAMPEDE",
              "phonetic": "(stam-pEd')",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a wild rush, sudden charge A STAMPEDE is a sudden, wild rush, usually of animals that have become frightened and run blindly. In a STAM- PEDE the animals are out of control; they are so crazy with fear they will trample anything in their way. “The cattle STAMPEDE destroyed the field of new corn.” “Don’t shoot your rifle now. The noise will cause a STAMPEDE.” STAMPEDE can also be used in a general sense about any wild rush. “The announcement of the big sale almost caused a STAMPEDE of shoppers to the store.” STAMPEDE is also a verb, which means to rush wildly or overrun. “The starving people STAMPEDED the supply wagons.</p>"
            },
            "PROCLAIM": {
              "word": "PROCLAIM",
              "phonetic": "(prO-klAm')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to declare openly, announce To PROCLAIM something is to announce it openly and publicly. “After he won the fight the boxer was PROCLAIMED champion of the world.” “When his father died the noblemen PROCLAIMED him king.” Often PROCLAIM has an official sense to it. “The governor PROCLAIMED next Monday a state holiday.” A PROCLAMATION is an official announcement. “Lincoln issued a PROCLAMATION that ended slavery in America.” Other forms of the word: PROCLAMATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "INCIDENT": {
              "word": "INCIDENT",
              "phonetic": "(in'-sÔøΩdent",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">in’-sÔøΩdant) n.: an event, occurrence, happening An INCIDENT is simply something that happens, an event. Usually an INCIDENT is small or unimportant. “It was just one of those unpleasant INCIDENTS that happen every day.” Often, though, the word is used about a seemingly minor event which could lead to serious consequences. “The arrest of the novelist became a serious interna- tional INCIDENT.” “There were so many violent INCIDENTS at the bor- der that both countries threatened to declare war.”</p>"
            },
            "MINDFUL": {
              "word": "MINDFUL",
              "phonetic": "(mlnd'-fal)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">aware, careful, attentive MINDFUL is made up of two parts: mind and ful. See -ful under Suffixes. If your mind is full of something, you are very aware of it. MINDFUL means “keeping in mind,” aware. “He was MINDFUL of the orders he had been given.” “You should be MINDFUL of the danger.” “You must be MINDFUL that some of these animals could hurt you.” Usage: MINDFUL is usually followed by of.</p>"
            },
            "PREVIOUS": {
              "word": "PREVIOUS",
              "phonetic": "(prE'-vE-as)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">former, earlier, prior PREVIOUS means “happening before” something else, former. See pre- under Prefixes. “All the PREVIOUS reports were wrong. Only the one we are putting out now is correct.” “We did well that season, but we did even better in the PREVIOUS season.” “After working there for a while he went back to his PREVIOUS job as a salesman.” PREVIOUS is often used with to to mean before. “PREVIOUS to the speech there was a wonderful din- ner.”</p>"
            },
            "QUARANTINE": {
              "word": "QUARANTINE",
              "phonetic": "(kwor'-ÔøΩn-tEn)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to isolate or separate from others to prevent the spread of a disease QUARANTINE is both a verb and a noun. To QUARANTINE a person is to keep him apart from others while he has a disease, or while he is suspected of having a disease, to make sure that the disease doesn’t spread. QUARAN- TINE comes from the Latin word for forty, because originally a person had to be kept isolated for a period of forty days. “You can take your dog to England, but it will have to be kept in QUARANTINE for six months.” “The entire ship was QUARANTINED when one of the passengers came down with smallpox.”</p>"
            },
            "RECREATION": {
              "word": "RECREATION",
              "phonetic": "(rek-rE-A'-shan)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">play, amusement RECREATION is something that refreshes you by pro- viding you with amusement or entertainment. “Walking is a pleasant RECREATION.” “His favorite RECREATION is watching television.” “She works too hard. She hardly has any time for RECREATION.” The adjective from RECREATION is RECREATIONAL. RECREATIONAL activities are things like games, sports, or hobbies which provide RECREATION. Other forms of the word: RECREATIONAL, adj.</p>"
            },
            "SEGMENT": {
              "word": "SEGMENT",
              "phonetic": "(seg'-mant)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a part, section, division A SEGMENT is a section, a piece of a larger whole. “One SEGMENT of the magazine is made up of business reports.” “Mr. Sweeney is the counselor for a large SEGMENT of the junior class.” “Mrs. Ames gave each of the children a SEGMENT of the orange.”</p>"
            },
            "SUBMERGE": {
              "word": "SUBMERGE",
              "phonetic": "(sab-merj')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to place underwater; to go under water, sink - See sub- under Prefixes. To SUBMERGE something is to plunge it into water. “The blacksmith quickly SUBMERGED the glowing horseshoe in a bucket of water.” When something SUBMERGES, it goes underwater. “The submarine SUBMERGED and quickly disappeared from sight.” “The treasure lay SUBMERGED in ten feet of water.”</p>"
            },
            "TURQUOISE": {
              "word": "TURQUOISE",
              "phonetic": "(ter'-kwoyz",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">ter’-koyz) adj.: blue- green TURQUOISE, when used as a noun, is a stone that is often blue-green in color. TURQUOISE, as an adjective, is used about anything with this blue-green color. “Her eyes are almost TURQUOISE in color.” “My TURQUOISE dress is the color of sea at mid- day.”</p>"
            },
            "UTMOST": {
              "word": "UTMOST",
              "phonetic": "(uht'-mOst)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">greatest, most extreme UTMOST means “of the highest degree possible\"-that is, the furthest, the most, the greatest, and so on. “This job requires the UTMOST skill and intelli- gence.” “This meeting will take place in the UTMOST secrecy.” UTMOST is also a noun, meaning “the most that is possible or that one can do.” “He enjoyed life to the UTMOST\"-that is, to the greatest degree possible. “This hotel will give you the UTMOST in comfort and service.” “We will do our UTMOST to finish the job on Saturday.”</p>"
            },
            "VICTOR": {
              "word": "VICTOR",
              "phonetic": "(vik'-tar)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a winner, conqueror A VICTOR is a person who defeats another in battle or any other kind of contest. “This year the VICTOR in the weight-lifting contest was a Russian.” “Harry Smith will be our mayor next year because he was the VICTOR in last week’s election.” A VICTOR wins a VICTORY; he is VICTORIOUS. “After his famous VICTORY, the VICTORIOUS general received all the glory due a VICTOR.” Other forms of the word: VICTORY, n. VICTORIOUS, adj.</p>"
            },
            "DWELL": {
              "word": "DWELL",
              "phonetic": "(dwel)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to live, reside; to speak, write, or think at length To DWELL in or at a place is to make your home there. “She DWELT all her life in the house where she was born.” “Many interesting people DWELL in that section of town.” In another sense, to DWELL on or upon something is to speak, write, or think about it at length. “I hate to DWELL on this, but you still owe me five dollars.” “In the first few chapters the author DWELLS on the problems of the early settlers.” Other forms of the word: DWELLING, n. Usage: The past tense of DWELL is DWELT or DWELLED.</p>"
            },
            "QUESTIONABLE": {
              "word": "QUESTIONABLE",
              "phonetic": "(kwes'-chÔøΩn-ÔøΩbÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">doubtful, uncertain See -able under Suffixes. Something which is QUES- TIONABLE is able to be QUESTIONED, is open to QUESTION. “The referee made a QUESTIONABLE call\"-that is, we are not certain that it was wrong, but we don’t think it was right. “It was QUESTIONABLE whether or not we would make it to school on time.” “He thought our results were QUESTIONABLE, so we checked them and discovered we had made a mistake.” Certain is the most commonly chosen incorrect answer on the Pretest. It is the exact opposite of QUESTIONABLE. Perhaps people who choose certain are confusing QUES- TIONABLE with unquestionable, which means “not open to QUESTION,” certain. Other forms of the word: QUESTION, n., v.</p>"
            },
            "ROUSE": {
              "word": "ROUSE",
              "phonetic": "(rowz)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to awaken, stir, excite To ROUSE someone is to stir or awaken him. “The fire alarm ROUSED them from their sleep.” You can ROUSE someone to something as well as from something. “The speaker’s words ROUSED the crowd to action.” “I was ROUSED to anger by his insults.” ROUSE is often used with up. “They ROUSED up their friends and made them help too.” ROUSING is an adjective which means exciting or stir- ring. “We gave a ROUSING cheer when the team came on the field.” Other forms of the word: ROUSING, adj.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "4",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Join the STAMPEDE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "meeting",
                    "crowd",
                    "wild rush",
                    "defense line",
                    "cattle"
                  ],
                  "word": "STAMPEDE",
                  "correct": "wild rush"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To PROCLAIM it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "invent",
                    "declare",
                    "want",
                    "oppose",
                    "celebrate"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROCLAIM",
                  "correct": "declare"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Unusual INCIDENT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "crime",
                    "problem",
                    "idea",
                    "complaint",
                    "event"
                  ],
                  "word": "INCIDENT",
                  "correct": "event"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MINDFUL of his duties.",
                  "answers": [
                    "aware",
                    "fond",
                    "afraid",
                    "forgetful",
                    "ashamed"
                  ],
                  "word": "MINDFUL",
                  "correct": "aware"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PREVIOUS job.",
                  "answers": [
                    "former",
                    "steady",
                    "second",
                    "important",
                    "new"
                  ],
                  "word": "PREVIOUS",
                  "correct": "former"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To QUARANTINE them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "destroy",
                    "divide",
                    "isolate",
                    "protect",
                    "free"
                  ],
                  "word": "QUARANTINE",
                  "correct": "isolate"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "More time for RECREATION.",
                  "answers": [
                    "sleep",
                    "play",
                    "work",
                    "practice",
                    "thinking"
                  ],
                  "word": "RECREATION",
                  "correct": "play"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "This SEGMENT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "word",
                    "choice",
                    "part",
                    "idea",
                    "time"
                  ],
                  "word": "SEGMENT",
                  "correct": "part"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Completely SUBMERGED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "open",
                    "lost",
                    "sunk",
                    "wet",
                    "joined"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUBMERGE",
                  "correct": "sunk"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TURQUOISE dresses.",
                  "answers": [
                    "blue-green",
                    "foreign",
                    "dark-red",
                    "white",
                    "gold"
                  ],
                  "word": "TURQUOISE",
                  "correct": "blue-green"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The UTMOST danger.",
                  "answers": [
                    "unknown",
                    "least",
                    "next",
                    "famous",
                    "greatest"
                  ],
                  "word": "UTMOST",
                  "correct": "greatest"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Who was the VICTOR?",
                  "answers": [
                    "loser",
                    "minister",
                    "general",
                    "winner",
                    "leader"
                  ],
                  "word": "VICTOR",
                  "correct": "winner"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Where does she DWELL?",
                  "answers": [
                    "live",
                    "eat",
                    "study",
                    "travel",
                    "work"
                  ],
                  "word": "DWELL",
                  "correct": "live"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It was QUESTIONABLE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "difficult",
                    "impossible",
                    "doubtful",
                    "certain",
                    "unnecessary"
                  ],
                  "word": "QUESTIONABLE",
                  "correct": "doubtful"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ROUSE the people.",
                  "answers": [
                    "cheat",
                    "awaken",
                    "trap",
                    "unite",
                    "destroy"
                  ],
                  "word": "ROUSE",
                  "correct": "awaken"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it dangerous to he in the middle of a STAMPEDE?",
                  "word": "STAMPEDE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually PROCLAIM secrets?",
                  "word": "PROCLAIM",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is going to the dentist an INCIDENT in people's lives?",
                  "word": "INCIDENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Should a driver be MINDFUL of dangers on the road?",
                  "word": "MINDFUL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Did the Civil War happen PREVIOUS to the War of Independence?",
                  "word": "PREVIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are people who aren't sick ever QUARANTINED?",
                  "word": "QUARANTINE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is swimming a form of RECREATION?",
                  "word": "RECREATION",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a chapter a SEGMENT of a book?",
                  "word": "SEGMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a rock be SUBMERGED?",
                  "word": "SUBMERGE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can the sky ever appear TURQUOISE?",
                  "word": "TURQUOISE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are people who are doing their UTMOST really trying?",
                  "word": "UTMOST",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is the VICTOR in a race the one who finishes last?",
                  "word": "VICTOR",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do you DWELL somewhere?",
                  "word": "DWELL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a close call by an umpire in baseball be QUESTIONABLE?",
                  "word": "QUESTIONABLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a sleeping person usually be ROUSED by a leaf falling?",
                  "word": "ROUSE",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "The STAMPEDE was quiet all night, but acted up again in the morning.",
                  "word": "STAMPEDE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Sam said he caught the criminal, so he PROCLAIMED the reward.",
                  "word": "PROCLAIM",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "This book is about several INCIDENTS that took place in the town of Salem.",
                  "word": "INCIDENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I won't he MINDFUL if you want to come with me.",
                  "word": "MINDFUL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She had no PREVIOUS experience, hut still she did the job very well.",
                  "word": "PREVIOUS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The horse was kept in QUARANTINE until it was completely cured.",
                  "word": "QUARANTINE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Scientists think it has been five billion years since the RECREATION of the earth.",
                  "word": "RECREATION",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "One SEGMENT of the movie takes place in Spain.",
                  "word": "SEGMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He SUBMERGED from the water and walked up onto the beach.",
                  "word": "SUBMERGE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Barry turned TURQUOISE with anger at the insult.",
                  "word": "TURQUOISE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Dave enjoyed himself to the UTMOST during his vacation.",
                  "word": "UTMOST",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They were VICTORIOUS in their battle with the enemy forces.",
                  "word": "VICTOR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His speech will DWELL on the problems of getting a job.",
                  "word": "DWELL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His honesty is QUESTIONABLE. There are rumors that he takes bribes.",
                  "word": "QUESTIONABLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The coach's speech ROUSED the team to try even harder.",
                  "word": "ROUSE",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "STAMPEDE",
                  "answers": [
                    "speed",
                    "joy",
                    "fear"
                  ],
                  "word": "STAMPEDE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PROCLAIM",
                  "answers": [
                    "shout",
                    "whisper",
                    "state"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROCLAIM",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INCIDENT",
                  "answers": [
                    "happening",
                    "hope",
                    "occurrence"
                  ],
                  "word": "INCIDENT",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MINDFUL",
                  "answers": [
                    "aware",
                    "careful",
                    "brilliant"
                  ],
                  "word": "MINDFUL",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PREVIOUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "easier",
                    "past",
                    "earlier"
                  ],
                  "word": "PREVIOUS",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "QUARANTINE",
                  "answers": [
                    "separate",
                    "isolate",
                    "tax"
                  ],
                  "word": "QUARANTINE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "RECREATION",
                  "answers": [
                    "lessons",
                    "games",
                    "sports"
                  ],
                  "word": "RECREATION",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SEGMENT",
                  "answers": [
                    "most",
                    "all",
                    "half"
                  ],
                  "word": "SEGMENT",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SUBMERGE",
                  "answers": [
                    "sink",
                    "dive",
                    "sail"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUBMERGE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TURQUOISE",
                  "answers": [
                    "green",
                    "blue",
                    "yellow"
                  ],
                  "word": "TURQUOISE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "UTMOST",
                  "answers": [
                    "extra",
                    "furthest",
                    "best"
                  ],
                  "word": "UTMOST",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "VICTOR",
                  "answers": [
                    "conqueror",
                    "fighter",
                    "winner"
                  ],
                  "word": "VICTOR",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DWELL",
                  "answers": [
                    "stay",
                    "live",
                    "visit"
                  ],
                  "word": "DWELL",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "QUESTIONABLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "doubtful",
                    "untrue",
                    "uncertain"
                  ],
                  "word": "QUESTIONABLE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ROUSE",
                  "answers": [
                    "excite",
                    "worry",
                    "stir"
                  ],
                  "word": "ROUSE",
                  "correct": "1"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.5",
          "definitions": {
            "WAIL": {
              "word": "WAIL",
              "phonetic": "(wail)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to cry, weep </p><p>To WAIL is to cry, usually long and loud in a voice that expresses deep unhappiness or pain; to make a loud, high-pitched sound. </p><p>“The baby WAILED when we took her bottle away.” </p><p>“We could hear the siren WAIL in the distance.” </p><p>WAIL is also a noun. </p><p>“Jane gave out a loud WAIL when she saw that every- one had left without her.”</p>"
            },
            "ABSURD": {
              "word": "ABSURD",
              "phonetic": "(gb-serd'",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">gb-zerd’) adj.: ridiculous, foolish, unreasonable </p><p>Something that is ABSURD makes no sense; it is not reasonable. </p><p>“It was freezing outside when he made the ABSURD suggestion that we all go swimming.” </p><p>“You may think the plan is reasonable, but I consider it ABSURD.” </p><p>“The television show was completely ABSURD. I’ve never seen a sillier program.” </p><p>The noun from ABSURD is ABSURDITY, which means <i class=“def-ital\">ridiculousness</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">foolishness</i>. “She understands the ABSURDITY of pretending to be richer than she is.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ABSURDITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "DEVOUR": {
              "word": "DEVOUR",
              "phonetic": "(di-vowr')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to eat, eat up, consume </p><p>To DEVOUR something is to eat it up greedily. </p><p>“He was so hungry that he DEVOURED the entire pizza at once.” </p><p>DEVOUR can also mean “to use up as if by eating greedily.” </p><p>“The raging fire DEVOURED an entire city block.” </p><p>“He liked her writing so much that he DEVOURED each book in one sitting\"-that is, he read each one quickly and eagerly.</p>"
            },
            "CEASE": {
              "word": "CEASE",
              "phonetic": "(sEs)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to stop, halt, end </p><p>To CEASE is to <i class=“def-ital\">stop</i>, to bring or come to an end. </p><p>“The teacher told them to CEASE talking.” </p><p>“When the rain CEASED the children came out to play again.” </p><p>“Their club CEASED to exist many years ago.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: CEASELESS, adj.</p>"
            },
            "ELIGIBLE": {
              "word": "ELIGIBLE",
              "phonetic": "(el'-ÔøΩjÔøΩbgl)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">fit to be chosen, desirable; qualified </p><p>See -<i class=“def-ital\">able</i> under Suffixes. ELIGIBLE comes from the same Latin word as <i class=“def-ital\">elect</i>; both words have to do with choosing. To <i class=“def-ital\">elect</i> is to <i class=“def-ital\">choose</i>, particularly to choose someone for public office. An ELIGIBLE person is fit or qualified to be chosen. Sometimes this means the person has satisfied legal or other requirements: if you are “EL- IGIBLE for football,” it means, usually, that your school grades are high enough for you to be allowed to play on a team. </p><p>“Previous winners are not ELIGIBLE to enter the con- test again.” </p><p>Sometimes ELIGIBLE simply means “fit to be chosen” because the person or thing is good or desirable: “EL- IGIBLE bachelors” are single men who are suitable or desirable for marriage. </p><p>Other forms of the word: ELIGIBILITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "AMATEUR": {
              "word": "AMATEUR",
              "phonetic": "(am'-g-cher",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">am’-ÔøΩter or am’-g- tyUr) adj.: nonprofessional </p><p>AMATEUR means <i class=“def-ital\">not professional</i>, that is, “not paid for what is being done.” AMATEUR comes from a Latin word meaning to <i class=“def-ital\">love</i>, and is used about people who do something for the love of it, or as a pastime, not to earn money. </p><p>“He was an AMATEUR tennis player; he never played the game for money.” </p><p>“We enjoyed the AMATEUR production of <i class=“def-ital\">Romeo and Juliet</i>.” </p><p>AMATEUR can also be used as a noun and means “a person who does something for the love of it or as a pastime.” </p><p>“Many AMATEURS eventually become professionals.” </p><p>AMATEUR often, but not always, suggests that the person is inexperienced and not very good at what he is doing. </p><p>“He’s just an AMATEUR at this. He’s only been doing it for a couple of months.” </p><p>“She has become such a great pianist that we can no longer call her an AMATEUR.”</p>"
            },
            "EXCLUDE": {
              "word": "EXCLUDE",
              "phonetic": "(eks-klUd')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to keep out, bar, leave out </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">ex-</i> under Prefixes. EXCLUDE means to <i class=“def-ital\">shut out</i>, to keep someone or something from getting in. You can EX- CLUDE either persons or things. </p><p>“Everyone agreed we had to EXCLUDE him from the club.” </p><p>“They decided their report would EXCLUDE all mention of the incident.” </p><p>“We can EXCLUDE the possibility that you committed the crime, since you were out of the country at the time.” </p><p>The adjective from EXCLUDE is EXCLUSIVE. EXCLUSIVE stores deal only with certain rich customers. An EXCLUSIVE in a newspaper is a piece of news which only that newspaper has uncovered, and which it prints before anyone else. </p><p>Other forms of the word: EXCLUSION, n. </p><p>EXCLUSIVE, adj., n.</p>"
            },
            "HOIST": {
              "word": "HOIST",
              "phonetic": "(hoyst)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to raise, lift </p><p>HOIST means to <i class=“def-ital\">lift</i>. The word is especially used about lifting something very heavy by mechanical means. </p><p>“They HOISTED the boat out of the water with ropes and pulleys.” </p><p>“The movers had difficulty HOISTING the piano up to the third floor.” </p><p>HOIST can also be used as a noun and means “a device for lifting.” </p><p>“They used the HOIST to lift the engine out of the car.” </p><p>The most commonly chosen wrong answer on the Pretest is <i class=“def-ital\">steal</i>. This is probably due to a confusion of HOIST with <i class=“def-ital\">heist</i>, which means a <i class=“def-ital\">robbery</i>.</p>"
            },
            "IMPERSONATE": {
              "word": "IMPERSONATE",
              "phonetic": "(im-per'-sÔøΩn-At)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to pretend to be, act the part of  </p><p>To IMPERSONATE someone is to pretend you are that person, to act his part. </p><p>“The robber got into the apartment by IMPERSONATING a telephone repairman.” </p><p>“She IMPERSONATED the movie star so well it was hard to believe she was only a waitress.” </p><p>The noun from IMPERSONATE is IMPERSONATION. </p><p>“His clever IMPERSONATION fooled everyone.” </p><p>Many people think that to IMPERSONATE someone is to <i class=“def-ital\">make fun of</i> him. But you can pretend to be a person without making fun of him. </p><p>Other forms of the word: IMPERSONATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "EXPOSE": {
              "word": "EXPOSE",
              "phonetic": "(eks-pOz')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to uncover, leave open; to disclose, make known </p><p>To EXPOSE is to put out in the open what has previously been protected, hidden, or secret. EXPOSE can be used about physical objects and people. </p><p>“The statue was EXPOSED to the wind and the rain.” </p><p>“The destruction of the fort EXPOSED the soldiers to enemy gunfire.” </p><p>EXPOSE can also be used about plots and secrets. </p><p>“The reporter EXPOSED the secret plot to overthrow the government.” </p><p>EXPOSURE is a noun form of EXPOSE. To die of EXPOSURE means to die from being outside in the cold or the heat for too long. </p><p>“The EXPOSURE of his crimes shocked everyone.” </p><p>“Too much EXPOSURE to X rays is dangerous.” </p><p>” Other forms of the word: EXPOSURE, n.</p>"
            },
            "KERNEL": {
              "word": "KERNEL",
              "phonetic": "(ker'-nÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a seed, core, central part </p><p>A KERNEL is the soft inner part of a nut or a fruit stone. It is also the whole grain or seed of a cereal like wheat or corn. </p><p>“The KERNELS of corn were cut from the ears and put into cans.” </p><p>In general use, KERNEL means “the central or most important part of something.” </p><p>“Although I disagree with much of what you say, there is a KERNEL of truth in it\"-that is, an important, essential part of it is true.</p>"
            },
            "LEASE": {
              "word": "LEASE",
              "phonetic": "(IEs)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to rent </p><p>A LEASE is a contract renting lands, buildings, or the like to someone for a certain period of time. To LEASE something is to rent it to or from someone. </p><p>“He LEASED the farm from its owner for ten years.” </p><p>“The man LEASED the automobile to us for six months.” </p><p>The most common mistake on the Pretest is <i class=“def-ital\">sell</i>. To LEASE something involves paying money for the use of it for a certain period of time. But it does not involve buying or selling.</p>"
            },
            "PENITENTIARY": {
              "word": "PENITENTIARY",
              "phonetic": "(pen-J-ten'-shJ-rE)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a prison, reformatory </p><p>PENITENTIARY is related to the word <i class=“def-ital\">penitent</i>, which means <i class=“def-ital\">sorry</i>. A PENITENTIARY is a place where people are sent as punishment for crimes they have committed. In this country, a PENITENTIARY is always a state or federal prison for people who have committed serious crimes.n“He entered the PENITENTIARY to begin his five-year sentence for robbery.” </p><p>“He worked as a guard in the state’s largest PENITENTIARY.”</p>"
            },
            "ACCELERATE": {
              "word": "ACCELERATE",
              "phonetic": "(ak-sel'-ÔøΩ-rAt)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to speed up, hasten, go faster </p><p>To ACCELERATE something is to make it go faster, to speed it up. </p><p>“Fertilizer ACCELERATES the growth of most plants.” </p><p>“The regular program takes six months; the ACCELERATED program takes only three months.” </p><p>When something ACCELERATES, it speeds up. </p><p>“The car ACCELERATED to sixty miles an hour very quickly.” </p><p>In a car, the ACCELERATOR, or gas pedal, controls the car’s speed. </p><p>“He pressed down on the ACCELERATOR in order to pass the car in front of him.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ACCELERATION, n. </p><p>ACCELERATOR, n.</p>"
            },
            "PRECISE": {
              "word": "PRECISE",
              "phonetic": "(pri-sls')",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">exact, certain, correct </p><p>PRECISE means <i class=“def-ital\">exact</i>, “without error or unclearness.” </p><p>“He says he’ll come some time next week, but he can’t be more PRECISE than that.” </p><p>“Donna tried to be PRECISE in her description of the car.” </p><p>“The bank knew the PRECISE amount of money he had in his savings account.” </p><p>“The game will start at PRECISELY eight o’clock- not a minute sooner or later.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: PRECISION, n.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "5",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Began to WAIL.",
                  "answers": [
                    "laugh",
                    "run",
                    "fight",
                    "hurt",
                    "cry"
                  ],
                  "word": "WAIL",
                  "correct": "cry"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The ABSURD plan.",
                  "answers": [
                    "helpful",
                    "fake",
                    "ridiculous",
                    "clever",
                    "humorous"
                  ],
                  "word": "ABSURD",
                  "correct": "ridiculous"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEVOURED the cake.",
                  "answers": [
                    "baked",
                    "ate",
                    "tasted",
                    "burned",
                    "passed"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEVOUR",
                  "correct": "ate"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "You must CEASE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "stop",
                    "slow down",
                    "change",
                    "begin",
                    "continue"
                  ],
                  "word": "CEASE",
                  "correct": "stop"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They were ELIGIBLE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "reliable",
                    "beautiful",
                    "qualified",
                    "successful",
                    "poor"
                  ],
                  "word": "ELIGIBLE",
                  "correct": "qualified"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "AMATEUR athlete.",
                  "answers": [
                    "stupid",
                    "college",
                    "nonprofessional",
                    "paid",
                    "young"
                  ],
                  "word": "AMATEUR",
                  "correct": "nonprofessional"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They EXCLUDE all foreigners.",
                  "answers": [
                    "hate",
                    "disapprove of",
                    "keep out",
                    "welcome",
                    "hide"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXCLUDE",
                  "correct": "keep out"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Wanted to HOIST it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "carry",
                    "steal",
                    "watch",
                    "raise",
                    "lower"
                  ],
                  "word": "HOIST",
                  "correct": "raise"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "IMPERSONATE him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "meet",
                    "make fun of",
                    "beg",
                    "imitate",
                    "kill"
                  ],
                  "word": "IMPERSONATE",
                  "correct": "imitate"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They EXPOSED it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "uncovered",
                    "talked about",
                    "saw",
                    "guessed",
                    "overlooked"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXPOSE",
                  "correct": "uncovered"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Found the KERNEL.",
                  "answers": [
                    "root",
                    "top",
                    "skin",
                    "seed",
                    "weed"
                  ],
                  "word": "KERNEL",
                  "correct": "seed"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He LEASED it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "saved",
                    "rented",
                    "bought",
                    "lost",
                    "sold"
                  ],
                  "word": "LEASE",
                  "correct": "rented"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Entered the PENITENTIARY.",
                  "answers": [
                    "church",
                    "cell",
                    "school",
                    "prison",
                    "court"
                  ],
                  "word": "PENITENTIARY",
                  "correct": "prison"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The car ACCELERATES.",
                  "answers": [
                    "races",
                    "improves",
                    "crashes",
                    "slows down",
                    "speeds up"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACCELERATE",
                  "correct": "speeds up"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The PRECISE meaning.",
                  "answers": [
                    "former",
                    "exact",
                    "greatest",
                    "usual",
                    "general"
                  ],
                  "word": "PRECISE",
                  "correct": "exact"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people generally WAIL when they are happy?",
                  "word": "WAIL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it ABSURD to ask for help when you're in trouble?",
                  "word": "ABSURD",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a hungry dog DEVOUR a piece of meat?",
                  "word": "DEVOUR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Will you get thin if you CEASE eating?",
                  "word": "CEASE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are children ELIGIBLE to vote for president?",
                  "word": "ELIGIBLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are major league baseball players AMATEURS?",
                  "word": "AMATEUR",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would an EXCLUSIVE club let in everyone who wanted to join it?",
                  "word": "EXCLUDE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would it be easy for one person to HOIST an airplane?",
                  "word": "HOIST",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would it be easy for identical twins to IMPERSONATE each other?",
                  "word": "IMPERSONATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can EXPOSURE to the hot sun give you sunburn?",
                  "word": "EXPOSE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a corn KERNEL be very large?",
                  "word": "KERNEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can automobiles be LEASED?",
                  "word": "LEASE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually dislike being in a PENITENTIARY?",
                  "word": "PENITENTIARY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a car ACCELERATE when it hits a brick wall?",
                  "word": "ACCELERATE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is \"sometime next year\" a PRECISE time?",
                  "word": "PRECISE",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Everyone in the building could hear her WAILING over the death of her friend.",
                  "word": "WAIL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I'm not in the mood for foolishness, so don't give me any ABSURD explanations.",
                  "word": "ABSURD",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She DEVOURED the table so that it was completely clean.",
                  "word": "DEVOUR",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "After listening to the same song for two hours, he was glad when it CEASED.",
                  "word": "CEASE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The chair is so ELIGIBLE it will fall apart when someone sits in it.",
                  "word": "ELIGIBLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He enjoyed being an AMATEUR chess player and didn't care whether or not he made any money at it.",
                  "word": "AMATEUR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Walter was EXCLUDED from taking part because he was too young.",
                  "word": "EXCLUDE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The golfer HOISTED the ball into the hole.",
                  "word": "HOIST",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Sally can do a great IMPERSONATION of her aunt.",
                  "word": "IMPERSONATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Our digging EXPOSED some ancient statues that had been buried for centuries.",
                  "word": "EXPOSE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "There wasn't a KERNEL of truth to the rumor that the teacher was quitting.",
                  "word": "KERNEL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Mr. Allen makes a good income by LEASING apartments he owns.",
                  "word": "LEASE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The judge sentenced him to ten years in the PENITENTIARY.",
                  "word": "PENITENTIARY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They told us we were going too fast and should ACCELERATE our pace instead.",
                  "word": "ACCELERATE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The PRECISE value of the painting is from two to ten thousand dollars or so.",
                  "word": "PRECISE",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "WAIL",
                  "answers": [
                    "yell",
                    "sob",
                    "chat"
                  ],
                  "word": "WAIL",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ABSURD",
                  "answers": [
                    "unsafe",
                    "foolish",
                    "senseless"
                  ],
                  "word": "ABSURD",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEVOUR",
                  "answers": [
                    "give up",
                    "use up",
                    "eat"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEVOUR",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CEASE",
                  "answers": [
                    "end",
                    "wait",
                    "quit"
                  ],
                  "word": "CEASE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ELIGIBLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "eager",
                    "suitable",
                    "desirable"
                  ],
                  "word": "ELIGIBLE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "AMATEUR",
                  "answers": [
                    "unusual",
                    "unpaid",
                    "inexperienced"
                  ],
                  "word": "AMATEUR",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EXCLUDE",
                  "answers": [
                    "enter",
                    "omit",
                    "leave out"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXCLUDE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HOIST",
                  "answers": [
                    "raise",
                    "carry",
                    "lift"
                  ],
                  "word": "HOIST",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "IMPERSONATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "imitate",
                    "imagine",
                    "pretend"
                  ],
                  "word": "IMPERSONATE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EXPOSE",
                  "answers": [
                    "renew",
                    "open",
                    "bare"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXPOSE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "KERNEL",
                  "answers": [
                    "end",
                    "seed",
                    "center"
                  ],
                  "word": "KERNEL",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "LEASE",
                  "answers": [
                    "rent",
                    "give",
                    "use"
                  ],
                  "word": "LEASE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PENITENTIARY",
                  "answers": [
                    "whip",
                    "jail",
                    "prison"
                  ],
                  "word": "PENITENTIARY",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ACCELERATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "quicken",
                    "enlarge",
                    "hasten"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACCELERATE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PRECISE",
                  "answers": [
                    "true",
                    "correct",
                    "usual"
                  ],
                  "word": "PRECISE",
                  "correct": "2"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.6",
          "definitions": {
            "CONFLICT": {
              "word": "CONFLICT",
              "phonetic": "{kon'-flikt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a struggle, battle, quarrel, clash </p><p>CONFLICT comes from a Latin word which means “a striking together.” See <i class=“def-ital\">con-</i> under Prefixes. A CONFLICT is a situation in which people, nations, events, or interests disagree or interfere with one another. It could be as major as a war or battle. </p><p>“During the CONFLICT ten thousand soldiers lost their lives.” </p><p>Or a CONFLICT could be minor. “She had a CONFLICT between Math and English. Both classes met at the same time.” CONFLICT is also a verb, meaning to <i class=“def-ital\">clash</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">disagree</i>. As a verb the word is pronounced k:in-flikt’. “Their stories of what happened CONFLICT, so who is telling the truth?” </p><p>“His latest statement CONFLICTS with several earlier statements he made.” </p><p>The most commonly chosen incorrect answer in the Pretest is <i class=“def-ital\">injury</i>. An <i class=“def-ital\">injury</i> may be the result of a CONFLICT, but the two words do not have the same meaning.</p>"
            },
            "PROSPER": {
              "word": "PROSPER",
              "phonetic": "{pros'-pÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to succeed, flourish </p><p>When someone PROSPERS he is succeeding or doing well. The word usually suggests continued and steadily increasing success. The word often suggests financial suc- cess. </p><p>“He PROSPERED in his new business.” </p><p>It can be used about other kinds of success as well. </p><p>“Our cat was sickly for a while, but with the proper medicine and a better diet he began to PROSPER.” </p><p>Things like companies or countries can also PROSPER. </p><p>“The town PROSPERED when the highway was built near it.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: PROSPERITY, n. </p><p>PROSPEROUS, adj.</p>"
            },
            "REAP": {
              "word": "REAP",
              "phonetic": "{rEp)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to harvest, gather </p><p>To REAP is to cut down and gather in a crop, especially a crop of grain. </p><p>“They worked all day to REAP the wheat.” </p><p>In a general sense, REAP means “to get or win as a result of your work.” </p><p>“He hoped to REAP the benefits of his college education.” </p><p>“The inventor REAPED a fortune from this machine.”</p>"
            },
            "CAVITY": {
              "word": "CAVITY",
              "phonetic": "{kav'-ÔøΩtE)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a hole, empty space </p><p>CAVITY is related to the word <i class=“def-ital\">cave</i>. A CAVITY is a hole, a hollowed-out space in a solid object. A CAVITY in a tooth is a hole caused by decay. </p><p>“In a hidden CAVITY in the wall they found a sack of gold.” </p><p>“The dentist found several CAVITIES in the child’s teeth.” Many people pick tooth as the meaning of CAVITY on the Pretest. These people have heard the word used, but don’t know its exact meaning. A CAVITY is a hole in a tooth, not the tooth itself.</p>"
            },
            "SHRIVEL": {
              "word": "SHRIVEL",
              "phonetic": "{shriv'-ÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to shrink, wither, dry up and wrinkle  </p><p>To SHRIVEL is to shrink in size and become dry and wrinkled. Often something SHRIVELS because of heat. </p><p>“He threw the note into the fireplace where it SHRIV- ELED up as it burned.” </p><p>Or because of age or illness: “When people get very old, their skin SHRIVELS.” </p><p>“In the old book we found a SHRIVELED leaf which someone had wanted to keep.” </p><p>SHRIVEL can also be used about anything that can be said to dry up and shrink. </p><p>“His once great talent seemed to SHRIVEL with age.” </p><p>Usage: SHRIVEL is often followed by <i class=“def-ital\">up</i>.</p>"
            },
            "SLAY": {
              "word": "SLAY",
              "phonetic": "{slA)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to murder, kill </p><p>To SLAY someone is to put him to death by force, to murder him. SLAY is a literary word, more often used in print than in ordinary conversation. </p><p>“The bank guard was SLAIN by an unknown gun- man.” </p><p>“The giant SLEW him with one swing of his mighty fist.” </p><p>Usage: The past tense of SLAY is SLEW. The past participle is SLAIN.</p>"
            },
            "THRASH": {
              "word": "THRASH",
              "phonetic": "(thrash)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to beat, pound, whip; to move violently </p><p>THRASH means to <i class=“def-ital\">beat</i>, usually repeatedly with a stick or whip. </p><p>“In the spring he always had to THRASH the carpets with a rug beater.” </p><p>“Mr. Jones took out his anger at the world by THRASHING his dog.” </p><p>Because the idea of waving the arms about in beating something is included in THRASH, the word has also come to mean simply “to move or toss about violently.” </p><p>“In her sleep Debbie THRASHED around so much that she kicked off all her covers.”</p>"
            },
            "ACQUAINTANCE": {
              "word": "ACQUAINTANCE",
              "phonetic": "(a-kwAn'-tans)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">familiarity; a person one knows slightly </p><p>To be ACQUAINTED with something is to be familiar with it. The word suggests only a slight knowledge, not a deep understanding. </p><p>“He speaks two languages very well and is ACQUAINTED with a dozen more.” To be ACQUAINTED with a person is to know him, although usually not very well. </p><p>“I am ACQUAINTED with Bill. I have spoken to him a few times.” ACQUAINTANCE is a noun from ACQUAINT. See <i class=“def-ital\">-ance</i> under Suffixes. ACQUAINTANCE is a general familiarity with something, but not a thorough knowledge. “Ralph has some ACQUAINTANCE with legal matters, although he has never studied law.” </p><p>An ACQUAINTANCE is someone you know slightly, not quite a friend. Other forms of the word: ACQUAINT, v. </p><p>ACQUAINTED, adj. </p><p>Usage: ACQUAINTANCE, when it means <i class=“def-ital\">familiarity</i>, is usually followed by <i class=“def-ital\">with</i>.</p>"
            },
            "BANQUET": {
              "word": "BANQUET",
              "phonetic": "(bang'-kwit)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a feast, elaborate meal </p><p>A BANQUET is a large, elaborate meal attended by many people. It is usually given in honor of someone or to mark a special occasion. </p><p>“The championship football team was given a large BANQUET to celebrate their victory.” “Five hundred people were at the BANQUET to honor Mr. Jones on his retirement.” </p><p>“When he saw all the food and drink on the table he said this wasn’t just a regular meal, it was a BANQUET.”</p>"
            },
            "REDUCE": {
              "word": "REDUCE",
              "phonetic": "(ri-dUs')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to make less, make smaller, lessen, shrink </p><p>To REDUCE something is to make it smaller or less. </p><p>“The driver REDUCED his speed as he went around the corner.” </p><p>“Alice REDUCED her weight by going without lunch.” </p><p>“We must REDUCE the amount of money we spend.” </p><p>“The soldier’s rank was REDUCED from sergeant to corporal.” </p><p>REDUCTION is the noun from REDUCE. </p><p>“There has been a great REDUCTION in the number of mistakes since we started checking the work more carefully.” </p><p>“I will wait for a REDUCTION in the price before I buy it.” </p><p>The most common mistake on the Pretest is to think that REDUCE means <i class=“def-ital\">end</i>. You do not end something by RE- DUCING it, you just make the size or amount of it smaller. Other forms of the word: REDUCTION, n.</p>"
            },
            "BLOATED": {
              "word": "BLOATED",
              "phonetic": "(blO'-tid)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">swollen, puffed up </p><p>When something is BLOATED it is swollen beyond its normal size, usually with a liquid or gas. </p><p>BLOATED usually gives the sense of being puffed up in an unhealthy way. </p><p>“After drinking so much water she felt BLOATED.” </p><p>“Her legs became BLOATED as a result of the dis- ease.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: BLOAT, v.</p>"
            },
            "CLUTCH": {
              "word": "CLUTCH",
              "phonetic": "(kluhch)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to seize, grab </p><p>To CLUTCH something is to seize it and hold on to it tightly, like a bird grasping something in its claws. </p><p>“He CLUTCHED the kitten so tightly that it tried to wriggle free.” </p><p>“The baby CLUTCHED its bottle with both hands.” </p><p>To CLUTCH at something is to try to get hold of it. </p><p>“Whenever she was frightened she would CLUTCH at her mother’s hand.” </p><p>CLUTCH is also a noun, meaning <i class=“def-ital\">grasp</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">control</i>. It is often used in the plural. </p><p>“The child was in the CLUTCHES of evil kidnappers.”</p>"
            },
            "STAGGER": {
              "word": "STAGGER",
              "phonetic": "(stag'-ÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to move unsteadily, totter, sway </p><p>STAGGER means to <i class=“def-ital\">move unsteadily</i> or to <i class=“def-ital\">sway</i>. Someone who is STAGGERING looks as if he is about to fall. </p><p>“The drunken man STAGGERED down the street.” </p><p>“The fighter was hit so hard by his opponent that he STAGGERED.” </p><p>When something STAGGERS you, it almost knocks you down. STAGGER can be used in this sense about news or ideas which astonish or shock. </p><p>“The news of her accident STAGGERED me.” </p><p>“Everyone was STAGGERED by the increase in the cost of living.” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Fall down</i> is the most popular wrong answer. Someone who STAGGERS may be about to fall, but STAGGER does not mean to <i class=“def-ital\">fall down</i>.</p>"
            },
            "COMMITMENT": {
              "word": "COMMITMENT",
              "phonetic": "(kÔøΩmit'-mÔøΩnt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a pledge, obligation, promise </p><p>One meaning of the verb to COMMIT is to <i class=“def-ital\">pledge</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">undertake</i>. </p><p>“The governor has COMMITTED himself to lowering taxes this year.” </p><p>A COMMITMENT is something to which you are pledged, a promise. See <i class=“def-ital\">-ment</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“She forgot all about her COMMITMENT to sing in the show.” </p><p>“You made a COMMITMENT to help me move this morning. You can’t back out now.” </p><p>COMMITMENT is also the state of being COMMIT- TED. </p><p>“His COMMITMENT to their cause lessened when they started talking about violence.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: COMMIT, v.</p>"
            },
            "DEBRIS": {
              "word": "DEBRIS",
              "phonetic": "(dÔøΩbrE')",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">ruins, rubbish, refuse </p><p>Note the pronunciation. DEBRIS is a French word and keeps its French pronunciation. DEBRIS is the scattered broken pieces of something that has fallen apart or been destroyed. </p><p>“The ground was covered with DEBRIS after the train wreck.” </p><p>“It took weeks to clean up the DEBRIS left behind by the flood.” </p><p>“After the fire there was nothing but DEBRIS where the house had once stood.”</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "6",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "After the CONFLICT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "injury",
                    "fall",
                    "storm",
                    "game",
                    "struggle"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONFLICT",
                  "correct": "struggle"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They will all PROSPER.",
                  "answers": [
                    "succeed",
                    "pray",
                    "wonder",
                    "enjoy",
                    "fail"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROSPER",
                  "correct": "succeed"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "REAP the corn.",
                  "answers": [
                    "harvest",
                    "boil",
                    "store",
                    "plant",
                    "buy"
                  ],
                  "word": "REAP",
                  "correct": "harvest"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Large CAVITY.",
                  "answers": [
                    "pile",
                    "stain",
                    "tooth",
                    "hole",
                    "cut"
                  ],
                  "word": "_",
                  "correct": "hole"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Will it SHRIVEL?",
                  "answers": [
                    "leak",
                    "squeak",
                    "shrink",
                    "stop",
                    "grow"
                  ],
                  "word": "SHRIVEL",
                  "correct": "shrink"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To SLAY them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "kill",
                    "hide",
                    "spread",
                    "strike",
                    "cure"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLAY",
                  "correct": "kill"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They will THRASH us.",
                  "answers": [
                    "bite",
                    "kill",
                    "tie",
                    "beat",
                    "thank"
                  ],
                  "word": "THRASH",
                  "correct": "beat"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "General ACQUAINTANCE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "love",
                    "excellence",
                    "ignorance",
                    "familiarity",
                    "oddity"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACQUAINTANCE",
                  "correct": "familiarity"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "At the BANQUET.",
                  "answers": [
                    "dance",
                    "feast",
                    "bar",
                    "meeting",
                    "game"
                  ],
                  "word": "BANQUET",
                  "correct": "feast"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "REDUCE tension.",
                  "answers": [
                    "fight",
                    "increase",
                    "cause",
                    "lessen",
                    "end"
                  ],
                  "word": "REDUCE",
                  "correct": "lessen"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It was BLOATED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "under water",
                    "scratched",
                    "swollen",
                    "diseased",
                    "shrunken"
                  ],
                  "word": "BLOATED",
                  "correct": "swollen"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CLUTCH them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "ruin",
                    "steal",
                    "hide",
                    "release",
                    "seize"
                  ],
                  "word": "CLUTCH",
                  "correct": "seize"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Caused him to STAGGER.",
                  "answers": [
                    "jump back",
                    "fall down",
                    "choke",
                    "scream",
                    "move unsteadily"
                  ],
                  "word": "STAGGER",
                  "correct": "move unsteadily"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His COMMITMENT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "feeling",
                    "refusal",
                    "crime",
                    "pledge",
                    "desire"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMMITMENT",
                  "correct": "pledge"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Saw the DEBRIS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "paper",
                    "party",
                    "ruins",
                    "building",
                    "riot"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEBRIS",
                  "correct": "ruins"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "If two stories CONFLICT, are they the same?",
                  "word": "CONFLICT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do most people want to PROSPER?",
                  "word": "PROSPER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a farmer REAP corn before he plants it?",
                  "word": "REAP",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are CAVITIES always large?",
                  "word": "CAVITY",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a balloon SHRIVEL when it is blown up?",
                  "word": "SHRIVEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Have you ever been SLAIN?",
                  "word": "SLAY",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do most people dislike being THRASHED?",
                  "word": "THRASH",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Should an auto mechanic have some ACQUAINTANCE with engines?",
                  "word": "ACQUAINTANCE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are most meals BANQUETS?",
                  "word": "BANQUET",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is there a REDUCTION in a child's size as he grows up?",
                  "word": "REDUCE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "1I. Is a BLOATED face pleasant to look at?",
                  "word": "BLOATED",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it easy to CLUTCH something that is slippery?",
                  "word": "CLUTCH",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a punch make a person STAGGER?",
                  "word": "STAGGER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "When two people get married, do they make a COMMITMENT to each other?",
                  "word": "COMMITMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Could a bomb produce a lot of DEBRIS?",
                  "word": "DEBRIS",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Quite a CONFLICT broke out between the supporters and the opponents of the king.",
                  "word": "CONFLICT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She PROSPERED that her students would do well on the test.",
                  "word": "PROSPER",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The employee received fifty dollars for his suggestion, but the company REAPED the profits.",
                  "word": "REAP",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The doctor removed a large CAVITY that was growing on his skin.",
                  "word": "CAVITY",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Bill started to SHRIVEL when he heard the funny story.",
                  "word": "SHRIVEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "David SLEW the giant Goliath with a stone.",
                  "word": "SLAY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Mr. White threatened to THRASH them if they ever stole anything from his store again.",
                  "word": "THRASH",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "You'll have to tell me what they're saying, since I am not ACQUAINTED with their language.",
                  "word": "ACQUAINTANCE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The prince invited everyone to a huge BANQUET when he became king.",
                  "word": "BANQUET",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The politician promised to REDUCE taxes, but instead they were increased.",
                  "word": "REDUCE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His stomach felt BLOATED after he ate the huge meal.",
                  "word": "BLOATED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The drowning man CLUTCHED at the rope they threw to him.",
                  "word": "CLUTCH",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Bill was STAGGERED when the boss told him he was fired.",
                  "word": "STAGGER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Unless we have a firm COMMITMENT that the work will be completed by December 1st, we will not sign the agreement.",
                  "word": "COMMITMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We had quite a DEBRIS when we won the championship.",
                  "word": "DEBRIS",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "CONFLICT",
                  "answers": [
                    "war",
                    "fear",
                    "quarrel"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONFLICT",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PROSPER",
                  "answers": [
                    "succeed",
                    "protect",
                    "thrive"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROSPER",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "REAP",
                  "answers": [
                    "gather",
                    "profit",
                    "seed"
                  ],
                  "word": "REAP",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CAVITY",
                  "answers": [
                    "stain",
                    "gap",
                    "hole"
                  ],
                  "word": "CAVITY",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SHRIVEL",
                  "answers": [
                    "wither",
                    "confuse",
                    "dry"
                  ],
                  "word": "SHRIVEL",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SLAY",
                  "answers": [
                    "shoot",
                    "stab",
                    "rob"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLAY",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "THRASH",
                  "answers": [
                    "throw",
                    "whip",
                    "pound"
                  ],
                  "word": "THRASH",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ACQUAINTANCE",
                  "answers": [
                    "knowledge",
                    "friendship",
                    "happiness"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACQUAINTANCE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "BANQUET",
                  "answers": [
                    "food",
                    "drink",
                    "sleep"
                  ],
                  "word": "BANQUET",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "REDUCE",
                  "answers": [
                    "decrease",
                    "lessen",
                    "widen"
                  ],
                  "word": "REDUCE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "BLOATED",
                  "answers": [
                    "bloody",
                    "enlarged",
                    "stuffed"
                  ],
                  "word": "BLOATED",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CLUTCH",
                  "answers": [
                    "hold",
                    "move",
                    "grab"
                  ],
                  "word": "CLUTCH",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "STAGGER",
                  "answers": [
                    "shock",
                    "stop",
                    "sway"
                  ],
                  "word": "STAGGER",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "COMMITMENT",
                  "answers": [
                    "agreement",
                    "hope",
                    "promise"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMMITMENT",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEBRIS",
                  "answers": [
                    "litter",
                    "rubble",
                    "snow"
                  ]
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ],
      "reviewTest": {
        "wordList": [
          {
            "word": "ACCELERATE",
            "answer": "accelerate"
          },
          {
            "word": "ELIGIBLE",
            "answer": "eligible"
          },
          {
            "word": "KERNEL",
            "answer": "kernels"
          },
          {
            "word": "REDUCE",
            "answer": "reduced"
          },
          {
            "word": "SUBMERGE",
            "answer": "submerged"
          },
          {
            "word": "ACQUAINTANCE",
            "answer": "acquaintance."
          },
          {
            "word": "EXCLUDE",
            "answer": "exclude"
          },
          {
            "word": "MINDFUL",
            "answer": "mindful"
          },
          {
            "word": "SEGMENT",
            "answer": "segment"
          },
          {
            "word": "THRASH",
            "answer": "thrashed"
          },
          {
            "word": "CLUTCH",
            "answer": "clutched"
          },
          {
            "word": "EXPOSE",
            "answer": "exposed"
          },
          {
            "word": "PENITENTIARY",
            "answer": "penitentiary"
          },
          {
            "word": "SHRIVEL",
            "answer": "shrivel"
          },
          {
            "word": "VICTOR",
            "answer": "victor"
          },
          {
            "word": "COMMITMENT",
            "answer": "commitment"
          },
          {
            "word": "IMPERSONATE",
            "answer": "impersonated"
          },
          {
            "word": "QUESTIONABLE",
            "answer": "questionable"
          },
          {
            "word": "SLAY",
            "answer": "slay"
          },
          {
            "word": "WAIL",
            "answer": "wail"
          },
          {
            "word": "CONFLICT",
            "answer": "conflict"
          },
          {
            "word": "INCIDENT",
            "answer": "incident"
          },
          {
            "word": "RECREATION",
            "answer": "recreation"
          },
          {
            "word": "ABSURD",
            "answer": "absurd"
          },
          {
            "word": "CEASE",
            "answer": "ceased"
          },
          {
            "word": "LEASE",
            "answer": "lease"
          },
          {
            "word": "PROSPER",
            "answer": "prosper"
          },
          {
            "word": "STAGGER",
            "answer": "staggered"
          },
          {
            "word": "AMATEUR",
            "answer": "amateur"
          },
          {
            "word": "DEBRIS",
            "answer": "debris"
          },
          {
            "word": "PRECISE",
            "answer": "precise"
          },
          {
            "word": "QUARANTINE",
            "answer": "quarantine"
          },
          {
            "word": "STAMPEDE",
            "answer": "stampede"
          },
          {
            "word": "BANQUET",
            "answer": "banquet"
          },
          {
            "word": "DEVOUR",
            "answer": "devour"
          },
          {
            "word": "PREVIOUS",
            "answer": "previous"
          },
          {
            "word": "REAP",
            "answer": "reap"
          },
          {
            "word": "TURQUOISE",
            "answer": "turquoise"
          },
          {
            "word": "BLOATED",
            "answer": "bloated"
          },
          {
            "word": "DWELL"
          },
          {
            "word": "PROCLAIM",
            "answer": "proclaimed"
          },
          {
            "word": "ROUSE",
            "answer": "roused"
          },
          {
            "word": "UTMOST",
            "answer": "utmost"
          },
          {
            "word": "CAVITY",
            "answer": "cavities"
          },
          {
            "word": "HOIST",
            "answer": "hoist"
          }
        ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "part1": "The",
            "part2": "was settled when both sides agreed they had been partly to blame.",
            "correct": "conflict",
            "word": "CONFLICT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The man with the gun threatened to",
            "part2": "them all if they talked.",
            "correct": "slay",
            "word": "SLAY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "She",
            "part2": "the doll even more tightly as the man tried to take it away from her.",
            "correct": "clutched",
            "word": "CLUTCH"
          },
          {
            "part1": "When they received the loan, they made a(n)",
            "part2": "to pay it back within two years.",
            "correct": "commitment",
            "word": "COMMITMENT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Since no one liked Bert, they tried to",
            "part2": "him from all their games.",
            "correct": "exclude",
            "word": "EXCLUDE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Bill",
            "part2": "Jim so well that he fooled Jim's brother.",
            "correct": "impersonated",
            "word": "IMPERSONATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Ed had to put on the brakes because the bicycle began to",
            "part2": "too fast as it went downhill.",
            "correct": "accelerate",
            "word": "ACCELERATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "What happened was of no great importance; it was simply a minor",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "incident",
            "word": "INCIDENT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "After working hard all week you need some time for",
            "part2": "on Saturday and Sunday.",
            "correct": "recreation",
            "word": "RECREATION"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The unhappy little boy began to",
            "part2": "when his parents told him that he had to go to school all by himself.",
            "correct": "wail",
            "word": "WAIL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The plant began to",
            "part2": "from lack of water.",
            "correct": "shrivel",
            "word": "SHRIVEL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Ken loves to eat popcorn, even though he usually gets a few",
            "part2": "stuck in his teeth.",
            "correct": "kernels",
            "word": "KERNEL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Nora",
            "part2": "about in pain until the doctor gave her some medication.",
            "correct": "thrashed",
            "word": "THRASH"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Central High was the",
            "part2": "in the football game; they defeated us 20-17.",
            "correct": "victor",
            "word": "VICTOR"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We must be",
            "part2": "of our responsibilities if we want to succeed.",
            "correct": "mindful",
            "word": "MINDFUL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It is",
            "part2": "whether or not we will finish on time. Most people think we won't.",
            "correct": "questionable",
            "word": "QUESTIONABLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They said a lost continent lay",
            "part2": "deep in the middle of the ocean.",
            "correct": "submerged",
            "word": "SUBMERGE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The prisoners were taken to the federal",
            "part2": "to serve their sentences.",
            "correct": "penitentiary",
            "word": "PENITENTIARY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Art was not",
            "part2": "to run for this office because he hadn't lived in town long enough.",
            "correct": "eligible",
            "word": "ELIGIBLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The magazine article",
            "part2": "the secret inner workings of the large corporation.",
            "correct": "exposed",
            "word": "EXPOSE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Tom is only a(n)",
            "part2": "We met at a party but have never really spoken to each other.",
            "correct": "acquaintance.",
            "word": "ACQUAINTANCE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They",
            "part2": "the size of the stage from a hundred feet to fifty.",
            "correct": "reduced",
            "word": "REDUCE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Each",
            "part2": "of the history course covers a different century.",
            "correct": "segment",
            "word": "SEGMENT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The ads promised that this car will give you the",
            "part2": "excitement you could possibly have in your life.",
            "correct": "utmost",
            "word": "UTMOST"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It's",
            "part2": "to expect a two-year-old child to prepare supper for the whole family.",
            "correct": "absurd",
            "word": "ABSURD"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The blow to the head",
            "part2": "him, but he managed to stay on his feet.",
            "correct": "staggered",
            "word": "STAGGER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The",
            "part2": "surface of the lake seemed to mix the color of the blue sky and the green grass.",
            "correct": "turquoise",
            "word": "TURQUOISE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "His stomach was",
            "part2": "because he drank too many soft drinks.",
            "correct": "bloated",
            "word": "BLOATED"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Her heart had stopped beating and her breathing had",
            "part2": ", but the doctor was able to bring her back to life.",
            "correct": "ceased",
            "word": "CEASE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The teacher said her",
            "part2": "classes had all been much smarter than her present one.",
            "correct": "previous",
            "word": "PREVIOUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The famous writer",
            "part2": "for many years in that house on the corner.",
            "correct": "dwelt",
            "word": "DWELL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "There were several",
            "part2": "in her teeth which the dentist had to fill.",
            "correct": "cavities",
            "word": "CAVITY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "After years of barely being able to pay the bills he finally started to",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "prosper",
            "word": "PROSPER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The noise of the rubbish truck",
            "part2": "Ann early in the morning.",
            "correct": "roused",
            "word": "ROUSE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Mr. Simpson was unable to",
            "part2": "the benefits of his discovery because he died shortly afterward.",
            "correct": "reap",
            "word": "REAP"
          },
          {
            "part1": "I'm only a(n)",
            "part2": "golfer now, but someday I hope to be good enough so that I can make a lot of money.",
            "correct": "amateur",
            "word": "AMATEUR"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They used a large crane to",
            "part2": "the cement blocks up to the roof.",
            "correct": "hoist",
            "word": "HOIST"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We all cooked something for the huge",
            "part2": "at which we were honoring the principal.",
            "correct": "banquet",
            "word": "BANQUET"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The fire at one end of the room caused a real",
            "part2": "for the exits as people rushed to get out.",
            "correct": "stampede",
            "word": "STAMPEDE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Our family used to",
            "part2": "a cottage on the lake for three months every summer.",
            "correct": "lease",
            "word": "LEASE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Steve arrived home at the",
            "part2": "moment that his father pulled into the driveway.",
            "correct": "precise",
            "word": "PRECISE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It took us weeks to clean up the",
            "part2": "after the tornado went through the city.",
            "correct": "debris",
            "word": "DEBRIS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The defendant",
            "part2": "his innocence to everyone in the courtroom.",
            "correct": "proclaimed",
            "word": "PROCLAIM"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They had to",
            "part2": "him in order to keep his disease from spreading.",
            "correct": "quarantine",
            "word": "QUARANTINE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Mary liked candy so much that she could",
            "part2": "a whole box of chocolates at one sitting.",
            "correct": "devour",
            "word": "DEVOUR"
          }
        ],
        "type": "fitb"
      }
    },
    {
      "wordsets": [
        {
          "title": "2.7",
          "definitions": {
            "PROTEST": {
              "word": "PROTEST",
              "phonetic": "(prO-test')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to object to, talk against, disapprove of </p><p>PROTEST is a word that has undergone a complete change of meaning. PROTEST used to mean <i class=“def-ital\">to speak</i> for something. See <i class=“def-ital\">pro-</i> under Prefixes. This use is still found in the expression “to PROTEST your innocence\"-that is, to declare or speak in favor of your innocence. Now, however, PROTEST usually means to <i class=“def-ital\">speak against</i> something. </p><p>“The loser PROTESTED the decision against him.” </p><p>“The college students PROTESTED against the war.” </p><p>“The workers PROTESTED that they weren’t paid enough.” </p><p>PROTEST is also a noun, pronounced prO’-test. </p><p>“They ignored our PROTESTS and cut down the tree anyway.”</p>"
            },
            "ISOLATED": {
              "word": "ISOLATED",
              "phonetic": "(Is'-ÔøΩIAt-id)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">alone, solitary, apart </p><p>ISOLATED comes from a Latin word meaning <i class=“def-ital\">island</i>. Someone or something that is ISOLATED is cut off, like an island, from other persons or things. </p><p>“We live on a very ISOLATED farm. There’s no one else for miles around.” </p><p>“The doctors said the patient should be kept ISOLATED so that he doesn’t give the disease to anyone else.” </p><p>To ISOLATE something is to put or keep it apart from others. </p><p>“We tried to ISOLATE the problems and solve them one by one.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ISOLATE, v.</p><p> ISOLATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "DEDICATED": {
              "word": "DEDICATED",
              "phonetic": "(ded'-ÔøΩkA-tid)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">devoted, committed, zealous </p><p>To DEDICATE something is to devote it to a particular use, person, or goal. </p><p>“She DEDICATED the book to her parents.” </p><p>“He DEDICATED his life to finding a cure for the common cold.” </p><p>Someone who is DEDICATED is devoted to a cause or a purpose. </p><p>“She is a very DEDICATED musician. She practices many hours every day.” </p><p>“They are DEDICATED to proving their father’s innocence.” </p><p>“There aren’t enough DEDICATED men in the party. Too many of them just don’t seem to care.\"</p><p> Other forms of the word: DEDICATE, v. </p><p>DEDICATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "FLAWLESS": {
              "word": "FLAWLESS",
              "phonetic": "(flo'-lis)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">perfect, faultless</p><p>A FLAW is a faulty part of something, like a crack in a dish or an imperfection in a jewel. FLAWLESS means “having no FLAW.” See <i class=“def-ital\">-less</i> under Suffixes. “The diamond was FLAWLESS. I have never seen such a perfect stone.” </p><p>“His FLAWLESS reputation was spoiled by that one stupid act.” </p><p>“Donna memorized the poem and then recited it FLAWLESSLY to the class.” </p><p>Many people choose <i class=“def-ital\">bad</i> as the meaning of FLAWLESS. Bad is just about the opposite in meaning of FLAWLESS. People who choose it perhaps know what a FLAW is, but do not know what the suffix <i class=“def-ital\">-less</i> means. </p><p>Other forms of the word: FLAW, n. </p><p>FLAWLESSLY, adv.</p>"
            },
            "DISRUPT": {
              "word": "DISRUPT",
              "phonetic": "(dis-ruhpt')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to break up, throw into disorder </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">dis-</i> under Prefixes. The <i class=“def-ital\">rupt</i> part of the word means break. It is also found in words like <i class=“def-ital\">interrupt</i> and <i class=“def-ital\">rupture</i>. To DISRUPT something is to break it apart, to destroy the way it normally works. Very often the word suggests that this is only happening for a short time. </p><p>“The electrical storm DISRUPTED telephone service for several hours.” </p><p>“His angry speech DISRUPTED the conference.” </p><p>“Her attempt to teach the class was totally DISRUPTED by the noise outside.” </p><p>“The painters DISRUPTED our office completely. We didn’t know where to find anything, where to sit, or what to do.\"</p><p> Other forms of the word: DISRUPTION, n. </p><p>DISRUPTIVE, adj.</p>"
            },
            "FULFILL": {
              "word": "FULFILL",
              "phonetic": "(ful-fil')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to carry out, complete, satisfy, accomplish </p><p>To FULFILL originally meant what it sounds like: to <i class=“def-ital\">fill up, make full</i>. It is no longer used in this way. Today it means to <i class=“def-ital\">do</i> something <i class=“def-ital\">fully</i>, to <i class=“def-ital\">complete</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">accomplish</i> it. </p><p>“Jane FULFILLED her promise to complete the job on time.” </p><p>“Alan has FULFILLED all the requirements for be- coming a lifeguard.” </p><p>“This product FULFILLED all our expectations. It is just what we wanted.”</p>"
            },
            "HORDE": {
              "word": "HORDE",
              "phonetic": "(hord)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a crowd, mob, throng, swarm </p><p>A HORDE was originally a wandering tribe of Mongols (an Asian people). Today HORDE is used about any large number of people or things, especially when they are rough or savage. </p><p>“HORDES of fans pushed against the gates of the stadium screaming to be let in.” </p><p>“A HORDE of children tramped through the house, leaving their dirty fingerprints on everything.”</p>"
            },
            "INTERNAL": {
              "word": "INTERNAL",
              "phonetic": "(in-tern'-ÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">inner, interior </p><p>INTERNAL means “having to do with the inside” of something, <i class=“def-ital\">inner</i>. See <i class=“def-ital\">in-</i>, under Prefixes. INTERNAL injuries are injuries suffered inside the body. “The president claimed the foreign government was interfering in the INTERNAL affairs of his country.” </p><p>“They carefully removed the cover to get at the INTERNAL parts of the machine.” </p><p>The opposite of INTERNAL is <i class=“def-ital\">external</i>, which means <i class=“def-ital\">outside, outer</i>. See <i class=“def-ital\">ex</i> under Prefixes.</p>"
            },
            "JUNCTION": {
              "word": "JUNCTION",
              "phonetic": "(juhngk'-shÔøΩn)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a joining, meeting-place, union, connection </p><p>A JUNCTION is a joining, a coming together of two or more things. A JUNCTION is also a place where the joining occurs. </p><p>“They built a town at the JUNCTION of the two railroad lines\"-that is, where the two lines met and crossed. The most popular wrong answer on the Pretest is <i class=“def-ital\">dividing</i>, which is an opposite of JUNCTION.</p>"
            },
            "NUISANCE": {
              "word": "NUISANCE",
              "phonetic": "(nUs-ÔøΩns)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a bother, annoyance </p><p>A NUISANCE is a person or thing that causes trouble or worry to others. </p><p>“This table is in everyone’s way. It’s nothing but a NUISANCE.” </p><p>“That boy is making a NUISANCE of himself, teasing his sister while she’s trying to do her homework.” </p><p>“The hole in the sidewalk wasn’t really dangerous, but it was a NUISANCE for us to have to walk around it all the time.” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Complaint</i> is the most popular wrong answer. A NUISANCE is likely to cause people to complain, but is not the <i class=“def-ital\">complaint</i> itself.</p>"
            },
            "LOYAL": {
              "word": "LOYAL",
              "phonetic": "(loy'-ÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">faithful, true, devoted </p><p>To be LOYAL is to be devoted or faithful to a person, cause, or ideal. </p><p>“The brave soldier was LOYAL to his country and would not reveal military secrets even under torture.” </p><p>“The LOYAL dog jumped into the river to save its drowning master.” </p><p>LOYALTY, the noun form of the word, is the quality of being faithful. </p><p>“We admired the child’s constant LOYALTY to her aged father.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: LOYALTY, n.</p>"
            },
            "POSSESS": {
              "word": "POSSESS",
              "phonetic": "(pÔøΩzes')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to have, own </p><p>To POSSESS something is to <i class=“def-ital\">have</i> it. </p><p>“She POSSESSES great wealth.” </p><p>“He POSSESSES a lot of charm.” </p><p>“This coin POSSESSES little value.” </p><p>POSSESSION is the owning or having of something. </p><p>“He came into POSSESSION of the painting.” </p><p>POSSESSIONS are things which someone has. </p><p>“All her POSSESSIONS were destroyed in the fire.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: POSSESSION, n. </p><p>POSSESSIVE, adj.</p>"
            },
            "DISTRESS": {
              "word": "DISTRESS",
              "phonetic": "(dis-tres')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to trouble, upset, disturb, bother </p><p>To DISTRESS someone is to cause him pain or sorrow. </p><p>“It DISTRESSES me to see you so unhappy.” </p><p>“She was DISTRESSED by the news of her husband’s disappearance.” </p><p>“We have received DISTRESSING news about an air- plane crash.” </p><p>DISTRESS is also a noun, meaning suffering or <i class=“def-ital\">misfortune</i>. “The ship radioed that it was in DISTRESS and was in danger of sinking.\"</p><p> “He tried to relieve Susan’s DISTRESS by telling her that everything would turn out all right in the end.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: DISTRESSING, adj.</p>"
            },
            "PRECIOUS": {
              "word": "PRECIOUS",
              "phonetic": "(presh'-ÔøΩs)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">valuable, costly, priceless, dear </p><p>PRECIOUS is related to the word <i class=“def-ital\">price</i>. Something that is PRECIOUS has a high price, is of great value. </p><p>“These PRECIOUS jewels are worth a fortune to us.” </p><p>PRECIOUS is also used about things which are of such value that they have no price. </p><p>“My children are PRECIOUS to me. I wouldn’t do anything to harm them.” </p><p>“We have a few PRECIOUS hours in which to find the bomb before it goes off.” </p><p>Many people choose <i class=“def-ital\">rare</i> as the right answer. Often something is PRECIOUS because it is <i class=“def-ital\">rare</i>, but the two words do not have the same meaning.</p>"
            },
            "PURSUE": {
              "word": "PURSUE",
              "phonetic": "(pÔøΩr-sU')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to chase, follow, go after </p><p>To PURSUE something is to follow after it. You can PURSUE anything: a car, a person, success, happiness, and so on. </p><p>“The police PVRSUED the escaped prisoner.” </p><p>“He was PURSUED by shouts as he left the meeting.” </p><p>“All people should have the right to PURSUE happiness.” </p><p>PURSUIT is the noun from PURSUE. </p><p>“Everyone joined in the PURSUIT of the criminal.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: PURSUIT, n.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "7",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "They PROTEST the decision.",
                  "answers": [
                    "hate",
                    "agree with",
                    "ask for",
                    "object to",
                    "forget"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROTEST",
                  "correct": "object to"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They kept him ISOLATED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "quiet",
                    "unhappy",
                    "nearby",
                    "warm",
                    "alone"
                  ],
                  "word": "ISOLATED",
                  "correct": "alone"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEDICATED people.",
                  "answers": [
                    "disloyal",
                    "intelligent",
                    "displeased",
                    "devoted",
                    "obedient"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEDICATED",
                  "correct": "devoted"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FLAWLESS performance.",
                  "answers": [
                    "perfect",
                    "suitable",
                    "illegal",
                    "bad",
                    "unbelievable"
                  ],
                  "word": "FLAWLESS",
                  "correct": "perfect"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISRUPT the meeting.",
                  "answers": [
                    "break up",
                    "shock",
                    "avoid",
                    "arrange",
                    "call off"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISRUPT",
                  "correct": "break up"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FULFILL the obligation.",
                  "answers": [
                    "forget",
                    "accept",
                    "complete",
                    "add to",
                    "put off"
                  ],
                  "word": "FULFILL",
                  "correct": "complete"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "A HORDE of them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "dozen",
                    "crowd",
                    "few",
                    "bag",
                    "pair"
                  ],
                  "word": "HORDE",
                  "correct": "crowd"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INTERNAL signs.",
                  "answers": [
                    "outside",
                    "invisible",
                    "obvious",
                    "inner",
                    "necessary"
                  ],
                  "word": "INTERNAL",
                  "correct": "inner"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The JUNCTION of the rivers.",
                  "answers": [
                    "end",
                    "width",
                    "dividing",
                    "beginning",
                    "joining"
                  ],
                  "word": "JUNCTION",
                  "correct": "joining"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "General NUISANCE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "help",
                    "knowledge",
                    "bother",
                    "complaint",
                    "evil"
                  ],
                  "word": "NUISANCE",
                  "correct": "bother"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "LOYAL men.",
                  "answers": [
                    "smart",
                    "faithful",
                    "funny",
                    "noble",
                    "brave"
                  ],
                  "word": "LOYAL",
                  "correct": "faithful"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They POSSESS little.",
                  "answers": [
                    "have",
                    "advance",
                    "need",
                    "spend",
                    "lose"
                  ],
                  "word": "POSSESS",
                  "correct": "have"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It will DISTRESS him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "change",
                    "kill",
                    "trouble",
                    "tire",
                    "thrill"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISTRESS",
                  "correct": "trouble"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PRECIOUS things.",
                  "answers": [
                    "pretty",
                    "rare",
                    "new",
                    "valuable",
                    "useless"
                  ],
                  "word": "PRECIOUS",
                  "correct": "valuable"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Will they PURSUE us?",
                  "answers": [
                    "find",
                    "chase",
                    "fight",
                    "lead",
                    "promise"
                  ],
                  "word": "PURSUE",
                  "correct": "chase"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually PROTEST when they win a prize?",
                  "word": "PROTEST",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "When a mother kisses her baby, is she ISOLATING it?",
                  "word": "ISOLATED",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a DEDICATED teacher be likely to spend extra time helping her students?",
                  "word": "DEDICATED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would an artist like to paint a FLAWLESS picture?",
                  "word": "FLAWLESS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would the noise of a jackhammer DISRUPT a concert?",
                  "word": "DISRUPT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "If you keep a promise, have you FULFILLED it?",
                  "word": "FULFILL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a HORDE usually be peaceful and friendly?",
                  "word": "HORDE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is your hair an INTERNAL part of you?",
                  "word": "INTERNAL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Could your wrist be called the JUNCTION between your hand and your arm?",
                  "word": "JUNCTION",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people like NUISANCES?",
                  "word": "NUISANCE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a boss want to hire workers who would be LOYAL to the company?",
                  "word": "LOYAL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a person POSSESS a sense of humor?",
                  "word": "POSSESS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it DISTRESSING to win a race?",
                  "word": "DISTRESS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are most pencils PRECIOUS?",
                  "word": "PRECIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do you always catch something that you PURSUE?",
                  "word": "PURSUE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {}
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "They PROTESTED that there wasn't enough time to do what he wanted them to do.",
                  "word": "PROTEST",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Hermits are people who avoid the company of others and would rather be ISOLATED.",
                  "word": "ISOLATED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The mayor DEDICATED the new city hall to the people of the city.",
                  "word": "DEDICATED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Jack made only a couple of mistakes in his FLAWLESS performance.",
                  "word": "FLAWLESS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The volcano looked like it was going to DISRUPT at any minute.",
                  "word": "DISRUPT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He FULFILLED the cup to overflowing.",
                  "word": "FULFILL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The sudden arrival of HORDES of insects ruined the barbecue.",
                  "word": "HORDE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Bob opened up the machine to get at its INTERNAL parts.",
                  "word": "INTERNAL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "This set of railroad tracks had many JUNCTIONS with other sets of tracks.",
                  "word": "JUNCTION",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The dog became such a NUISANCE that finally we had to give it away.",
                  "word": "NUISANCE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Benedict Arnold showed his LOYALTY to the United States by giving secrets to the British.",
                  "word": "LOYAL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He POSSESSED a magic ring that could make him invisible.",
                  "word": "POSSESS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The teacher DISTRESSED to them the importance of studying hard.",
                  "word": "DISTRESS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His weekends are PRECIOUS to him. He won't let anyone disturb them.",
                  "word": "PRECIOUS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He didn't care whom he hurt in his PURSUIT of great wealth.",
                  "word": "PURSUE",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "PROTEST",
                  "answers": [
                    "give up",
                    "complain",
                    "disapprove"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROTEST",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ISOLATED",
                  "answers": [
                    "apart",
                    "different",
                    "alone"
                  ],
                  "word": "ISOLATED",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEDICATED",
                  "answers": [
                    "committed",
                    "smart",
                    "determined"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEDICATED",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FLAWLESS",
                  "answers": [
                    "errorless",
                    "difficult",
                    "perfect"
                  ],
                  "word": "FLAWLESS",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISRUPT",
                  "answers": [
                    "stop",
                    "destroy",
                    "dislike"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISRUPT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FULFILL",
                  "answers": [
                    "complete",
                    "excite",
                    "satisfy"
                  ],
                  "word": "FULFILL",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HORDE",
                  "answers": [
                    "crowd",
                    "mob",
                    "criminal"
                  ],
                  "word": "HORDE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INTERNAL",
                  "answers": [
                    "inner",
                    "everlasting",
                    "hidden"
                  ],
                  "word": "INTERNAL",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "JUNCTION",
                  "answers": [
                    "meeting",
                    "connection",
                    "difference"
                  ],
                  "word": "JUNCTION",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "NUISANCE",
                  "answers": [
                    "trouble",
                    "anger",
                    "obstacle"
                  ],
                  "word": "NUISANCE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "LOYAL",
                  "answers": [
                    "united",
                    "faithful",
                    "devoted"
                  ],
                  "word": "LOYAL",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "POSSESS",
                  "answers": [
                    "need",
                    "own",
                    "buy"
                  ],
                  "word": "POSSESS",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISTRESS",
                  "answers": [
                    "silence",
                    "sorrow",
                    "pain"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISTRESS",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PRECIOUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "important",
                    "old",
                    "expensive"
                  ],
                  "word": "PRECIOUS",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PURSUE",
                  "answers": [
                    "seek",
                    "follow",
                    "choose"
                  ],
                  "word": "PURSUE",
                  "correct": "2"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.8",
          "definitions": {
            "TORMENT": {
              "word": "TORMENT",
              "phonetic": "(tor'-ment)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">great pain, agony, suffering </p><p>TORMENT is great pain and suffering.</p><p>“We could tell that our cat was in TORMENT because every few minutes he would give a great cry of pain.\"</p><p> Mental suffering can also be TORMENT. </p><p>“The missing boy’s parents were in TORMENT.” </p><p>TORMENT is also a verb which means “to cause great pain to,” to torture. As a verb the word is pronounced torment’ or torment. </p><p>“He was TORMENTED by a severe headache.” </p><p>Sometimes it simply means to annoy. </p><p>“He constantly teases and TORMENTS his sister.”</p>"
            },
            "SLACKEN": {
              "word": "SLACKEN",
              "phonetic": "(slak'-ÔøΩn)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to slow down; to make looser </p><p>SLACKEN means to <i class=“def-ital\">slow down</i>. </p><p>“The runner SLACKENED his pace when his leg began to hurt.” </p><p>“We enjoyed being on the beach once the wind SLACKENED.” SLACKEN is also used to mean “to make looser.” </p><p>“The horse was easier to control after Bill learned to SLACKEN the reins.\"</p><p> The adjective form of SLACKEN is SLACK, which means “not busy, or not tense or taut.” </p><p>“It was a SLACK season for his business; few customers came to his shop.” </p><p>“The rope was SLACK; it hung loosely from the sail.” </p><p>SLACK is also a noun. </p><p>“There was some SLACK in the rope.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: SLACK, adj., n.</p>"
            },
            "QUALIFIED": {
              "word": "QUALIFIED",
              "phonetic": "(kwo'-lÔøΩfld)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">suited, fit, competent; limited, restricted </p><p>To QUALIFY a person is to make him fit for something like a job or an award. </p><p>“Your score on the test QUALIFIES you for a prize.” </p><p>Someone who is QUALIFIED, therefore, is fit or competent for something. </p><p>“Both of them were well QUALIFIED for the job.” </p><p>“Only QUALIFIED experts should work with bombs.” </p><p>“He wasn’t QUALIFIED to run in the race because he didn’t enter on time.” </p><p>Another meaning of QUALIFIED is <i class=“def-ital\">limited, restricted</i>. To give your “QUALIFIED approval” to something is to approve it with some limitations, not wholeheartedly. </p><p>Other forms of the word: QUALIFICATION, n. </p><p>QUALIFY, v.</p>"
            },
            "RESTRAIN": {
              "word": "RESTRAIN",
              "phonetic": "(ri-strAn')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to hold back, curb, limit, restrict </p><p>To RESTRAIN someone is to hold him back from doing something. See <i class=“def-ital\">re-</i> under Prefixes. </p><p>“We held on to Bill to RESTRAIN him from hitting the other boy.” </p><p>“It was difficult for him to RESTRAIN his temper. He got angry very easily.” </p><p>“She could not RESTRAIN a smile at the child’s question.” </p><p>RESTRAINT is the noun from RESTRAIN. A RESTRAINT is something that holds you back. </p><p>“The prisoner hated the RESTRAINTS that had been placed on his freedom.” </p><p>RESTRAINT is also the act of holding back. </p><p>“We must exercise RESTRAINT in eating the cookies” -that is, we must hold back our desire to eat too many of them. </p><p>Other forms of the word: RESTRAINT, n.</p>"
            },
            "SLUMBER": {
              "word": "SLUMBER",
              "phonetic": "(sluhm'-bÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">sleep SLUMBER means sleep, usually peaceful sleep. </p><p>SLUMBER can be used as either a noun or a verb. </p><p>“The baby is quietly SLUMBERING in his crib.” </p><p>“As soon as the medicine took effect, he fell into a deep SLUMBER.” </p><p>“He lay in peaceful SLUMBER, unaware of the noise.”</p>"
            },
            "CONSUME": {
              "word": "CONSUME",
              "phonetic": "(kan-sUm')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to use up; to eat; to destroy</p><p>CONSUME means to <i class=“def-ital\">use up</i>, so that there is nothing left. </p><p>“By the end of the winter all the firewood we had cut was CONSUMED.” </p><p>“Her pay is CONSUMED by the necessary things like food and rent, so there’s nothing left over for fun.” </p><p>CONSUME also means to <i class=“def-ital\">eat</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">drink</i>; in other words, to <i class=“def-ital\">use up</i> food. </p><p>“We CONSUMED the meal in complete silence.” </p><p>“The guests at the party CONSUMED two cases of soft drinks.” </p><p>In a slightly different sense, CONSUME can mean to <i class=“def-ital\">destroy</i>. “Our house and all our belongings were CONSUMED in the fire.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: CONSUMER, n.</p>"
            },
            "SUMMON": {
              "word": "SUMMON",
              "phonetic": "(suhm'-an)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to send for, call together, call forth </p><p>To SUMMON someone is to send for him, to ask or require him to come. The word usually suggests that the re- quest is urgent, or that the person doing the SUMMONING is powerful and not to be disobeyed. </p><p>“The king SUMMONED all the noblemen to his castle.” </p><p>“The ringing of the bell SUMMONED them to their next class.” </p><p>To SUMMON <i class=“def-ital\">up</i> something is to call it forth. </p><p>“She tried to SUMMON up a smile, but she was just too unhappy.” </p><p>In law, a SUMMONS is a notice ordering a person to appear in court. </p><p>“When the witness didn’t appear in court, the judge is- sued a SUMMONS requiring him to come.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: SUMMONS, n.</p>"
            },
            "TOLERATE": {
              "word": "TOLERATE",
              "phonetic": "(tol-'a-rAt)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to bear, stand, put up with, endure </p><p>TOLERATE means to <i class=“def-ital\">bea</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">put up with</i>. The word suggests that you don’t like something, but you endure it because you have to, or because it’s not bad enough to make you resist it. </p><p>“Harry doesn’t like children, but he TOLERATES them when he’s visiting friends who have children.” </p><p>“She couldn’t TOLERATE having the puppy jump up on her.” </p><p>People who TOLERATE things are called TOLERANT. </p><p>“He’s very TOLERANT of little mistakes, but she yells about everything.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: TOLERANCE, n. </p><p>TOLERANT, adj.</p>"
            },
            "UNSETTLE": {
              "word": "UNSETTLE",
              "phonetic": "(uhn-set'-al)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to disturb, make troubled, make uncertain </p><p>One meaning of the verb SETTLE is to <i class=“def-ital\">calm</i>. </p><p>“This medicine will SETTLE your stomach if you are not feeling well.” </p><p>UNSETTLE is the opposite of SETTLE used in this sense. See <i class=“def-ital\">un-</i> under Prefixes. To UNSETTLE is to make someone or something disturbed or disordered. </p><p>“Monica’s attitude of superiority UNSETTLED Julia.” </p><p>“The UNSETTLED conditions at the end of the war eventually calmed down during the years of peace that followed.” </p><p>“Her final remark was very UNSETTLING. He worried about it all the way home.”</p>"
            },
            "VOW": {
              "word": "VOW",
              "phonetic": "(vow)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a promise, oath </p><p>A VOW is a solemn promise or oath, often taken in some kind of ceremony. </p><p>“He made a solemn VOW to find the person who had killed her.” </p><p>“She took a VOW of secrecy when she joined the club.” VOW is also a verb meaning to <i class=“def-ital\">promise</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">swear</i>. “We VOW to be true to one another forever.” </p><p>“Scarlett VOWED that she would never go hungry again.”</p>"
            },
            "CRISIS": {
              "word": "CRISIS",
              "phonetic": "(krl'-sis)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an emergency, climax, turning point</p><p> CRISIS comes from a Greek word meaning <i class=“def-ital\">decision</i>. A CRISIS is a point at which what happens in the future, good or bad, is decided. In medicine, for example, a CRI- SIS is the turning point in a serious disease, when the patient either starts to get better or dies. </p><p>“There was a political CRISIS in that country. No one knew who the next ruler would be.\"</p><p>“She was in the middle of a personal CRISIS then. Her husband was deciding whether he wanted a divorce.” </p><p>“That was quite a CRISIS. I’m glad things worked out all right.”</p>"
            },
            "EPISODE": {
              "word": "EPISODE",
              "phonetic": "(ep'-ÔøΩsOd)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an incident, scene, occurrence, one of a series of events </p><p>An EPISODE is a scene, incident, or story which is com- plete and interesting in itself, but which is also part of a larger story or series of events. </p><p>“The play had some exciting EPISODES, but in general was not very good.” </p><p>“It was not a very pleasant EPISODE in his career.” </p><p>Single programs in a television series are called EPISODES because they are complete by themselves, but are also part of the entire series. </p><p>Other forms of the word: EPISODIC, adj.</p>"
            },
            "WEARY": {
              "word": "WEARY",
              "phonetic": "(wEr'-E)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">tired, worn out </p><p>WEARY means just about the same as <i class=“def-ital\">tired</i>, although it is a little stronger and suggests someone who has lost most of his energy or his interest. </p><p>“After the fifty mile march the soldiers were WEARY and ready for bed.” </p><p>“We were all WEARY by the time we had finished cleaning the house.” </p><p>WEARY is often followed by of. </p><p>“I am getting very WEARY of people always yelling at me.” </p><p>WEARY is also a verb, meaning to tire or become tired. </p><p>“They began to WEARY of the noise and confusion of city life.” </p><p>Unhappy</i> is often chosen as the meaning of WEARY in the Pretest. Someone can be both physically WEARY and happy, though. </p><p>“The team was WEARY after the long game, but happy because they had won.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: WEARINESS, n.</p>"
            },
            "WOE": {
              "word": "WOE",
              "phonetic": "(wO)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">sorrow, trouble, grief </p><p>WOE is deep sorrow or misery. </p><p>“The field was a scene of WOE after the battle.” </p><p>In a related sense, a WOE is also a cause of sorrow or suffering, a <i class=“def-ital\">trouble</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">misfortune</i>. </p><p>“His WOES began when he fell and broke his leg.” </p><p>“She complained for hours about all the WOES of her life.” </p><p>The adjective form of WOE is WOEFUL. WOEFUL can mean unhappy. </p><p>“Jane had a WOEFUL look on her face when she heard the bad news.” </p><p>WOEFUL can also mean “of very poor quality,” <i class=“def-ital\">wretched</i>. </p><p>“This house is in WOEFUL condition. It needs a lot of work.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: WOEFUL, adj.</p>"
            },
            "COMPLIMENT": {
              "word": "COMPLIMENT",
              "phonetic": "(kom'-plÔøΩmÔøΩnt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">praise </p><p>A COMPLIMENT is a polite expression of praise or approval. When you tell people that you admire them or ap- prove of what they’re doing, you are giving them a COMPLIMENT. </p><p>“She received several COMPLIMENTS from her friends about her new dress.” </p><p>COMPLIMENT is also a verb and means “to express approval of or to give praise to.” As a verb the word is pronounced kom’-pl;)-ment. </p><p>“The teacher COMPLIMENTED him for raising his grade in French.” </p><p>“She COMPLIMENTED the way we cleaned the house. </p><p>Other forms of the word COMPLIMENTARY, adj.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "8",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Stopped the TORMENT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "singing",
                    "good times",
                    "flood",
                    "bleeding",
                    "great pain"
                  ],
                  "word": "TORMENT",
                  "correct": "great pain"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Production will SLACKEN.",
                  "answers": [
                    "slow down",
                    "start",
                    "stop",
                    "go on",
                    "speed up"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLACKEN",
                  "correct": "slow down"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They are both QUALIFIED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "expected",
                    "undesirable",
                    "educated",
                    "suited",
                    "satisfied"
                  ],
                  "word": "QUALIFIED",
                  "correct": "suited"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "RESTRAINED the dog.",
                  "answers": [
                    "led in",
                    "taught",
                    "held back",
                    "found",
                    "pulled out"
                  ],
                  "word": "RESTRAIN",
                  "correct": "held back"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Peaceful SLUMBER.",
                  "answers": [
                    "dream",
                    "sleep",
                    "morning",
                    "forest",
                    "walk"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLUMBER",
                  "correct": "sleep"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CONSUMED some of it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "increased",
                    "lost",
                    "reduced",
                    "used up",
                    "lied about"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONSUME",
                  "correct": "used up"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They will SUMMON him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "remember",
                    "talk about",
                    "visit",
                    "send for",
                    "need"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUMMON",
                  "correct": "send for"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can anyone TOLERATE him?",
                  "answers": [
                    "hate",
                    "calm",
                    "persuade",
                    "like",
                    "bear"
                  ],
                  "word": "TOLERATE",
                  "correct": "bear"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "UNSETTLED conditions.",
                  "answers": [
                    "unusual",
                    "disturbed",
                    "evil",
                    "quiet",
                    "crowded"
                  ],
                  "word": "UNSETTLE",
                  "correct": "disturbed"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Reminded him of his VOW.",
                  "answers": [
                    "religion",
                    "decision",
                    "past",
                    "promise",
                    "quarrel"
                  ],
                  "word": "VOW",
                  "correct": "promise"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "During the CRISIS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "battle",
                    "emergency",
                    "vacation",
                    "illness",
                    "argument"
                  ],
                  "word": "CRISIS",
                  "correct": "emergency"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Another EPISODE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "attempt",
                    "comedy",
                    "decision",
                    "moment",
                    "incident"
                  ],
                  "word": "EPISODE",
                  "correct": "incident"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "So WEARY.",
                  "answers": [
                    "old",
                    "unhappy",
                    "tired",
                    "uncertain",
                    "fresh"
                  ],
                  "word": "WEARY",
                  "correct": "tired"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Her tale of WOE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "sorrow",
                    "war",
                    "happiness",
                    "danger",
                    "death"
                  ],
                  "word": "WOE",
                  "correct": "sorrow"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Unexpected COMPLIMENT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "failure",
                    "result",
                    "blame",
                    "praise",
                    "friendship"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMPLIMENT",
                  "correct": "praise"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Are people happy to be in TORMENT?",
                  "word": "TORMENT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a runner's speed SLACKEN as he tried to win a race?",
                  "word": "SLACKEN",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a high school student QUALIFIED to be president of the United States?",
                  "word": "QUALIFIED",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Should someone who wants to commit murder be RESTRAINED?",
                  "word": "RESTRAIN",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people usually SLUMBER at night?",
                  "word": "SLUMBER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a fat person usually CONSUME a lot of food?",
                  "word": "CONSUME",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Could a principal SUMMON a student to his office?",
                  "word": "SUMMON",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do TOLERANT people get angry easily?",
                  "word": "TOLERATE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would seeing a ghost UNSETTLE a person?",
                  "word": "UNSETTLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it possible to break a VOW?",
                  "word": "VOW",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would people be worried during a CRISIS?",
                  "word": "CRISIS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Could there be several EPISODES in a novel?",
                  "word": "EPISODE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would most people be WEARY after running ten miles?",
                  "word": "WEARY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a playful kitten full of WOE?",
                  "word": "WOE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do most people like to receive a COMPLIMENT?",
                  "word": "COMPLIMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Pat was TORMENTED by the thought that he would soon have to take the test.",
                  "word": "TORMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She SLACKENED them for not trying hard enough.",
                  "word": "SLACKEN",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We felt that she was QUALIFIED for the job as an interpreter because she spoke French perfectly.",
                  "word": "QUALIFIED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Gail disliked any RESTRAINTS on her activity. She wanted to do as she pleased.",
                  "word": "RESTRAIN",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The car SLUMBERED to a stop by the side of the road.",
                  "word": "SLUMBER",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The climb up the mountain CONSUMED all our energy.",
                  "word": "CONSUME",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Cindy SUMMONED up all her remaining strength for the last mile of the race.",
                  "word": "SUMMON",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I simply cannot TOLERATE cigarette smoke.",
                  "word": "TOLERATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She was UNSETTLED by the news that she might lose her job.",
                  "word": "UNSETTLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They received a beautiful blue VOW for a wedding present.",
                  "word": "VOW",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He survived one CRISIS after another during his career.",
                  "word": "CRISIS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He called the Civil War one of the saddest EPISODES in American history.",
                  "word": "EPISODE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Carla quickly began to WEARY of her dull job at the factory.",
                  "word": "WEARY",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Her WOEFUL look told us that she was deeply unhappy.",
                  "word": "WOE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Dick didn't think she meant it when she COMPLIMENTED him. He felt she was just praising him to make him feel better.",
                  "word": "COMPLIMENT",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "TORMENT",
                  "answers": [
                    "delay",
                    "pain",
                    "worry"
                  ],
                  "word": "TORMENT",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SLACKEN",
                  "answers": [
                    "loosen",
                    "slow",
                    "fasten"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLACKEN",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "QUALIFIED",
                  "answers": [
                    "competent",
                    "unusual",
                    "limited"
                  ],
                  "word": "QUALIFIED",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "RESTRAIN",
                  "answers": [
                    "stop",
                    "limit",
                    "try"
                  ],
                  "word": "RESTRAIN",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SLUMBER",
                  "answers": [
                    "sleep",
                    "nightmare",
                    "rest"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLUMBER",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CONSUME",
                  "answers": [
                    "eat",
                    "use up",
                    "throw away"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONSUME",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SUMMON",
                  "answers": [
                    "leave",
                    "call for",
                    "bring"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUMMON",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TOLERATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "suffer",
                    "endure",
                    "reject"
                  ],
                  "word": "TOLERATE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "UNSETTLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "bother",
                    "confuse",
                    "enjoy"
                  ],
                  "word": "UNSETTLE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "VOW",
                  "answers": [
                    "promise",
                    "guarantee",
                    "reminder"
                  ],
                  "word": "VOW",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CRISIS",
                  "answers": [
                    "pain",
                    "climax",
                    "decision"
                  ],
                  "word": "CRISIS",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EPISODE",
                  "answers": [
                    "event",
                    "problem",
                    "scene"
                  ],
                  "word": "EPISODE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "WEARY",
                  "answers": [
                    "sleepy",
                    "weak",
                    "tiny"
                  ],
                  "word": "WEARY",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "WOE",
                  "answers": [
                    "sadness",
                    "trouble",
                    "danger"
                  ],
                  "word": "WOE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "COMPLIMENT",
                  "answers": [
                    "approve",
                    "admire",
                    "expect"
                  ],
                  "word": "COMPLIMENT",
                  "correct": "2"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.9",
          "definitions": {
            "STRIVE": {
              "word": "STRIVE",
              "phonetic": "(strlv)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to attempt, contend, struggle </p><p>To STRIVE is to put out great effort or energy in working or competing. The word suggests that what you are trying to do is difficult and that there are obstacles in the way of success. </p><p>“We must all STRIVE to do the best job we can.” </p><p>“They STROVE against impossible odds to reach the trapped miners.” </p><p>“The two of them STROVE to see who would win the prize.” </p><p>“You should STRIVE to understand the other person’s point of view.” </p><p>Usage: The past tense of STRIVE is STROVE.</p>"
            },
            "IMPULSE": {
              "word": "IMPULSE",
              "phonetic": "(im'-puhls)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an urge, sudden desire </p><p>The basic meaning of IMPULSE is a <i class=“def-ital\">push</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">thrust</i>. When used about people, it refers to an urge or feeling which pushes someone to act in a certain way. </p><p>“He is always helping people. He has an IMPULSE to do good.” </p><p>The word usually suggests that this urge or feeling is sudden and not thought out. </p><p>“He decided on an IMPULSE to take a trip to Hawaii.” </p><p>“He acts on IMPULSE and regrets it later.” </p><p>Someone who is always acting on IMPULSE is IMPULSIVE. </p><p>“She is an IMPULSIVE shopper. If something looks good to her, she buys it right away.” </p><p>ssOther forms of the word: IMPULSIVE, adj.</p>"
            },
            "DETECT": {
              "word": "DETECT",
              "phonetic": "(di-tekt')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to discover, find, find out </p><p>To DETECT something is to discover it, to find out that it exists or is present. </p><p>“You can’t DETECT these germs unless you look through a microscope.\"</p><p>“She DETECTED the odor of leaking gas in the basement.” </p><p>“Didn’t you DETECT something wrong in the way he was walking?” </p><p>A DETECTIVE is someone whose job is to uncover facts about a person or an event. DETECTION is the act of DETECTING. </p><p>“Early DETECTION of the disease enables doctors to cure it completely.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: DETECTION, n. DETECTIVE, n.</p>"
            },
            "DISREGARD": {
              "word": "DISREGARD",
              "phonetic": "(dis-ri-gahrd')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to ignore, neglect </p><p>To regard something is to notice it, to pay attention to it. To DISREGARD something is to pay no attention or give no thought to it. See <i class=“def-ital\">dis-</i> under Prefixes. </p><p>“He DISREGARDED his own safety in order to save the others.” </p><p>“She DISREGARDED the ‘No Trespassing’ sign and went into the building anyway.” </p><p>“We DISREGARDED the other team’s insults.” </p><p>DISREGARD is also a noun, meaning “lack of attention,” neglect. </p><p>“The rude stranger showed a complete DISREGARD for the rights of others.”</p>"
            },
            "HARNESS": {
              "word": "HARNESS",
              "phonetic": "(hahr'-nÔøΩs",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">hahr’-nis) v.: to put to work, use, control </p><p>A HARNESS is the equipment which is put on a horse to attach him to a wagon or plow so that he can pull it. Thus, to HARNESS something is to get control of it so that you can put it to work for you. “Will we be able to HARNESS the energy of the sun?” </p><p>“He was a good writer, but he could never quite HARNESS his wild imagination.” </p><p>“They HARNESSED the power of the waterfall to produce cheap electricity.”</p>"
            },
            "DISSECT": {
              "word": "DISSECT",
              "phonetic": "(di-sekt')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to cut apart, examine, analyze </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">dis-</i> under Prefixes. The <i class=“def-ital\">sec</i> part of DISSECT comes from a Latin word meaning to<i class=“def-ital\">cut</i>. It is also found in words like intersect and section. DISSECT means to cut apart, especially the parts of an animal or plant in order to study them. </p><p>“In biology class we had to DISSECT a frog in order to learn about the workings of the body.” </p><p>In a broader sense, DISSECT can mean “to examine and analyze in detail,” the way a scientist would in DISSECTING an animal. </p><p>“The critic DISSECTED the author’s theory and showed just how silly it was.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: DISSECTION, n.</p>"
            },
            "INFURIATE": {
              "word": "INFURIATE",
              "phonetic": "(in-fyUr'-E-At)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to anger, enrage, madden </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">in-</i> under Prefixes, and <i class=“def-ital\">-ate</i> under Suffixes. FURY is violent anger, rage. To INFURIATE someone is to fill him with FURY. </p><p>“The coach’s decision to cut Bill from the team INFU- RIATED him.” </p><p>“I am INFURIATED by people who don’t know what they are doing.”</p>"
            },
            "MOBILE": {
              "word": "MOBILE",
              "phonetic": "(mO'-bÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">able to move or change easily </p><p>MOBILE means “able to move quickly or easily.” </p><p>A MOBILE home is a house which can be moved from place to place. </p><p>“They put wheels on the table so that it would be more MOBILE.” </p><p>“Their repair crews were very MOBILE. They could go to any part of the country on a moment’s notice.” </p><p>The noun from MOBILE is MOBILITY. </p><p>“She has lost all her MOBILITY since she broke her ankle.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: MOBILITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "SOOTHE": {
              "word": "SOOTHE",
              "phonetic": "(sUTH)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to calm, quiet, comfort, relieve </p><p>SOOTHE means “to give relief or comfort to,” to calm or quiet. You can SOOTHE a sorrow or a physical pain. </p><p>“She SOOTHED the sick child with a lullaby.” </p><p>“Cough drops help to SOOTHE a sore throat.” </p><p>“He found that listening to music helped to SOOTHE his mind.” </p><p>“He SOOTHED the nervous horse by speaking quietly and calmly.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: SOOTHING, adj.</p>"
            },
            "MOURN": {
              "word": "MOURN",
              "phonetic": "(morn)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to feel sorrow, grieve </p><p>To MOURN is to feel a deep sorrow, often over a person’s death. </p><p>“Everyone MOURNED when they heard he had died.” </p><p>“The team MOURNED the loss of its captain.” </p><p>You can MOURN other things besides death. </p><p>“He MOURNED the passing of so many nice old customs.” </p><p>MOURNING is the act of someone who MOURNS. To be in MOURNING is to feel deep sorrow and to express it by wearing black clothing, for example, or by flying flags at half mast. </p><p>“The whole nation was in MOURNING when the President died.\"</p><p> The most commonly chosen wrong answer in the Pretest is <i class=“def-ital\">complain</i>. <i class=“def-ital\">Complain</i> is used about things that annoy you; MOURN would only be used about events that cause you great unhappiness. </p><p>Other forms of the word: MOURNING, n.</p>"
            },
            "STABLE": {
              "word": "STABLE",
              "phonetic": "(stA'-bÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">solid, firm, steady Something that is </p><p>STABLE is unlikely to move; it is so firmly fixed in place that it is hard to change. STABLE is used about things and qualities. </p><p>“His house was so STABLE and well built that it survived the earthquake.” </p><p>“The price of meat remained STABLE for some time.” </p><p>“She was a very STABLE person. You could count on her never to do anything foolish or unexpected.” </p><p>The verb form of STABLE is STABILIZE. To STABILIZE means to make or become steady. </p><p>“The government tried to STABILIZE prices.” </p><p>“They developed a new way of STABILIZING small boats.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: STABILIZE, v. </p><p>STABILITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "SWINDLE": {
              "word": "SWINDLE",
              "phonetic": "(swin'-dÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to cheat, trick </p><p>To SWINDLE someone is to <i class=“def-ital\">cheat <i class=“def-ital\">or <i class=“def-ital\">trick</i> him in order to get money. </p><p>“The investors were SWINDLED out of thousands of dollars by the scheme.” </p><p>“Confidence men make their living by SWINDLING unsuspecting people.” </p><p>SWINDLE is also a noun which means “an act of cheating, trickery, or fraud.” </p><p>“He was involved in a SWINDLE which cheated many people out of their hard-earned money.”</p>"
            },
            "ABUNDANT": {
              "word": "ABUNDANT",
              "phonetic": "(ÔøΩbuhn'-dÔøΩnt)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">plentiful </p><p>ABUNDANT means “more than enough,” <i class=“def-ital\">plentiful</i>. </p><p>“We have an ABUNDANT supply of food in the cabin for the winter.” </p><p>“There is ABUNDANT rain in this area; it’s good farmland.” </p><p>The noun form, ABUNDANCE, means a <i class=“def-ital\">great supply, plenty</i>. </p><p>“The library has an ABUNDANCE of books.” </p><p>“There used to be an ABUNDANCE offish in this river; now there are none.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ABUNDANCE, n.</p>"
            },
            "STRIDE": {
              "word": "STRIDE",
              "phonetic": "(strld)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a long step </p><p>A STRIDE is a single long step. A STRIDE is also the distance covered in a long step. </p><p>“He crossed the room in several STRIDES.” </p><p>“They were only a few STRIDES away from the finish line.” </p><p>STRIDE is also a verb. To STRIDE is to take long steps, especially in an energetic manner. </p><p>“They STRIDE quickly through the dark streets.” </p><p>“Yesterday he STRODE up to the teacher and asked to speak with her.” </p><p>The most commonly chosen incorrect answer is <i class=“def-ital\">leap</i>, which is close to the meaning of STRIDE, but not the same. </p><p>Usage: The past tense of STRIDE is STRODE.</p>"
            },
            "TRIBUTE": {
              "word": "TRIBUTE",
              "phonetic": "(trib'-yUt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an honor, gift; payment, taxation </p><p>A TRIBUTE is an honor or gift given to somebody to show respect or give thanks. </p><p>“With a charming speech, she accepted the TRIBUTE to her skill.” </p><p>“This statue is a TRIBUTE to the memory of soldiers who have fallen in war.” </p><p>TRIBUTE is often used in the phrase “to pay TRIBUTE,” which means to <i class=“def-ital\">give honor</i>. </p><p>“We gathered to pay TRIBUTE to the man who founded our company fifty years ago.” </p><p>TRIBUTE also means a kind of payment or taxation a conqueror gets from those he has conquered. “The king set the yearly TRIBUTE from the town at a hundred gold pieces.” </p><p>Usage: TRIBUTE, when it means honor or gift, is usually followed by to.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "9",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "STRIVE to improve.",
                  "answers": [
                    "arrange",
                    "prepare",
                    "fail",
                    "manage",
                    "attempt"
                  ],
                  "word": "STRIVE",
                  "correct": "attempt"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Another IMPULSE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "decision",
                    "sacrifice",
                    "urge",
                    "move",
                    "order"
                  ],
                  "word": "IMPULSE",
                  "correct": "urge"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To DETECT the problem.",
                  "answers": [
                    "cause",
                    "solve",
                    "hide",
                    "discover",
                    "avoid"
                  ],
                  "word": "DETECT",
                  "correct": "discover"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISREGARD them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "protect",
                    "oppose",
                    "notice",
                    "ignore",
                    "insult"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISREGARD",
                  "correct": "ignore"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Tried to HARNESS it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "control",
                    "buy",
                    "destroy",
                    "increase",
                    "loosen"
                  ],
                  "word": "HARNESS",
                  "correct": "control"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISSECT the animal.",
                  "answers": [
                    "cure",
                    "look over",
                    "cut apart",
                    "wash",
                    "kill"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISSECT",
                  "correct": "cut apart"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He INFURIATES me.",
                  "answers": [
                    "injures",
                    "angers",
                    "tolerates",
                    "comforts",
                    "hates"
                  ],
                  "word": "INFURIATE",
                  "correct": "angers"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They are MOBILE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "stuck fast",
                    "angry",
                    "coming soon",
                    "grand",
                    "easily moved"
                  ],
                  "word": "MOBILE",
                  "correct": "easily moved"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Her reply SOOTHED him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "touched",
                    "pleased",
                    "angered",
                    "calmed",
                    "impressed"
                  ],
                  "word": "SOOTHE",
                  "correct": "calmed"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Why do they MOURN?",
                  "answers": [
                    "feel sorrow",
                    "dance",
                    "suffer",
                    "fall asleep",
                    "complain"
                  ],
                  "word": "MOURN",
                  "correct": "feel sorrow"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "STABLE structures.",
                  "answers": [
                    "chief",
                    "solid",
                    "thick",
                    "unsteady",
                    "large"
                  ],
                  "word": "STABLE",
                  "correct": "solid"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They SWINDLED me.",
                  "answers": [
                    "tickled",
                    "attacked",
                    "assisted",
                    "cheated",
                    "covered"
                  ],
                  "word": "SWINOLE",
                  "correct": "cheated"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ABUNDANT ideas.",
                  "answers": [
                    "difficult",
                    "several",
                    "plentiful",
                    "rare",
                    "repeated"
                  ],
                  "word": "ABUNDANT",
                  "correct": "plentiful"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Quick STRIDES.",
                  "answers": [
                    "steps",
                    "cuts",
                    "signals",
                    "leaps",
                    "turns"
                  ],
                  "word": "STRIDE",
                  "correct": "steps"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Unusual TRIBUTE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "honor",
                    "help",
                    "shame",
                    "bravery",
                    "friendship"
                  ],
                  "word": "TRIBUTE",
                  "correct": "honor"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a baseball team STRIVE to win a game?",
                  "word": "STRIVE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does an IMPULSIVE person give careful thought to something before doing it?",
                  "word": "IMPULSE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would it be hard to DETECT an elephant if it were in the same room with you?",
                  "word": "DETECT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a police officer give someone a ticket for DISREGARDING a stop sign?",
                  "word": "DISREGARD",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it possible to HARNESS the power of electricity?",
                  "word": "HARNESS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can only animals be DISSECTED?",
                  "word": "DISSECT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does getting a present INFURIATE most people?",
                  "word": "INFURIATE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a MOBILE person faster than a person who isn't MOBILE?",
                  "word": "MOBILE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would an explosion SOOTHE a nervous person?",
                  "word": "SOOTHE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Could a person MOURN the death of a pet?",
                  "word": "MOURN",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is the ground STABLE during an earthquake?",
                  "word": "STABLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it fun to be SWINDLED?",
                  "word": "SWINOLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is water found in ABUNDANCE in a desert?",
                  "word": "ABUNDANT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do newborn babies know how to STRIDE?",
                  "word": "STRIDE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do you pay TRIBUTE to a person by insulting him?",
                  "word": "TRIBUTE",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Ann STROVE to get there on time, but couldn't quite make it.",
                  "word": "STRIVE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He gave in to the IMPULSE to skip class and go to the ball game.",
                  "word": "IMPULSE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They wanted to DETECT him, but he wouldn't let them inside.",
                  "word": "DETECT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She is honored by all for her devoted DISREGARD for her parents.",
                  "word": "DISREGARD",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The hoodlums HARNESSED us so much that we had to call the police.",
                  "word": "HARNESS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She used soap and water to DISSECT the walls.",
                  "word": "DISSECT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She was INFURIATED at having to miss the circus in order to mind her baby brother.",
                  "word": "INFURIATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Giving all you own to the poor was the most MOBILE thing you could have done.",
                  "word": "MOBILE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He SOOTHED the child's scraped knee with a cold compress.",
                  "word": "SOOTHE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He MOURNED them that no good would come of it.",
                  "word": "MOURN",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They tried to STABILIZE the table by cutting an inch off one of the legs.",
                  "word": "STABLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "At the break of dawn the enemy SWINDLED us, leaving four men injured.",
                  "word": "SWINDLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Because of the heavy rains there was an ABUNDANT supply of water.",
                  "word": "ABUNDANT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Each child took a short STRIDE around the block on the pony.",
                  "word": "STRIDE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "There was a moment of silence before the game as a TRIBUTE to the player who had just died.",
                  "word": "TRIBUTE",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "STRIVE",
                  "answers": [
                    "try",
                    "work",
                    "wonder"
                  ],
                  "word": "STRIVE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "IMPULSE",
                  "answers": [
                    "urge",
                    "memory",
                    "desire"
                  ],
                  "word": "IMPULSE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DETECT",
                  "answers": [
                    "spot",
                    "notice",
                    "remember"
                  ],
                  "word": "DETECT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISREGARD",
                  "answers": [
                    "neglect",
                    "dislike",
                    "disobey"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISREGARD",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HARNESS",
                  "answers": [
                    "control",
                    "support",
                    "use"
                  ],
                  "word": "HARNESS",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DISSECT",
                  "answers": [
                    "examine",
                    "cut",
                    "display"
                  ],
                  "word": "DISSECT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INFURIATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "enrage",
                    "upset",
                    "disobey"
                  ],
                  "word": "INFURIATE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MOBILE",
                  "answers": [
                    "active",
                    "athletic",
                    "excited"
                  ],
                  "word": "MOBILE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SOOTHE",
                  "answers": [
                    "comfort",
                    "soften",
                    "thrill"
                  ],
                  "word": "SOOTHE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MOURN",
                  "answers": [
                    "pain",
                    "sorrow",
                    "grieve"
                  ],
                  "word": "MOURN",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "STABLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "firm",
                    "unchanging",
                    "large"
                  ],
                  "word": "STABLE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SWINDLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "cheat",
                    "steal",
                    "murder"
                  ],
                  "word": "SWINDLE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ABUNDANT",
                  "answers": [
                    "many",
                    "scarce",
                    "enough"
                  ],
                  "word": "ABUNDANT",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "STRIDE",
                  "answers": [
                    "step",
                    "pace",
                    "kick"
                  ],
                  "word": "STRIDE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "TRIBUTE",
                  "answers": [
                    "praise",
                    "enjoyment",
                    "tax"
                  ],
                  "word": "TRIBUTE",
                  "correct": "1"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ],
      "reviewTest": {
        "wordList": [
          {
            "word": "COMPLIMENT",
            "answer": "compliments"
          },
          {
            "word": "EPISODE",
            "answer": "episode"
          },
          {
            "word": "MOBILE",
            "answer": "mobile"
          },
          {
            "word": "PROTEST",
            "answer": "protested"
          },
          {
            "word": "SWINDLE",
            "answer": "swindled"
          },
          {
            "word": "DETECT",
            "answer": "detect"
          },
          {
            "word": "HORDE",
            "answer": "horde"
          },
          {
            "word": "MOURN",
            "answer": "mourned"
          },
          {
            "word": "PURSUE",
            "answer": "pursued"
          },
          {
            "word": "TORMENT",
            "answer": "torment "
          },
          {
            "word": "DISREGARD",
            "answer": "disregarded"
          },
          {
            "word": "ISOLATED",
            "answer": "isolated"
          },
          {
            "word": "NUISANCE",
            "answer": "nuisance"
          },
          {
            "word": "STRIVE",
            "answer": "strides"
          },
          {
            "word": "UNSETTLE",
            "answer": "unsettled"
          },
          {
            "word": "DISRUPT",
            "answer": "disregarded"
          },
          {
            "word": "JUNCTION",
            "answer": "junction"
          },
          {
            "word": "POSSESS",
            "answer": "possess"
          },
          {
            "word": "SUMMON",
            "answer": "summoned"
          },
          {
            "word": "WOE",
            "answer": "woe"
          },
          {
            "word": "DISSECT",
            "answer": "dissect"
          },
          {
            "word": "LOYAL",
            "answer": "loyal"
          },
          {
            "word": "PRECIOUS",
            "answer": "precious"
          },
          {
            "word": "ABUNDANT",
            "answer": "abundant"
          },
          {
            "word": "FLAWLESS",
            "answer": "flawless"
          },
          {
            "word": "INTERNAL",
            "answer": "internal"
          },
          {
            "word": "SLUMBER",
            "answer": "slumber"
          },
          {
            "word": "TOLERATE",
            "answer": "tolerate"
          },
          {
            "word": "CONSUME",
            "answer": "consumed"
          },
          {
            "word": "FULFILL",
            "answer": "fulfilled"
          },
          {
            "word": "QUALIFIED",
            "answer": "qualified"
          },
          {
            "word": "SOOTHE",
            "answer": "soothe"
          },
          {
            "word": "TRIBUTE",
            "answer": "tribute"
          },
          {
            "word": "CRISIS",
            "answer": "crisis"
          },
          {
            "word": "HARNESS",
            "answer": "harness"
          },
          {
            "word": "RESTRAIN",
            "answer": "restrain"
          },
          {
            "word": "STABLE",
            "answer": "stable"
          },
          {
            "word": "VOW",
            "answer": "vow"
          },
          {
            "word": "DEDICATED",
            "answer": "dedicated"
          },
          {
            "word": "IMPULSE",
            "answer": "impulse"
          },
          {
            "word": "SLACKEN",
            "answer": "slacken"
          },
          {
            "word": "STRIDE",
            "answer": "strides"
          },
          {
            "word": "WEARY",
            "answer": "weary"
          },
          {
            "word": "DISTRESS",
            "answer": "distressed"
          },
          {
            "word": "INFURIATE",
            "answer": "infuriate"
          }
        ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "part1": "Jack was pleased by the many",
            "part2": "he received about the way he looked.",
            "correct": "compliments",
            "word": "COMPLIMENT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It's impossible to",
            "part2": "the stain unless you examine the dress carefully.",
            "correct": "detect",
            "word": "DETECT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Mrs. Jackson",
            "part2": "the death of her husband for many years.",
            "correct": "mourned",
            "word": "MOURN"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Johnny constantly",
            "part2": "the class by making noises and throwing things.",
            "correct": "disrupted",
            "word": "DISRUPT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "I was surprised by how much money they",
            "part2": "; they're really quite wealthy.",
            "correct": "possess",
            "word": "POSSESS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "She kept her most",
            "part2": "jewels locked in a safe.",
            "correct": "precious",
            "word": "PRECIOUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Our picnic was spoiled by the",
            "part2": "of mosquitoes that suddenly descended on us.",
            "correct": "horde",
            "word": "HORDE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "A town was built at the",
            "part2": "of the two main highways.",
            "correct": "junction",
            "word": "JUNCTION"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The president",
            "part2": "businessmen from all across the country to the meeting.",
            "correct": "summoned",
            "word": "SUMMON"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Each chapter discusses a different",
            "part2": "in the life of the author.",
            "correct": "episode",
            "word": "EPISODE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Gus didn't",
            "part2": "hard enough to improve, and so he just stayed the same.",
            "correct": "strive",
            "word": "STRIDE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Andy has not been very",
            "part2": "since they put the cast on his leg.",
            "correct": "mobile",
            "word": "MOBILE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The doctor had to",
            "part2": "the animal to find out what had caused its death.",
            "correct": "dissect",
            "word": "DISSECT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It's quite a(n)",
            "part2": "for us to have to drive him home, but I suppose we have to do it.",
            "correct": "nuisance",
            "word": "NUISANCE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We",
            "part2": "him through three states before we finally caught up with him.",
            "correct": "pursued",
            "word": "PURSUE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The cure for the disease was very painful; it caused him greater",
            "part2": "than the disease itself.",
            "correct": "torment ",
            "word": "TORMENT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Her short unhappy life was full of",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "woe",
            "word": "WOE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Two men posing as insurance salesmen",
            "part2": "the lady out of her life's savings.",
            "correct": "swindled",
            "word": "SWINDLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "He",
            "part2": "the warning on the bottle, and swallowed all the pills in it.",
            "correct": "disregarded",
            "word": "DISRUPT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The rebels remained",
            "part2": "to their cause even after all hope of victory was gone.",
            "correct": "loyal",
            "word": "LOYAL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "When Ed received only half of his usual allowance he",
            "part2": "to his mother about it.",
            "correct": "protested",
            "word": "PROTEST"
          },
          {
            "part1": "In wintertime the village is cut off from the outside world; it is totally",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "isolated",
            "word": "ISOLATED"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The sudden noise",
            "part2": "us; we began to think that perhaps there was a robber in the house.",
            "correct": "unsettled",
            "word": "UNSETTLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Her paper was",
            "part2": "; no one could find a mistake in it.",
            "correct": "flawless",
            "word": "FLAWLESS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Jack took a few long",
            "part2": "to reach the other end of the gym.",
            "correct": "strides",
            "word": "STRIDE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Their hopes of having a daughter were finally",
            "part2": "when Marie was born.",
            "correct": "fulfilled",
            "word": "FULFILL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "In Holland, windmills are used to",
            "part2": "the power of the wind.",
            "correct": "harness",
            "word": "HARNESS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Delays",
            "part2": "Peter; he hates to be late for anything.",
            "correct": "infuriate",
            "word": "INFURIATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The lungs, heart, and liver are some of the",
            "part2": "organs of the human body.",
            "correct": "internal",
            "word": "INTERNAL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "He is so",
            "part2": "to his job that he will work all night to make sure everything is right.",
            "correct": "dedicated",
            "word": "DEDICATED"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Gail was supposed to be taking a little nap, but she soon fell into a deep",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "slumber",
            "word": "SLUMBER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Donna rubbed lotion on to try to",
            "part2": "the pain of the sunburn.",
            "correct": "soothe",
            "word": "SOOTHE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It was a serious",
            "part2": "for our company; we almost went out of business, but we managed to pull through.",
            "correct": "crisis",
            "word": "CRISIS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Our family",
            "part2": "two whole turkeys last Thanksgiving.",
            "correct": "consumed",
            "word": "CONSUME"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The lamp was not very",
            "part2": "; it fell over every time you brushed against it.",
            "correct": "stable",
            "word": "STABLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We have a(n)",
            "part2": "supply of tomatoes; we'll never be able to eat them all ourselves.",
            "correct": "abundant",
            "word": "ABUNDANT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The park is named Jones Field as a(n)",
            "part2": "to our mayor, without whom it would never have existed.",
            "correct": "tribute",
            "word": "TRIBUTE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The teacher can",
            "part2": "students who make mistakes, but she can't stand students who lie about them.",
            "correct": "tolerate",
            "word": "TOLERATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "He broke his",
            "part2": "never to take another drink.",
            "correct": "vow",
            "word": "VOW"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Don tried to overcome the",
            "part2": "to break things whenever he was angry.",
            "correct": "impulse",
            "word": "IMPULSE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "I became very",
            "part2": "of hotdogs after having them for supper every night for a month.",
            "correct": "weary",
            "word": "WEARY"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Our rate of working started to",
            "part2": "as we became more and more tired.",
            "correct": "slacken",
            "word": "SLACKEN"
          },
          {
            "part1": "As a lawyer he knows the law thoroughly; he is well",
            "part2": "to become a judge.",
            "correct": "qualified",
            "word": "QUALIFIED"
          },
          {
            "part1": "It took three of us to",
            "part2": "him from attacking the other man.",
            "correct": "restrain",
            "word": "RESTRAIN"
          },
          {
            "part1": "I was",
            "part2": "to find out that I had failed the exam.",
            "correct": "distressed",
            "word": "DISTRESS"
          }
        ],
        "type": "fitb"
      }
    },
    {
      "wordsets": [
        {
          "title": "2.10",
          "definitions": {
            "INFANTILE": {
              "word": "INFANTILE",
              "phonetic": "(in'-fan-tll)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">childish, babyish </p><p>An INFANT is a baby, a child in the first year or so of life, before it begins to walk or talk. INFANTILE means “of or relating to INFANTS.” INFANTILE diseases are sicknesses common to INFANTS. When used about adults, INFANTILE usually has a bad sense, “lacking the maturity or reasoning power of an adult.” </p><p>“His INFANTILE behavior during the speech shocked everyone.” </p><p>“Her INFANTILE attitude about doing household chores was most unpleasant.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: INFANT, n.</p>"
            },
            "FLABBERGAST": {
              "word": "FLABBERGAST",
              "phonetic": "(flab'-ÔøΩr-gast)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to surprise, astonish, amaze, astound </p><p>To FLABBERGAST someone is to fill him with surprise and astonishment, to make him so surprised that he can barely speak. </p><p>“His odd behavior FLABBERGASTED us.” </p><p>Someone who is FLABBERGASTED is amazed, aston- ished. </p><p>“I was FLABBERGASTED to discover that I had won first prize.” </p><p>In the Pretest, many people choose <i class=“def-ital\">delighted</i> as the word closest in meaning to FLABBERGASTED. But you can be FLABBERGASTED and not be <i class=“def-ital\">delighted</i> at all. </p><p>“Sue was FLABBERGASTED when she learned that she had failed the exam. She thought she had done quite well.”</p>"
            },
            "ACQUIRE": {
              "word": "ACQUIRE",
              "phonetic": "(ÔøΩkwlr')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to get, obtain </p><p>ACQUIRE means to <i class=“def-ital\">get</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">obtain</i>. You can ACQUIRE objects, or nonphysical things like knowledge or skill. </p><p>“After some hard bargaining, we ACQUIRED the house at a very low price.” </p><p>“She eventually ACQUIRED some skill in ice skating, but she was never really very good at it.” </p><p>“I’ve tried olives many times, but I haven’t been able to ACQUIRE a taste for them.”</p>"
            },
            "LEISURE": {
              "word": "LEISURE",
              "phonetic": "(IE'-zhÔøΩ)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">free time, spare time, ease </p><p>LEISURE is time which is free from work, spare time. </p><p>“The first settlers in this country had little LEISURE. Almost all their time was spent trying to survive in the wilderness.” </p><p>“In this country sports are a popular LEISURE activity.” </p><p>The phrase “at LEISURE” means “when one has free time” or “at one’s convenience.” </p><p>“Would you do me a favor and read through my report at your LEISURE?” </p><p>“While she was unemployed she was able to paint her entire house at LEISURE.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: LEISURELY, adj.</p>"
            },
            "ETERNAL": {
              "word": "ETERNAL",
              "phonetic": "(i-tern'-ÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">endless, lasting forever, timeless </p><p>Something is ETERNAL which lasts forever, which will never end. </p><p>“They promised ETERNAL love to one another.” </p><p>“Death finally brought him ETERNAL rest.” </p><p>ETERNAL is often used, in a joking way, to describe things that <i class=“def-ital\">seem</i> endless. </p><p>“This ETERNAL arguing has to stop!” The noun form of ETERNAL is ETERNITY, which means <i class=“def-ital\">endless time</i>. </p><p>“We hope it will never change for all ETERNITY.” </p><p>ETERNITY is also used for time that seems ETERNAL. </p><p>“We had to wait an ETERNITY for the bus to come.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ETERNITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "ADEOUATE": {
              "word": "ADEOUATE",
              "phonetic": "(ad'-ÔøΩkwit)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">sufficient, enough </p><p>ADEQUATE means “equal to what is needed,” <i class=“def-ital\">sufficient</i>. “She does not get ADEQUATE pay for the amount of work she does.” </p><p>“I think you will find that there is an ADEQUATE supply of food in the freezer.” </p><p>Often ADEQUATE has the sense of <i class=“def-ital\">just barely enough</i>. </p><p>“The supply of food is ADEQUATE for us, I suppose, but I wish we had more in case guests arrive.” </p><p>“He did an ADEQUATE job, although not an outstanding one.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: ADEQUACY, n.</p>"
            },
            "DEJECTED": {
              "word": "DEJECTED",
              "phonetic": "(di-jek'-tid)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">downcast, unhappy </p><p>DEJECTED means <i class=“def-ital\">unhappy</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">downcast</i>. The word usually suggests being in low spirits for a short time because of some disappointment or sad event. </p><p>“You seem DEJECTED today. I haven’t seen you smile once.” </p><p>“She was DEJECTED because the picnic had been called off.” </p><p>“We’ve tried to cheer him up, but he’s still DEJECTED.” </p><p>“Getting a D on a test would make anyone feel DEJECTED.”</p>"
            },
            "EXCLAIM": {
              "word": "EXCLAIM",
              "phonetic": "(eks-klAm')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to cry out suddenly and loudly </p><p>To EXCLAIM is to cry out or speak loudly because you are surprised, angry, hurt, happy, or feel some other strong emotion. </p><p>“He EXCLAIMED angrily at the amount of time it was taking.” </p><p>“They EXCLAIMED in delight over the idea of going to the beach.” </p><p>“We EXCLAIMED with wonder at the size of the elephant.“nAn EXCLAMATION is the act of EXCLAIMING, or something that has been EXCLAIMED. </p><p>“He stopped suddenly with an EXCLAMATION of surprise.</p><p> An EXCLAMATION <i class=“def-ital\">point</i>(!) is a sign that a sentence is very forceful and, if spoken, would be EXCLAIMED. </p><p>“‘We will never give in!’ they EXCLAIMED.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: EXCLAMATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "GENUINE": {
              "word": "GENUINE",
              "phonetic": "(jen'-yU-:;m)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">real, true, authentic, not faked </p><p>Something which is GENUINE is really what it is sup- posed to be. It isn’t fake or counterfeit. </p><p>“The man at the jewelry store said they were GENU- INE pearls.” </p><p>“I don’t think his sorrow is GENUINE. He just wants us to think he’s unhappy.” </p><p>“No one could be holier than she was. She was a GEN- UINE saint.”</p>"
            },
            "GIBBERISH": {
              "word": "GIBBERISH",
              "phonetic": "(jib'-ÔøΩrish",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">gib’-ÔøΩrish) n.: nonsense; confused, meaningless speech </p><p>GIBBERISH is confused speech or writing that is impossible to understand or make sense of. </p><p>“The child spoke nothing but GIBBERISH until she was seven years old.” </p><p>“He was trying to speak Chinese, but it sounded like GIBBERISH to me.” </p><p>GIBBERISH is often used about writing which is very technical or needlessly difficult to understand. </p><p>“His explanation of how the machine worked was so complicated that it seemed like GIBBERISH to us.”</p>"
            },
            "HURL": {
              "word": "HURL",
              "phonetic": "(her()",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to throw forcefully, cast, fling </p><p>To HURL something is to throw it, especially with force or violence. </p><p>“They HURLED rocks down at us from the top of the castle.” </p><p>“The force of the explosion HURLED him to the ground.” </p><p>“At the sound of the trumpet they HURLED themselves at the enemy.” </p><p>In the Pretest, <i class=“def-ital\">spin</i> is often chosen as the meaning of HURL, perhaps because HURL sounds like <i class=“def-ital\">twirl</i>, and to <i class=“def-ital\">spin</i> something is to <i class=“def-ital\">twirl</i> it.</p>"
            },
            "INVINCIBLE": {
              "word": "INVINCIBLE",
              "phonetic": "(in-vin'-sÔøΩb:)I)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">unconquerable, unbeatable See <i class=“def-ital\">in-</i> under Prefixes and <i class=“def-ital\">-able</i> under Suffixes. The vine part of the word comes from a Latin word meaning to conquer. Someone or something that is INVINCIBLE is not able to be beaten or conquered. </p><p>“We thought our team was INVINCIBLE until it finally lost a game.” </p><p>“His INVINCIBLE spirit overcame all obstacles.” </p><p>“The fort was INVINCIBLE: it withstood dozens of attacks.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: INVINCIBILITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "JUSTICE": {
              "word": "JUSTICE",
              "phonetic": "(juhs'-tis)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">fairness </p><p>JUSTICE is fairness, the quality of being fair or just, of giving to someone what he deserves. </p><p>“His sense of JUSTICE kept him from taking advantage of their problems.” </p><p>“We don’t want any favors, we only want JUSTICE.” </p><p>“He went into the courtroom expecting JUSTICE to be done, but the judge’s decision seemed quite unfair to him.” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Punishment</i> and <i class=“def-ital\">mercy</i> are often chosen as synonyms for JUSTICE. Both have to do with JUSTICE, but they aren’t the same thing. JUSTICE often involves <i class=“def-ital\">punishing</i> someone, but not always. And a person who has too much <i class=“def-ital\">mercy</i> or kindness will not provide JUSTICE. </p><p>Other forms of the word: JUST, adj.</p>"
            },
            "MELODIOUS": {
              "word": "MELODIOUS",
              "phonetic": "(mÔøΩIO'-dE-ÔøΩs)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">full of melody, sweet sounding, tuneful </p><p>A MELODY is a tune, a pleasing succession of musical sounds. Something which is MELODIOUS has MELODY, sounds sweet and tuneful. See <i class=“def-ital\">-ous</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“These songs are not very MELODIOUS. They are very unpleasant to hear.” </p><p>“She had a MELODIOUS voice. When she spoke, it sounded as if she were singing.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: MELODY, n.</p>"
            },
            "GORGEOUS": {
              "word": "GORGEOUS",
              "phonetic": "(gor'-jÔøΩs)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">magnificent, colorful, superb, dazzling </p><p>Someone or something that is GORGEOUS looks wonderful, usually because it is so spectacular or colorful. </p><p>“We could see mile after mile of beautiful lakes and forests; the view was simply GORGEOUS.” </p><p>“She looked really GORGEOUS in her expensive new gown.” </p><p>Many people think GORGEOUS means <i class=“def-ital\">pleasant</i>, but GORGEOUS is much stronger than that. Something that is GORGEOUS is quite beautiful.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "10",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "INFANTILE behavior.",
                  "answers": [
                    "odd",
                    "childish",
                    "poor",
                    "perfect",
                    "grown-up"
                  ],
                  "word": "INFANTILE",
                  "correct": "childish"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I was FLABBERGASTED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "hurt",
                    "delighted",
                    "surprised",
                    "interested",
                    "bored"
                  ],
                  "word": "FLABBERGAST",
                  "correct": "surprised"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Who will ACQUIRE it?",
                  "answers": [
                    "like",
                    "steal",
                    "wreck",
                    "sing",
                    "get"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACQUIRE",
                  "correct": "get"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "More LEISURE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "pain",
                    "hope",
                    "ease",
                    "happiness",
                    "work"
                  ],
                  "word": "LEISURE",
                  "correct": "ease"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ETERNAL sleep.",
                  "answers": [
                    "endless",
                    "restless",
                    "deep",
                    "short",
                    "long"
                  ],
                  "word": "ETERNAL",
                  "correct": "endless"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The supply was ADEQUATE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "similar",
                    "growing",
                    "sufficient",
                    "excellent",
                    "small"
                  ],
                  "word": "ADEOUATE",
                  "correct": "sufficient"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Somewhat DEJECTED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "angry",
                    "downcast",
                    "cheerful",
                    "surprised",
                    "vain"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEJECTED",
                  "correct": "downcast"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They EXCLAIMED.",
                  "answers": [
                    "laughed",
                    "jumped up",
                    "refused",
                    "cried out",
                    "swore"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXCLAIM",
                  "correct": "cried out"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GENUINE things.",
                  "answers": [
                    "real",
                    "new",
                    "beautiful",
                    "old",
                    "fake"
                  ],
                  "word": "GENUINE",
                  "correct": "real"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "All the GIBBERISH.",
                  "answers": [
                    "destruction",
                    "noise",
                    "excitement",
                    "nonsense",
                    "truth"
                  ],
                  "word": "GIBBERISH",
                  "correct": "nonsense"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "To HURL it.",
                  "answers": [
                    "catch",
                    "drop",
                    "break",
                    "spin",
                    "throw"
                  ],
                  "word": "HURL",
                  "correct": "throw"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We were INVINCIBLE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "respectable",
                    "unconquerable",
                    "weak",
                    "unknown",
                    "huge"
                  ],
                  "word": "INVINCIBLE",
                  "correct": "unconquerable"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Expecting JUSTICE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "fairness",
                    "gifts",
                    "punishment",
                    "rewards",
                    "mercy"
                  ],
                  "word": "JUSTICE",
                  "correct": "fairness"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Several MELODIOUS songs.",
                  "answers": [
                    "easy",
                    "memorable",
                    "harsh-sounding",
                    "tuneful",
                    "hateful"
                  ],
                  "word": "MELODIOUS",
                  "correct": "tuneful"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GORGEOUS scenery.",
                  "answers": [
                    "hilly",
                    "magnificent",
                    "huge",
                    "pleasant",
                    "ordinary"
                  ],
                  "word": "GORGEOUS",
                  "correct": "magnificent"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Can adults be INFANTILE?",
                  "word": "INFANTILE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would most people be FLABBERGASTED by a talking dog?",
                  "word": "FLABBERGAST",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do you ACQUIRE knowledge by reading?",
                  "word": "ACQUIRE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are the hours you spend in school your LEISURE time?",
                  "word": "LEISURE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are television programs ETERNAL?",
                  "word": "ETERNAL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is five dollars usually ADEQUATE money to buy a ten dollar book?",
                  "word": "ADEOUATE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a baseball player usually DEJECTED when he hits a homerun?",
                  "word": "DEJECTED",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do you use your voice to EXCLAIM?",
                  "word": "EXCLAIM",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a GENUINE diamond be worthless?",
                  "word": "GENUINE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it easy to understand someone who speaks GIBBERISH?",
                  "word": "GIBBERISH",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a baseball pitcher HURL the ball to the catcher?",
                  "word": "HURL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a defeated army INVINCIBLE?",
                  "word": "INVINCIBLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do most people want to be treated with JUSTICE?",
                  "word": "JUSTICE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are the MELODY and the words of a song the same thing?",
                  "word": "MELODIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are spiders usually considered GORGEOUS?",
                  "word": "GORGEOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "The teacher said she wouldn't put up with any more INFANTILE behavior in her class.",
                  "word": "INFANTILE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The teacher FLABBERGASTED them for talking in class.",
                  "word": "FLABBERGAST",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She is going to get a new car, because she ACQUIRES it for her work as a traveling salesperson.",
                  "word": "ACQUIRE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We sat on the porch drinking lemonade and enjoying our LEISURE.",
                  "word": "LEISURE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It seemed an ETERNITY before we could see the doctor.",
                  "word": "ETERNAL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We had to get ADEQUATE food for the twenty people who were coming to the party.",
                  "word": "ADEOUATE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Jim was DEJECTED when he heard that he couldn't go to the dance.",
                  "word": "DEJECTED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "\"Look! An island!\" the shipwrecked sailor EXCLAIMED with relief.",
                  "word": "EXCLAIM",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Bob wasn't upset at all. His anger was completely GENUINE.",
                  "word": "GENUINE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Pete sometimes sounds intelligent, but usually he speaks nothing but GIBBERISH.",
                  "word": "GIBBERISH",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The rocket HURLED up into the sky.",
                  "word": "HURL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "In his daydreams he became an INVINCIBLE crime fighter.",
                  "word": "INVINCIBLE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He said there's no JUSTICE in this world. The most evil people always seem to be the most successful.",
                  "word": "JUSTICE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "She was very frightened and let out several MELODIOUS screams.",
                  "word": "MELODIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It was a GORGEOUS garden, full of very beautiful flowers.",
                  "word": "GORGEOUS",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "INFANTILE",
                  "answers": [
                    "happy",
                    "silly",
                    "babyish"
                  ],
                  "word": "INFANTILE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FLABBERGAST",
                  "answers": [
                    "interest",
                    "surprise",
                    "astound"
                  ],
                  "word": "FLABBERGAST",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ACQUIRE",
                  "answers": [
                    "need",
                    "get",
                    "obtain"
                  ],
                  "word": "ACQUIRE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "LEISURE",
                  "answers": [
                    "ease",
                    "freedom",
                    "silence"
                  ],
                  "word": "LEISURE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ETERNAL",
                  "answers": [
                    "forever",
                    "usual",
                    "always"
                  ],
                  "word": "ETERNAL",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "ADEQUATE",
                  "answers": [
                    "plenty",
                    "little",
                    "enough"
                  ],
                  "word": "ADEOUATE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEJECTED",
                  "answers": [
                    "unhappy",
                    "worried",
                    "cruel"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEJECTED",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EXCLAIM",
                  "answers": [
                    "shout",
                    "sing",
                    "yell"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXCLAIM",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GENUINE",
                  "answers": [
                    "true",
                    "clear",
                    "real"
                  ],
                  "word": "GENUINE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GIBBERISH",
                  "answers": [
                    "strange",
                    "dangerous",
                    "silly"
                  ],
                  "word": "GIBBERISH",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HURL",
                  "answers": [
                    "toss",
                    "fling",
                    "wet"
                  ],
                  "word": "HURL",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INVINCIBLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "powerful",
                    "warlike",
                    "unbeatable"
                  ],
                  "word": "INVINCIBLE",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "JUSTICE",
                  "answers": [
                    "right",
                    "fairness",
                    "kindness"
                  ],
                  "word": "JUSTICE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MELODIOUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "sweet",
                    "new",
                    "musical"
                  ],
                  "word": "MELODIOUS",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "GORGEOUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "magnificent",
                    "lovely",
                    "huge"
                  ],
                  "word": "GORGEOUS",
                  "correct": "2"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.11",
          "definitions": {
            "INJURIOUS": {
              "word": "INJURIOUS",
              "phonetic": "(in-jUr'-E-ÔøΩs)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">causing injury, harmful </p><p>INJURIOUS is the adjective from INJURY, which means <i class=“def-ital\">harm, damage, wrongful action</i>. INJURIOUS means “causing, or tending to cause, an INJURY.” </p><p>“Smoking is INJURIOUS to your health.” </p><p>“He complained about the INJURIOUS treatments he had received from the phony doctor.” </p><p>In the Pretest, <i class=“def-ital\">wild</i> is a common choice as the meaning of INJURIOUS, probably because of confusion with the word <i class=“def-ital\">furious</i>. </p><p>Other forms of the word: INJURE,v.INJURY,n.</p>"
            },
            "MORSEL": {
              "word": "MORSEL",
              "phonetic": "(mor'-sÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a bit, small piece, scrap </p><p>MORSEL comes from a Latin word meaning to <i class=“def-ital\">bite</i>. A MORSEL is a small piece of food that could be eaten in one bite. </p><p>“You must eat every MORSEL on your plate before you get dessert.” </p><p>“He ate the last MORSEL of bread, and then there was nothing left.\"</p><p> MORSEL can also be used about a small piece of news, knowledge, or the like. </p><p>“They picked up a few MORSELS of information about their ancestors there, but nothing very interesting.”</p>"
            },
            "PILLAR": {
              "word": "PILLAR",
              "phonetic": "(pil'-ÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a column, post </p><p>A PILLAR is a firm upright post which supports a ceiling or a building. </p><p>“Using all his strength Samson broke the PILLARS, and the building collapsed on top of him.” </p><p>PILLAR is also used generally about a person or thing that provides strong support. </p><p>“He was a PILLAR of the community. Without him this wouldn’t be as good a place to live.”</p>"
            },
            "EXTERIOR": {
              "word": "EXTERIOR",
              "phonetic": "(eks-tEr'-EÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">outside, outer, external </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">ex-</i> under Prefixes. EXTERIOR means <i class=“def-ital\">outer, outside</i>. </p><p>“They painted the EXTERIOR walls of the house and left the inside walls alone.” </p><p> “The EXTERIOR appearance of the building had faded over the years from the wind and the rain.” </p><p>EXTERIOR can also be used as a noun. “He had a rugged EXTERIOR\"—that is, his outside appearance was strong and rough looking. The opposite of EXTERIOR is interior, which means <i class=“def-ital\">inner, inside</i>.</p>"
            },
            "PREPOSTEROUS": {
              "word": "PREPOSTEROUS",
              "phonetic": "(pri-pos'-tÔøΩr-ÔøΩs)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">absurd, completely foolish, totally unreasonable </p><p>Anything PREPOSTEROUS is absolutely absurd, completely without sense or reason. It comes from a Latin word meaning “having the back end in front.” See <i class=“def-ital\">pre-</i> under Prefixes and <i class=“def-ital\">-ous</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“His ideas about the use of chewing gum to repair tires was PREPOSTEROUS.” </p><p>“She has the PREPOSTEROUS notion that telephone poles grow right where they are.” </p><p>“The book is PREPOSTEROUS. Nobody acts the way the author says they do.”</p>"
            },
            "INSPIRE": {
              "word": "INSPIRE",
              "phonetic": "(in-splr')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to influence, arouse, uplift, exalt, encourage </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">in-</i> under Prefixes. The spire part of the word comes from the Latin word for breathe, which is also the source for words like expire, perspire, and conspire. To INSPIRE people is to breathe life, purpose, excitement, or some other feeling into them, to uplift or encourage them. </p><p>“The coach’s speech at halftime INSPIRED the team to try even harder.” </p><p>“The teacher INSPIRED in Jane a desire to learn more about the subject.” </p><p>“We were all INSPIRED by your wonderful example.” </p><p>“The foreman’s harsh words INSPIRED a great deal of anger among the workers.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: INSPIRATION,n.</p>"
            },
            "PROGRESS": {
              "word": "PROGRESS",
              "phonetic": "(prog'-res)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">advance, forward movement PROGRESS is forward movement toward a goal. It is advancement or improvement. See <i class=“def-ital\">pro-</i> under Prefixes. </p><p>“We made some PROGRESS through the snowstorm, but finally we became stuck.” </p><p>“There was little PROGRESS in their efforts to end the war.” </p><p>“Scientists have made PROGRESS, but they still can- not cure the disease.” </p><p>The phrase “in PROGRESS” means “in the act of going forward,” still happening. </p><p>“He turned on the television show while it was in PROGRESS.” </p><p></p><p>PROGRESS is also a verb, pronounced pr:rgres’. </p><p>“He PROGRESSED rapidly for a while, but then seemed to get worse.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: PROGRESSION, n. </p><p>PROGRESSIVE, adj.</p>"
            },
            "CONSULT": {
              "word": "CONSULT",
              "phonetic": "(kÔøΩn-suhlt')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to confer, seek the advice of, refer to </p><p>To CONSULT something is to go to it for information, to refer to it.n“He CONSULTED the dictionary for the correct spelling of the word.“n“Did you CONSULT the phone book before you dialed the number?“nYou can also CONSULT a person. </p><p>“The teacher CONSULTED the principal before taking her class to the museum.“nTo CONSULT <i class=“def-ital\">with</i> someone is to confer with him, to talk over a problem and get advice. </p><p>“She CONSULTED with three lawyers about the complicated case.” </p><p>“I want to CONSULT with another doctor before deciding about the operation.“nOther forms of the word: CONSULTANT, n.</p><p>CONSULTATION, n.</p>"
            },
            "DAWDLE": {
              "word": "DAWDLE",
              "phonetic": "(do'-dÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to waste time, delay </p><p>To DAWDLE is to spend too much time doing something. </p><p>“He would DAWDLE over his homework and never get it done.“n“If she liked what she was doing, she would rush right through it. If she didn’t, she would DAWDLE and waste time and finally leave it half finished.“n“Come straight home from school and don’t DAWDLE along the way!” </p><p><i class=“def-ital\">Talk stupidly</i> is often picked as the synonym for DAWDLE. This is probably due to confusion with <i class=“def-ital\">twaddle</i>, which is a noun meaning “foolish, silly talk.”</p>"
            },
            "SUPERVISE": {
              "word": "SUPERVISE",
              "phonetic": "(sU'-pÔøΩr-vlz)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to oversee, superintend, direct </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">super-</i> under Prefixes. To SUPERVISE is to oversee work or workers, to look over them, so that you can make sure things are done right. </p><p>“I have to SUPERVISE every step of the job to make sure no mistakes are made.” </p><p>“The general himself SUPERVISED the landing of the soldiers.” </p><p>Someone who SUPERVISES is a SUPERVISOR. The act of SUPERVISING is SUPERVISION. </p><p>“He thought that SUPERVISION wasn’t really necessary. The workers could do the job by themselves.” </p><p>The most common mistake is to choose <i class=“def-ital\">help</i> as the meaning of SUPERVISE. To SUPERVISE people is to direct them, to give them orders, not to help them. </p><p>Other forms of the word: SUPERVISION, n. </p><p>SUPERVISOR, n. </p><p>SUPERVISORY, adj.</p>"
            },
            "UNDERGO": {
              "word": "UNDERGO",
              "phonetic": "(uhn-dÔøΩr-gO')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to experience, suffer </p><p>UNDERGO means to <i class=“def-ital\">experience</i>, usually to experience something unpleasant. </p><p>“We had to UNDERGO several tests before we were through.” </p><p>“My father will UNDERGO an operation for his heart murmur.” </p><p>“The witness UNDERWENT several hours of questioning at the trial yesterday.” </p><p>Usage: The past tense of UNDERGO is UNDERWENT.</p>"
            },
            "DEPRESS": {
              "word": "DEPRESS",
              "phonetic": "(di-pres')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to discourage, sadden; to lower, press down </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">de-</i> under Prefixes. To DEPRESS basically means to <i class=“def-ital\">press down</i>. </p><p>“When a car’s accelerator is DEPRESSED, the car goes faster.” DEPRESS is most often used in the sense “to press down on your spirits,” to discourage. </p><p>“The news of his death DEPRESSED all of us.” </p><p>“Joan was DEPRESSED by her failure to pass the course.” </p><p>“He has looked so DEPRESSED lately. Let’s try to cheer him up.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: DEPRESSING, adj. DEPRESSION, n.</p>"
            },
            "HUMANE": {
              "word": "HUMANE",
              "phonetic": "(hyU-mAn')",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">kind, compassionate, tender, benevolent </p><p>HUMANE, with an <i class=“def-ital\">e</i>, was once just another way of spelling <i class=“def-ital\">human</i>. The word has come to be used, however, only about the kindest or gentlest qualities of human beings. To be HUMANE is to be full of sympathy and consideration for other people or for animals. </p><p>“They were noted for their HUMANE treatment of the poor. No one was allowed to go hungry or home- less.” </p><p>“He was a HUMANE boss. He gave his workers time off if they really needed it.”</p>"
            },
            "FEE": {
              "word": "FEE",
              "phonetic": "(fE)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a charge, payment </p><p>A FEE is a charge for services. It is usually for professional services, like those of a doctor or a lawyer. </p><p>“The lawyer’s FEE was so high that we wondered if it had been worthwhile going to court.” </p><p>The word can also be used about any charge made for a right or privilege. </p><p>“The club raised its membership FEE by five dollars.” </p><p>“There is a small FEE for the use of the tennis courts.”</p>"
            },
            "INHABIT": {
              "word": "INHABIT",
              "phonetic": "(in-hab'-it)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to live in, dwell in </p><p>See <i class=“def-ital\">in-1</i> under Prefixes. To INHABIT a place is to live in it. </p><p>“Several million people INHABIT that city.” </p><p>“A family of raccoons INHABITS the woods behind our house.” </p><p>An INHABITANT is someone who INHABITS a place, a resident. </p><p>“The firemen rescued all the INHABITANTS of the building.</p><p>” Many people choose get used to as the meaning of IN- HABIT, probably because they are confused by the word habit. </p><p>Other forms of the word: INHABITANT, n.</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "11",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Threw a MORSEL.",
                  "answers": [
                    "few",
                    "bit",
                    "number",
                    "lot",
                    "bundle"
                  ],
                  "word": "MORSEL",
                  "correct": "bit"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Strong PILLARS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "walls",
                    "foundations",
                    "bell towers",
                    "columns",
                    "door frames"
                  ],
                  "word": "PILLAR",
                  "correct": "columns"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The EXTERIOR part.",
                  "answers": [
                    "inner",
                    "worst",
                    "rear",
                    "first",
                    "outside"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXTERIOR",
                  "correct": "outside"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PREPOSTEROUS remarks.",
                  "answers": [
                    "useless",
                    "unkind",
                    "absurd",
                    "pleasant",
                    "serious"
                  ],
                  "word": "PREPOSTEROUS",
                  "correct": "absurd"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They INSPIRED him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "influenced",
                    "amused",
                    "discouraged",
                    "concerned",
                    "interested"
                  ],
                  "word": "INSPIRE",
                  "correct": "influenced"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SUPERVISE them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "speak to",
                    "obey",
                    "hire",
                    "help",
                    "oversee"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUPERVISE",
                  "correct": "oversee"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "What will they UNDERGO?",
                  "answers": [
                    "lose",
                    "see",
                    "dig",
                    "deserve",
                    "experience"
                  ],
                  "word": "UNDERGO",
                  "correct": "experience"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Their remarks DEPRESS me.",
                  "answers": [
                    "confuse",
                    "discourage",
                    "anger",
                    "calm",
                    "influence"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEPRESS",
                  "correct": "discourage"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Rapid PROGRESS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "change",
                    "retreat",
                    "advance",
                    "decision",
                    "profit"
                  ],
                  "word": "PROGRESS",
                  "correct": "advance"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CONSULT with him.",
                  "answers": [
                    "joke",
                    "confer",
                    "work",
                    "argue",
                    "visit"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONSULT",
                  "correct": "confer"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Known to DAWDLE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "give up",
                    "wonder",
                    "work hard",
                    "talk stupidly",
                    "waste time"
                  ],
                  "word": "DAWDLE",
                  "correct": "waste time"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HUMANE people",
                  "answers": [
                    "pretty",
                    "kindhearted",
                    "popular",
                    "crazy",
                    "angry"
                  ],
                  "word": "HUMANE",
                  "correct": "kindhearted"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Low FEE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "charge",
                    "value",
                    "spot",
                    "tide",
                    "note"
                  ],
                  "word": "FEE",
                  "correct": "charge"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INHABIT the castle.",
                  "answers": [
                    "enter",
                    "get used to",
                    "discover",
                    "live in",
                    "attack"
                  ],
                  "word": "INHABIT",
                  "correct": "live in"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Should children play with INJURIOUS toys?",
                  "word": "INJURIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a few MORSELS make a good meal?",
                  "word": "MORSEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it usually easy to break a PILLAR?",
                  "word": "PILLAR",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Does a can have an EXTERIOR?",
                  "word": "EXTERIOR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would it be PREPOSTEROUS to pay someone a million dollars to clean your home?",
                  "word": "PREPOSTEROUS",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can an object INSPIRE a person?",
                  "word": "INSPIRE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do students usually SUPERVISE teachers?",
                  "word": " SUPERVISE ",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do college students usually UNDERGO four years of schooling before they receive their degrees?",
                  "word": " UNDERGO ",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would a person usually be DEPRESSED if he had just lost his job?",
                  "word": " DEPRESSED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can a person who walks very slowly make PROGRESS?",
                  "word": " PROGRESS ",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do you CONSULT a problem to get the answer?",
                  "word": " CONSULT ",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people who DAWDLE always get where they are going on time?",
                  "word": "DAWDLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is everybody HUMANE?",
                  "word": "HUMANE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is there a FEE for free services?",
                  "word": "FEE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can animals be INHABITANTS?",
                  "word": "INHABITANTS",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Jack was INJURIOUS with us when he found out what we had done.",
                  "word": "INJURIOUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He bought a huge MORSEL of wood, enough to last the winter.",
                  "word": "MORSEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Several wooden PILLARS held up the balcony.",
                  "word": "PILLAR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The team is so far EXTERIOR to ours that we'll never beat them.",
                  "word": "EXTERIOR",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "That was the largest bug I've ever seen. It was PREPOSTEROUS.",
                  "word": "PREPOSTEROUS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The artist must have been INSPIRED when he painted that picture.",
                  "word": "INSPIRE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Bill's father kept him under close SUPERVISION while he used the chainsaw.",
                  "word": "SUPERVISION",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The engineers decided to put in a tunnel so travelers could UNDERGO the mountain.",
                  "word": "UNDERGO",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I tried to DEPRESS what I thought, hut no one would listen to me.",
                  "word": "DEPRESS",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "His study of the language had PROGRESSED to the point where he could read it easily.",
                  "word": "PROGRESSED",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I shall have to CONSULT with your father before I can make a decision.",
                  "word": "CONSULT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He thought it was funny to frighten the boy by DAWDLING him over the side of the boat.",
                  "word": "DAWDLING",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They were very HUMANE in caring for stray cats and dogs.",
                  "word": "HUMANE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The doctor's FEE was much more than we expected.",
                  "word": "FEE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We INHABIT a small shack at the edge of town.",
                  "word": "INHABIT",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "INJURIOUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "hurting",
                    "harmful",
                    "twisting"
                  ],
                  "word": "INJURIOUS",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MORSEL",
                  "answers": [
                    "piece",
                    "end",
                    "crumb"
                  ],
                  "word": "MORSEL",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PILLAR",
                  "answers": [
                    "strength",
                    "softness",
                    "upright"
                  ],
                  "word": "PILLAR",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "EXTERIOR",
                  "answers": [
                    "appearance",
                    "outside",
                    "middle"
                  ],
                  "word": "EXTERIOR",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PREPOSTEROUS",
                  "answers": [
                    "silly",
                    "senseless",
                    "noisy"
                  ],
                  "word": "PREPOSTEROUS",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INSPIRE",
                  "answers": [
                    "worry",
                    "uplift",
                    "excite"
                  ],
                  "word": "INSPIRE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SUPERVISE",
                  "answers": [
                    "parent",
                    "boss",
                    "baby"
                  ],
                  "word": " SUPERVISE S",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "UNDERGO",
                  "answers": [
                    "experience",
                    "suffer",
                    "worry"
                  ],
                  "word": "UNDERGO",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DEPRESS",
                  "answers": [
                    "make thoughtful",
                    "sadden",
                    "lower"
                  ],
                  "word": "DEPRESS",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PROGRESS",
                  "answers": [
                    "ahead",
                    "forward",
                    "always"
                  ],
                  "word": " PROGRESS ",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "CONSULT",
                  "answers": [
                    "advise",
                    "inform",
                    "approve"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONSULT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DAWDLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "giggle",
                    "idle",
                    "delay"
                  ],
                  "word": "DAWDLE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "HUMANE",
                  "answers": [
                    "tender¬∑",
                    "gentle",
                    "normal"
                  ],
                  "word": "HUMANE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FEE",
                  "answers": [
                    "money",
                    "payment",
                    "loan"
                  ],
                  "word": "FEE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "INHABIT",
                  "answers": [
                    "reside",
                    "visit",
                    "live"
                  ],
                  "word": "INHABIT",
                  "correct": "1"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "2.12",
          "definitions": {
            "CONTRACT": {
              "word": "CONTRACT",
              "phonetic": "(kon'-trakt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">an agreement </p><p>A CONTRACT is a legal agreement between two or more persons or companies to do something. For a CON- TRACT to be <i class=“def-ital\">legal</i>, both sides have to state that they will do something. For example, a person agrees to perform a service and a company agrees to pay him for it. If either side fails to live up to the agreement, it could be sued.</p><p>“She signed a CONTRACT with the company stating that she would do the job in six months for ten thou- sand dollars.” </p><p>“He said he didn’t have to do the work because it wasn’t in his CONTRACT with them.” </p><p>“Our CONTRACT expires at midnight. Unless we agree on a new one, no one will go to work.”</p>"
            },
            "SLITHER": {
              "word": "SLITHER",
              "phonetic": "(sliTH'-ÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to slide, slip </p><p>SLITHER is one of many words that begin with the letters <i class=“def-ital\">sl</i> and which have the meaning of <i class=“def-ital\">slip or slide</i>. The motion in SLITHER is like that of a snake sliding over the ground. To SLITHER is to slide along in a side-to-side way. </p><p>“The snake SLITHERED away into the bushes.” </p><p>“The children SLITHERED across the ice on their backsides.” </p><p>SLITHERY, the adjective form, means slippery. </p><p>“The wet soap was SLITHERY and hard to hold.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: SLITHERY, adj.</p>"
            },
            "LEGISLATOR": {
              "word": "LEGISLATOR",
              "phonetic": "(lej'-is-lA-tÔøΩr)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a lawmaker </p><p>LEGISLATOR comes from the Latin word for <i class=“def-ital\">law</i>, which is also the source of <i class=“def-ital\">legal</i> and <i class=“def-ital\">legitimate</i>. A LEGISLATOR is a person who makes laws, a member of a lawmaking body like the Senate or the House of Representatives. </p><p>“She was one of the three LEGISLATORS to oppose the president’s plan.\"</p><p>A LEGISLATURE is the body of persons who make laws. To LEGISLATE is to make laws. LEGISLATION is the act of making laws, or the laws made. On the Pretest, many people choose judge as the synonym for LEGISLATOR. But a <i class=“def-ital\">judge</i> belongs to a totally separate branch of government. Judges interpret the laws that LEGISLATORS make.</p><p> Other forms of the word: LEGISLATE, v. </p><p>LEGISLATION, n. </p><p>LEGISLATURE, n.</p>"
            },
            "PARALLEL": {
              "word": "PARALLEL",
              "phonetic": "(par'-ÔøΩlel)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">going in the same direction, side by side; similar </p><p>PARALLEL lines are lines which go in the same direction and, even if they went on forever, would never meet. So PARALLEL is used about things which run side by side without crossing each other. </p><p>“The two roads ran PARALLEL to each other for several miles before they branched off.” </p><p>In general use PARALLEL means “having the same course, nature, or tendency,” <i class=“def-ital\">similar</i>.n“There was a PARALLEL increase in both poverty and crime in that city.”</p>"
            },
            "LOGICAL": {
              "word": "LOGICAL",
              "phonetic": "(loj'-i-kÔøΩI",
              "pos": "or",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">loj-ÔøΩkÔøΩI) adj.: agreeing with </p><p>LOGIC, reasonable LOGIC is sound reasoning. </p><p>“We all admired the LOGIC of her arguments.” </p><p>“There wasn’t much LOGIC in what he said.” </p><p>LOGICAL means “having LOGIC, according to LOGIC,” <i class=“def-ital\">reasonable</i>. See <i class=“def-ital\">-al</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“His speech sounded impressive, but it wasn’t very LOGICAL. When you really studied it, it didn’t make any sense at all.” </p><p>“The LOGICAL place to start looking for the missing pen is wherever you saw it last.” </p><p>“She was a LOGICAL person. She never jumped to conclusions, and always had a good reason for what- ever she did.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: LOGIC, n.</p>"
            },
            "FIENDISH": {
              "word": "FIENDISH",
              "phonetic": "(fEn'-dish)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">devilish, cruel and wicked </p><p>A FIEND was originally an enemy, the opposite of a friend. From this it came to be used only about devils, who are the enemies of mankind. Now it is used generally about any very cruel or wicked person. </p><p>“He must have been a FIEND to murder them all in cold blood.” </p><p>Something which is FIENDISH is appropriate to a FIEND; it is cruel and savage. See <i class=“def-ital\">-ish</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“He took a FIENDISH delight in pulling the wings off flies.” </p><p>“With a FIENDISH laugh he jumped out at them from behind the bush.” </p><p>“The FIENDISH old woman frightened little chil- dren.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: FIEND, n.</p>"
            },
            "MONARCH": {
              "word": "MONARCH",
              "phonetic": "(mon'-grk)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a ruler, a king or queen </p><p>A MONARCH is someone, like a king or queen, who is the ruler of a kingdom or empire. </p><p>“Queen Victoria was the MONARCH of the British Empire for many years.” </p><p>“He dreamed of being a MONARCH and having power over millions of people.” A MONARCHY is a government ruled by a MONARCH. “England is a limited MONARCHY. Its king or queen has very little real power any more.” Other forms of the word: MONARCHY, n.</p>"
            },
            "RECOLLECT": {
              "word": "RECOLLECT",
              "phonetic": "(re-kg-lekt')",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to remember, recall, bring to mind again </p><p>To RECOLLECT is to remember, to call to mind. RECOLLECT usually suggests more effort than remember. </p><p>“He tried to RECOLLECT how he had fixed the television set before.” </p><p>“Do you RECOLLECT what their telephone number is?” </p><p>“I can’t quite RECOLLECT what the score of that game was.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: RECOLLECTION, n.</p>"
            },
            "SNICKER": {
              "word": "SNICKER",
              "phonetic": "(snik'-gr)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to laugh, giggle </p><p>The word SNICKER is both a verb and a noun. SNICKER means to <i class=“def-ital\">laugh</i> or <i class=“def-ital\">giggle</i>, usually in an embarrassed or disrespectful fashion, as at a dirty joke. </p><p>“They SNICKERED at the cartoons in the magazine.” </p><p>“The speaker was annoyed at the SNICKERS from the back of the room.” </p><p>Usage: SNICKER is sometimes spelled snigger.</p>"
            },
            "VERDICT": {
              "word": "VERDICT",
              "phonetic": "(ver'-dikt)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">a decision, judgment </p><p>n law, a VERDICT is a decision reached, by a jury for example, about the guilt or innocence of someone who is on trial. </p><p>“The jury returned a VERDICT of guilty on all the charges against him.” </p><p>“The jury’s VERDICT was that the defendant had to pay us the ten thousand dollars he owed us.” </p><p>VERDICT can also be used about any kind of decision or opinion, especially one reached after carefully weighing the evidence. </p><p>“The doctors’ VERDICT was that he only had six months to live.” </p><p>“The voters will return their VERDICT on the mayor’s performance in the election this fall.”</p>"
            },
            "BARBARIC": {
              "word": "BARBARIC",
              "phonetic": "(bahr-bar'-ik)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">savage, uncivilized </p><p>A BARBARIAN is a person who is wild and almost completely uncivilized. It is said that the ancient Greeks coined the word because foreigners who didn’t speak Greek sounded as if they were saying nothing but <i class=“def-ital\">barbar</i>. BARBARIC and BARBAROUS are similar adjectives re- lated to BARBARIAN. BARBARIC means “of or like BARBARIANS,” <i class=“def-ital\">wild, savage, uncivilized</i>. See <i class=“def-ital\">-ic</i> under Suffixes. </p><p>“The way they treat prisoners in that jail is BARBARIC.” </p><p>“The wild, BARBARIC music drove the audience wild.” </p><p>BARBARIC is frequently confused with ancient. Ancient people were not all BARBARIC, however; and BARBARIC people still exist today. </p><p>Other forms of the word: BARBARIAN, n., adj. </p><p>BARBAROUS, adj.</p>"
            },
            "DAMAGE": {
              "word": "DAMAGE",
              "phonetic": "(dam'-ij)",
              "pos": "n.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">harm, hurt, injury </p><p>DAMAGE is injury that causes some kind of loss, as in property, value, or usefulness. </p><p>“The storm caused a great deal of DAMAGE along the coast.” </p><p>“There was little DAMAGE to our car as a result of the accident.” </p><p>DAMAGE is also a verb, meaning to cause harm to. </p><p>“Those false rumors DAMAGED his reputation.” </p><p>“The early frost DAMAGED our crops.” </p><p>“His house was DAMAGED slightly when it was struck by lightning.”</p>"
            },
            "FESTIVE": {
              "word": "FESTIVE",
              "phonetic": "(fes'-tiv)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">joyous, merry </p><p>FESTIVE is related to the word feast, which is a large, splendid meal. Something which is FESTIVE is appropriate to a feast or a similar happy time. </p><p>“He wore his fancy shirt only on FESTIVE occasions\"—that is, only at joyous times like Christmas, weddings, holidays, etc. </p><p>“Winning the championship put everyone in a FESTIVE mood; we celebrated all night.” </p><p>A FESTIVAL is an occasion for feasting or celebrating. </p><p>“The summer FESTIVAL was so much fun that we are going again next year.” </p><p>FESTIVITY is FESTIVE activity, merrymaking. </p><p>“The FESTIVITIES began with boat races and a singalong.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: FESTIVAL, n. </p><p>FESTIVITY, n.</p>"
            },
            "SUSCEPTIBLE": {
              "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
              "phonetic": "(sÔøΩ-sep'-tÔøΩbÔøΩI)",
              "pos": "adj.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">easily affected, easily influenced, sensitive </p><p>SUSCEPTIBLE means easily affected or influenced. </p><p>“Many people are SUSCEPTIBLE to the cold; they seem to sneeze and sniffle all winter long.” </p><p>“We feared that our defenses were SUSCEPTIBLE to an attack from the rear.” </p><p>The word is often used about people whose emotions or decisions are easily influenced. </p><p>“The king is SUSCEPTIBLE to flattery. If you flatter him, he’ll give you almost anything you want.” </p><p>“He is very stubborn; he is not even SUSCEPTIBLE to reason.” </p><p>Other forms of the word: SUSCEPTIBILITY, n. </p><p>Usage: SUSCEPTIBLE is usually followed by <i class=“def-ital\">to</i>.</p>"
            },
            "DREAD": {
              "word": "DREAD",
              "phonetic": "(dred)",
              "pos": "v.",
              "deftext": "<p class=\"definition\">to fear greatly, be terrified of </p><p>To DREAD something is to have a deep fear of it. DREAD is especially used about things that are going to happen in the future. </p><p>“I DREAD going to this party. I never have a good time at large parties.” </p><p>“Sally DREADED the math exam, but she ended up doing well on it.\"</p><p>DREAD is also a noun, meaning great fear. </p><p>“He has a DREAD of going into a dark house all by himself.” </p><p>“No one could cure her of her DREAD of spiders.”</p>"
            }
          },
          "id": "12",
          "exercises": [
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Read the CONTRACT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "report",
                    "instructions",
                    "agreement",
                    "decision",
                    "statements"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONTRACT",
                  "correct": "agreement"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Watched them SLITHER.",
                  "answers": [
                    "fall",
                    "slide",
                    "run",
                    "jump",
                    "fly"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLITHER",
                  "correct": "slide"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They were LEGISLATORS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "leaders",
                    "teachers",
                    "judges",
                    "lawyers",
                    "lawmakers"
                  ],
                  "word": "LEGISLATOR",
                  "correct": "lawmakers"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Running PARALLEL.",
                  "answers": [
                    "side by side",
                    "to a point",
                    "across",
                    "opposite",
                    "at angles"
                  ],
                  "word": "PARALLEL",
                  "correct": "side by side"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Completely LOGICAL.",
                  "answers": [
                    "reasonable",
                    "wonderful",
                    "serious",
                    "true",
                    "stupid"
                  ],
                  "word": "LOGICAL",
                  "correct": "reasonable"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FIENDISH plans.",
                  "answers": [
                    "childish",
                    "wonderful",
                    "poor",
                    "difficult",
                    "devilish"
                  ],
                  "word": "FIENDISH",
                  "correct": "devilish"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "True MONARCH.",
                  "answers": [
                    "servant",
                    "owner",
                    "father",
                    "ruler",
                    "kingdom"
                  ],
                  "word": "MONARCH",
                  "correct": "ruler"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I can't RECOLLECT.",
                  "answers": [
                    "win",
                    "remember",
                    "say",
                    "forget",
                    "refuse"
                  ],
                  "word": "RECOLLECT",
                  "correct": "remember"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He SNICKERS.",
                  "answers": [
                    "groans",
                    "sighs",
                    "sneezes",
                    "shouts",
                    "laughs"
                  ],
                  "word": "SNICKER",
                  "correct": "laughs"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "What is your VERDICT?",
                  "answers": [
                    "belief",
                    "charge",
                    "decision",
                    "request",
                    "excuse"
                  ],
                  "word": "VERDICT",
                  "correct": "decision"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "BARBARIC people.",
                  "answers": [
                    "ugly",
                    "stupid",
                    "friendly",
                    "ancient",
                    "savage"
                  ],
                  "word": "BARBARIC",
                  "correct": "savage"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Aware of the DAMAGE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "dirt",
                    "harm",
                    "rubbish",
                    "problem",
                    "danger"
                  ],
                  "word": "DAMAGE",
                  "correct": "harm"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "In a FESTIVE mood.",
                  "answers": [
                    "friendly",
                    "nervous",
                    "merry",
                    "sad",
                    "generous"
                  ],
                  "word": "FESTIVE",
                  "correct": "merry"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They are all SUSCEPTIBLE.",
                  "answers": [
                    "untrustworthy",
                    "simple minded",
                    "strong willed",
                    "likeable",
                    "easily affected"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
                  "correct": "easily affected"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "We DREAD them.",
                  "answers": [
                    "laugh at",
                    "demand",
                    "hope for",
                    "refuse",
                    "greatly fear"
                  ],
                  "word": "DREAD",
                  "correct": "greatly fear"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-one",
              "id": "pretest"
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "Do at least two people have to be involved in a CONTRACT?",
                  "word": "CONTRACT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "If you dropped an iron, would it SLITHER to the ground?",
                  "word": "SLITHER",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is a senator a LEGISLATOR?",
                  "word": "LEGISLATOR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Are the sides of a triangle PARALLEL?",
                  "word": "PARALLEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Could a LOGICAL person make mistakes?",
                  "word": "LOGICAL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is an angel FIENDISH?",
                  "word": "FIENDISH",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is the United States a MONARCHY?",
                  "word": "MONARCH",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Can most people RECOLLECT the names of their brothers and sisters?",
                  "word": "RECOLLECT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do people often SNICKER when someone makes a fool of himself?",
                  "word": "SNICKER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do only juries reach VERDICTS?",
                  "word": "VERDICT",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Would someone who kills children be called BARBARIC?",
                  "word": "BARBARIC",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do floods cause DAMAGE?",
                  "word": "DAMAGE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do most people have fun at a FESTIVAL?",
                  "word": "FESTIVE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Is it good for an athlete to be SUSCEPTIBLE to injury?",
                  "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Do some people DREAD flying in an airplane?",
                  "word": "DREAD",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 1
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "The judge ruled that the CONTRACT was legal, and that everyone who signed it had to do what it stated.",
                  "word": "CONTRACT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The men SLITHERED through the small tunnel to escape from prison.",
                  "word": "SLITHER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He was defeated in his first attempt to be elected to the LEGISLATURE.",
                  "word": "LEGISLATOR",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The PARALLEL streets crossed just north of the city.",
                  "word": "PARALLEL",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Her advice was so LOGICAL that we had to agree with her.",
                  "word": "LOGICAL",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The kind old man tried to be FIENDISH to everyone he met.",
                  "word": "FIENDISH",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "When he became MONARCH he freed all the prisoners and declared a national holiday.",
                  "word": "MONARCH",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "He was knocked unconscious, and when he came to he couldn't RECOLLECT his name or where he lived.",
                  "word": "RECOLLECT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The grownups listened politely while Jim sang, but his younger brother SNICKERED.",
                  "word": "SNICKER",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "The mechanic's VERDICT was that our car was a total loss.",
                  "word": "VERDICT",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "It was a BARBARIC moment for him when he finally saw his parents after so many years.",
                  "word": "BARBARIC",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Norma DAMAGED the radio when she dropped it.",
                  "word": "DAMAGE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "They were in a FESTIVE mood; they didn't stop celebrating until dawn.",
                  "word": "FESTIVE",
                  "correct": "true"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "I am SUSCEPTIBLE of anyone who offers me that much money for so little work.",
                  "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
                  "correct": "false"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "Pete DREADED having to decide which school to go to.",
                  "word": "DREAD",
                  "correct": "true"
                }
              ],
              "type": "tf",
              "id": 2
            },
            {
              "questions": [
                {
                  "prompt": "CONTRACT",
                  "answers": [
                    "refusal",
                    "agreement",
                    "promise"
                  ],
                  "word": "CONTRACT",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SLITHER",
                  "answers": [
                    "slip",
                    "slump",
                    "slide"
                  ],
                  "word": "SLITHER",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "LEGISLATOR",
                  "answers": [
                    "congressman",
                    "policeman",
                    "lawmaker"
                  ],
                  "word": "LEGISLATOR",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "PARALLEL",
                  "answers": [
                    "corresponding",
                    "unknown",
                    "similar"
                  ],
                  "word": "PARALLEL",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "LOGICAL",
                  "answers": [
                    "hopeful",
                    "reasonable",
                    "understandable"
                  ],
                  "word": "LOGICAL",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FIENDISH",
                  "answers": [
                    "cruel",
                    "strict",
                    "evil"
                  ],
                  "word": "FIENDISH",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "MONARCH",
                  "answers": [
                    "general",
                    "emperor",
                    "king"
                  ],
                  "word": "MONARCH",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "RECOLLECT",
                  "answers": [
                    "recall",
                    "think",
                    "judge"
                  ],
                  "word": "RECOLLECT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SNICKER",
                  "answers": [
                    "chuckle",
                    "smile",
                    "giggle"
                  ],
                  "word": "SNICKER",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "VERDICT",
                  "answers": [
                    "judgment",
                    "opinion",
                    "punishment"
                  ],
                  "word": "VERDICT",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "BARBARIC",
                  "answers": [
                    "wild",
                    "false",
                    "uncivilized"
                  ],
                  "word": "BARBARIC",
                  "correct": "1"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DAMAGE",
                  "answers": [
                    "injure",
                    "hurt",
                    "stop"
                  ],
                  "word": "DAMAGE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "FESTIVE",
                  "answers": [
                    "joyful",
                    "merry",
                    "tiring"
                  ],
                  "word": "FESTIVE",
                  "correct": "2"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
                  "answers": [
                    "angry",
                    "weak",
                    "sensitive"
                  ],
                  "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
                  "correct": "0"
                },
                {
                  "prompt": "DREAD",
                  "answers": [
                    "shame",
                    "fear",
                    "terrify"
                  ],
                  "word": "DREAD",
                  "correct": "0"
                }
              ],
              "type": "mc-all",
              "id": 3
            }
          ]
        }
      ],
      "reviewTest": {
        "wordList": [
          {
            "word": "ADEQUATE",
            "answer": "adequate"
          },
          {
            "word": "DEPRESS",
            "answer": "depresses"
          },
          {
            "word": "GORGEOUS",
            "answer": "gorgeous"
          },
          {
            "word": "LOGICAL",
            "answer": "logical"
          },
          {
            "word": "PARALLEL",
            "answer": "parallel"
          },
          {
            "word": "CONSULT",
            "answer": "consulted"
          },
          {
            "word": "DREAD",
            "answer": "dreaded"
          },
          {
            "word": "JUSTICE",
            "answer": "justice"
          },
          {
            "word": "MELODIOUS",
            "answer": "melodious"
          },
          {
            "word": "PILLAR",
            "answer": "pillars"
          },
          {
            "word": "CONTRACT",
            "answer": "contract"
          },
          {
            "word": "EXTERIOR",
            "answer": "exterior"
          },
          {
            "word": "LEGISLATOR",
            "answer": "legislators"
          },
          {
            "word": "MONARCH",
            "answer": "monarch"
          },
          {
            "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE",
            "answer": "susceptible"
          },
          {
            "word": "DAMAGE",
            "answer": "damage"
          },
          {
            "word": "FIENDISH",
            "answer": "fiendish"
          },
          {
            "word": "LEISURE",
            "answer": "leisure"
          },
          {
            "word": "MORSEL",
            "answer": "morsel"
          },
          {
            "word": "VERDICT",
            "answer": "verdict"
          },
          {
            "word": "DEJECTED",
            "answer": "dejected"
          },
          {
            "word": "FLABBERGAST",
            "answer": "flabbergasted"
          },
          {
            "word": "ACQUIRE",
            "answer": "acquire"
          },
          {
            "word": "FEE",
            "answer": "fee"
          },
          {
            "word": "HURL",
            "answer": "hurled"
          },
          {
            "word": "INVINCIBLE",
            "answer": "invincible"
          },
          {
            "word": "SLITHER",
            "answer": "slithered"
          },
          {
            "word": "BARBARIC",
            "answer": "barbaric"
          },
          {
            "word": "FESTIVE",
            "answer": "festive"
          },
          {
            "word": "INFANTILE",
            "answer": "infantile"
          },
          {
            "word": "PREPOSTEROUS",
            "answer": "preposterous"
          },
          {
            "word": "SNICKER",
            "answer": "snickered"
          },
          {
            "word": "DAWDLE",
            "answer": "dawdles"
          },
          {
            "word": "GENUINE",
            "answer": "genuine"
          },
          {
            "word": "INHABIT",
            "answer": "inhabit"
          },
          {
            "word": "PROGRESS",
            "answer": "progress"
          },
          {
            "word": "SUPERVISE",
            "answer": "supervised"
          },
          {
            "word": "ETERNAL",
            "answer": "eternal"
          },
          {
            "word": "GIBBERISH",
            "answer": "gibberish"
          },
          {
            "word": "INJURIOUS",
            "answer": "injurious"
          },
          {
            "word": "RECOLLECT",
            "answer": "recollect"
          },
          {
            "word": "UNDERGO",
            "answer": "undergo"
          },
          {
            "word": "EXCLAIM",
            "answer": "exclaimed"
          },
          {
            "word": "HUMANE",
            "answer": "humane"
          },
          {
            "word": "INSPIRE",
            "answer": "inspire"
          }
        ],
        "questions": [
          {
            "part1": "Betty is",
            "part2": "to illness, and must be protected from all kinds of germs.",
            "correct": "susceptible",
            "word": "SUSCEPTIBLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The jury couldn't reach a(n)",
            "part2": "about whether he was guilty or innocent, so he had to stand trial again.",
            "correct": "verdict",
            "word": "VERDICT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Carl became",
            "part2": "whenever he thought of all the work he had left to do.",
            "correct": "dejected",
            "word": "DEJECTED"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Often developments in one field run",
            "part2": "with similar developments in other fields.",
            "correct": "parallel",
            "word": "PARALLEL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "I signed a(n)",
            "part2": "so I have to work for him or he will sue me.",
            "correct": "contract",
            "word": "CONTRACT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We managed to put the fire out quickly, but it still caused some",
            "part2": "to the house.",
            "correct": "damage",
            "word": "DAMAGE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Rainy weather always",
            "part2": "me.I almost feel like crying all the time.",
            "correct": "depresses",
            "word": "DEPRESS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The paintings were so",
            "part2": "that we couldn't take our eyes off them.",
            "correct": "gorgeous",
            "word": "GORGEOUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Several",
            "part2": "voted against the bill in Congress because it would cost too much money.",
            "correct": "legislators",
            "word": "LEGISLATOR"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The secret police have many",
            "part2": "ways of torturing people to make them confess.",
            "correct": "fiendish",
            "word": "FIENDISH"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Several large",
            "part2": "held up the huge roof of the building.",
            "correct": "pillars",
            "word": "PILLAR"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The storm damaged the",
            "part2": "of the house, but did no harm to the inside.",
            "correct": "exterior",
            "word": "EXTERIOR"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We hope that",
            "part2": "will be done at the trial, and that a fair decision will be reached.",
            "correct": "justice",
            "word": "JUSTICE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "A _C-_ average is",
            "part2": "for promotion, but it certainly isn't outstanding.",
            "correct": "adequate",
            "word": "ADEQUATE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Karen is so busy working she has no time for",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "leisure",
            "word": "LEISURE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "When they called on him to give a speech, he was",
            "part2": "; they had never asked him to speak before.",
            "correct": "flabbergasted",
            "word": "FLABBERGAST"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Jim's argument was so",
            "part2": "that we couldn't disagree with him.",
            "correct": "logical",
            "word": "LOGICAL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They sing together in a very",
            "part2": "fashion; they're delightful to listen to.",
            "correct": "melodious",
            "word": "MELODIOUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "He needed advice in preparing his income tax report, so he",
            "part2": "an accountant.",
            "correct": "consulted",
            "word": "CONSULT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "When the prince's father died, he became the nation's",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "monarch",
            "word": "MONARCH"
          },
          {
            "part1": "All Jim had for supper was a small",
            "part2": "of fish he found in the bottom of the refrigerator.",
            "correct": "morsel",
            "word": "MORSEL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Paula",
            "part2": "going to a hospital. She would start to sweat as soon as she walked in.",
            "correct": "dreaded",
            "word": "DREAD"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Mr. Smith",
            "part2": "the workers carefully to make sure they followed his orders.",
            "correct": "supervised",
            "word": "SUPERVISE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The bank has a machine that can tell if a bill is",
            "part2": "or fake.",
            "correct": "genuine",
            "word": "GENUINE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "His speech was complete",
            "part2": "Nobody knew what he was talking about.",
            "correct": "gibberish",
            "word": "GIBBERISH"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Ellen wanted to",
            "part2": "a complete collection of books by her favorite author.",
            "correct": "acquire",
            "word": "ACQUIRE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Two families",
            "part2": "that large house on the corner.",
            "correct": "inhabit",
            "word": "INHABIT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Timmy",
            "part2": "over breakfast on school days, but on Saturdays he gulps it down and rushes out of the house to play.",
            "correct": "dawdles",
            "word": "DAWDLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Our living conditions were almost",
            "part2": "; there was no electricity, no heat, no running water. We felt like savages.",
            "correct": "barbaric",
            "word": "BARBARIC"
          },
          {
            "part1": "He wanted to be young forever, so he searched for a drug that would give him",
            "part2": "youth.",
            "correct": "eternal",
            "word": "ETERNAL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Some hospital emergency rooms charge a large",
            "part2": "for their services to discourage people from coming there.",
            "correct": "fee",
            "word": "FEE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The doctor was",
            "part2": "; he worked long hours at a small salary to help people.",
            "correct": "humane",
            "word": "HUMANE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Gary pulled the lizard off his arm and",
            "part2": "it violently away from him.",
            "correct": "hurled",
            "word": "HURL"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Dad said our behavior was",
            "part2": "and asked us if we were ever going to grow up.",
            "correct": "infantile",
            "word": "INFANTILE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The settlers had to",
            "part2": "years of hardship and work before they could be successful.",
            "correct": "undergo",
            "word": "UNDERGO"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The doctor said that eating too much rich food was",
            "part2": "to your health.",
            "correct": "injurious",
            "word": "INJURIOUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "His writings",
            "part2": "us all to lead better lives.",
            "correct": "inspire",
            "word": "INSPIRE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Several students in the back of the hall",
            "part2": "when the principal dropped his glasses.",
            "correct": "snickered",
            "word": "SNICKER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "\"Look out!\" Al",
            "part2": "when he saw Frank stepping into the path of the approaching car.",
            "correct": "exclaimed",
            "word": "EXCLAIM"
          },
          {
            "part1": "On this",
            "part2": "occasion I am sure everyone will have a wonderful time.",
            "correct": "festive",
            "word": "FESTIVE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Some people used to think that humans would never fly; they called the idea completely",
            "part2": ".",
            "correct": "preposterous",
            "word": "PREPOSTEROUS"
          },
          {
            "part1": "Because he is over sixty years old, it is difficult for him to",
            "part2": "his first-grade classmates.",
            "correct": "recollect",
            "word": "RECOLLECT"
          },
          {
            "part1": "The snake",
            "part2": "along the ground toward the man.",
            "correct": "slithered",
            "word": "SLITHER"
          },
          {
            "part1": "They couldn't convince him that his father was a thief. He had a(n)",
            "part2": "belief in his father's honesty.",
            "correct": "invincible",
            "word": "INVINCIBLE"
          },
          {
            "part1": "We were trying very hard, but we couldn't make any",
            "part2": "toward our goal.",
            "correct": "progress",
            "word": "PROGRESS"
          }
        ],
        "type": "fitb"
      }
    }
  ]
}